At this moment,
someone seeks to take my life.
If anyone has clues, report to me at once.
This group you mentioned,
what exactly is it?
The Viwat People,
founded by Banjong.
We all share the same goal,
to dethrone King Chaiyached.
I had my men infiltrate Lord Kosol’s estate
and they found this map.
I’m not the only one plotting rebellion.
Somdet Saenyakorn is
after the throne as well.
You killed young bunny before my eyes,
how could I possibly eat?
You, too, have a charm that entices me.
Oh!
It’s like…
something just brushed against my leg.
The giant snakehead fish I keep.
Some fish just swam into my leg too.
My own snakehead.
Kosol.
I…
may I play with your little one for a bit?
Go ahead.
Careful, it might bite.
Wait.
Why?
Did I hurt your little one?
Someone’s coming.
Stay here and wait for me.
I’ll lure them away.
Like this, In this state?
Go.
What are you dawdling for, Kosol?
You left me here alone
on purpose, didn’t you?
I even washed your clothes.
Don’t make me wash them for nothing.
Who’s there?
I said, who’s there?
Kosol?
Kosol.
Didn’t know you actually cared about me.
Of course I care.
We’re the only two humans in this forest.
If something happened to you,
how would I survive?
Don’t make me worry like
that again, understand?
I can’t promise you that.
Because I was born to face danger.
What I can promise you is...
I swear,
every time I survive and return,
I will come back to you.
Really?
I… I think…
you should get dressed first.
Stop swinging back and forth like that.
What leaf is this?
Smells so strong.
Wild basil leaves.
What do you use it for?
Rub it on to keep mosquitoes away.
You can be kind, you know.
Do you know that when you’re kind,
you’re actually very sweet?
No, I’m not being kind.
I just don’t want to see
you die of malaria.
That’s exactly what being kind is.
No. When I say no, I mean no.
Fine.
No means no.
You’re a wicked man.
Your heart’s as rough
as the soles of my feet.
Satisfied now?
I think the reason
I’d take poison isn’t heartbreak.
It’s because you’re like this.
Anyone living with you would go insane.
Why do you blame only me?
Don’t you think Banjong
might be at fault too?
You knew about me and Banjong?
Tell me about it.
Of course. I’m not a fool.
And I also know you two
exchanged long love poems.
So what did you do?
Did you beat me?
Or did you go thrash Banjong?
Tell me, Kosol.
Tell me.
If I had,
neither of you would still be alive today.
Then why did you just let it go?
Kosol Kosol!
Come back, Kosol.
Kosol.
Kosol!
Kosol, hey,
tell me first. Hey!
Don’t you fake sleep,
just got here, no way you’re out.
Wake up. Wake up, Kosol.
Hey, wake up.
Hey.
Tell me right now.
About me, you, and Banjong,
what was going on?
I want to know what happened
before I took poison.
You used to be quiet.
Didn’t talk much.
Are you saying I talk too much now?
Not just too much,
now you’re loud, brash,
and sharp-tongued.
Even though I used to teach you better,
you never got it right.
Today I’ll give you a new lesson.
Try cursing someone out for me.
Why would I do that?
I’ve got no reason to curse anyone.
Just imagine someone hurt you deeply.
You’d get mad and let it out.
Go on, try.
You… bad person.
Was that a curse or a lullaby?
Make it harsher.
Repeat after me.
Worthless scum.
Is that really okay?
We’re human.
Shouldn’t we talk things out calmly?
Throwing insults,
it won’t make things better.
But it’s satisfying, isn’t it?
Come on, say it again, worthless scum.
Worth… less scum.
- Louder.
- Worthless scum.
Yeah.
That’s more like it.
I used to teach you hundreds of times,
you never pulled it off.
But today you did it
without me even trying.
Might’ve even cursed harsher than me.
You’re always bossing me around.
I used to be meek, just let me be meek.
Why bother with me?
Because you’re the one
who asked me to make you stronger.
You said if you stayed weak and spineless,
you’d never reach your goal.
You know…
what my desire is?
Tell me, Kosol.
I honestly forgot.
Your desire,
is this.
Worradej.
This is really your desire?
You called me from the future
just to kiss a man?
But with a kiss this sweet,
I’m not surprised
that this would be your desire.
I’ve kissed you now.
So I can go home, right?
One.
Two.
Three.
Hup.
What? Still not home.
What’s with you?
It’s your first night here,
you already wanna go?
Didn’t you say you didn’t
want to see your father again?
Why go back then?
Not that home.
If not that home, then where?
Even if I say it, no one will get it.
I get it.
Must be the poison making you hallucinate.
Rest a bit more, you’ll feel better.
Don’t worry.
I’ll stay by your side.
Come to think of it,
a world with this giant rascal in it
isn’t so bad after all.
The soldiers I sent with the royal decree
to arrest Count Kosol,
were killed, their bodies dumped
by the forest edge.
I’ve come to report the rebel’s brutality.
He must be executed, Your Majesty.
No. Didn’t I already order,
Kosol be put through the fire ritual
to prove his innocence?
How can you kill him now?
But such a brazen act,
clearly shows Count Kosol defied
Your Majesty’s command.
It proves his treason beyond doubt.
There’s no need for further proof.
Kosol may have killed the soldiers
in self-defense.
That doesn’t mean he’s the one
who tried to assassinate me.
I don’t care. Either way,
I want to see Kosol walk through
the flames before me.
Understood.
As you wish, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
But if there’s a clash during the arrest,
and Count Kosol ends up dead,
it will be deemed unavoidable.
And where is Kosol now?
Last seen hiding in the western forest,
Your Majesty.
I haven’t been to the forest in ages.
I’ll come along then.
Chit, go get the bug-catching box.
I bet in that forest,
there are plenty of strange insects.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What’s that smell? Smells so good.
It’s little bunny.
Here.
That’s the second bunny you’ve killed.
What if it has a family? Then what?
Don’t you feel sorry for it?
Go wash up and eat.
We need to head out.
Where are we heading this time?
Haven’t we gone deep enough
into the forest?
We’ll head back to the city
and hide at Banjong’s place.
If we stay in the forest,
we won’t survive.
With you being this delicate,
you should’ve thought of that yesterday.
If you had thought of it yesterday,
we wouldn’t have had to suffer
here all night.
But...
before we go back,
I...
can I bathe with you
one more time?
Right here, Your Majesty.
Where the soldiers’ bodies
were dumped.
We believe Count Kosol
is hiding in this part of the forest.
Chit.
I heard there are plenty of
beautiful insects here.
Lead the way.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The fire just burned out.
They might still be nearby.
Search the area.
Two pillows.
That means there are two of them.
And who’s the other one?
Oh, dear brother.
If you’re going to camp out in the forest,
And you didn’t even invite me along.
You picked a great spot too.
Chit.
Do you hear a waterfall?
I do, Your Majesty.
Count.
Let me take a quick swim.
But we’re here to catch
a criminal, Your Majesty.
Let’s finish Count Kosol’s case first.
Then you can come back
to enjoy yourself later.
Count.
We searched everywhere
but didn’t find him.
Only two sets of footprints.
- Heading north.
- Follow them.
Yes, Count.
Kosol.
Where are you?
I’ve come to arrest you.
Come out quietly.
Your Majesty.
Please keep it down.
You’ll tip them off.
Oh, is that so?
Didn’t think of that.
The forest air’s refreshing though.
When this is over, let's
come back here again, Kosol.
Yeah?
When this is over,
let's come here again.
Don't act like
you're too happy.
Have you forgotten
you're my hostage
and I'm running
from the law for treason?
Go on. Lead the way.
Yes.
Don't run.
Come out quietly.
Come out.
- Wait, wait.
- What now?
I heard someone shouting.
Could it be soldiers
coming after us?
Probably. Sounds like Chaiyached.
They must've brought
soldiers to catch us.
So what do we do now?
Can you run for long?
I think they're still far off.
If we start running now,
they won't catch up.
I can handle it.
I’ve done Zumba
classes for hours.
Chid, Chid! Follow me, quick.
- This one's beautiful.
- Yes.
Hey.
Your Majesty.
If we keep dawdling like this,
we won’t catch Kosol in time.
Are you saying I’m dawdling?
I just stopped to catch
a few insects.
If you want me to walk faster,
I might not manage.
Better to take it slow like this.
Lead the way.
Yes.
Soldier.
The troops I ordered,
are they ready?
All set, sir.
They’re lying in wait
at the north edge of the forest.
If Kosol comes out, he’ll be caught.
Go.
Careful, Your Majesty.
I never took a long jump class.
You okay?
No. Can we rest first?
Then get on my back.
What?
If the soldiers catch up,
we’re done for.
Chid, follow me.
I have to catch this insect.
Yes.
- Keep up with him!
- Wait for me, Your Majesty!
How am I supposed to help?
Brother.
Oh my, that’s Father.
This time I’ve caught up
to you at last.
Give yourself up nicely
so I won’t have to use force.
Thing is, I rather like
using force.
Better tell your soldiers
to come at me all at once.
Seize him!
Go on, grab him!
Why are you in the way?
I’m taking care of Kosol.
Worradej.
How did you end up here?
I took him hostage.
Tell your soldiers to back off.
Or if you don’t care about
your son’s life, say so.
I’ll slit his throat right now.
Count, do you still
need to think about it?
Choose Worradej’s life first.
Deal with catching Kosol later.
Don’t follow me.
I’m grateful to you both.
From here, I can get
into the city myself.
You two go back and
keep an eye on Chaiyached.
Please take care, sir.
Mm.
You care for your brother so much
you have him followed everywhere?
No, I’m not worried about him.
I just want to keep an eye on him
to track his movements.
Like this time, we were lucky.
We made it in time to help.
Right.
I forgot you’re heartless.
No way you’d care about anyone.
You just had a sword to my throat.
Let’s see if you’re hurt.
Don’t touch me.
I’m just your hostage.
Even if I die, it wouldn’t
matter to you anyway.
Fine, sulk if you want.
Don’t think I’ll coax you.
I never wanted you to anyway.
How did you get here?
Come inside quickly.
Good thing.
You had people follow
Prince Chaiyached.
We made it in time to save him.
Brother Kosol, are you hurt anywhere?
Let me tend to your wounds.
Just a few bruises.
It’ll heal soon.
Nothing serious.
And you, Worradej?
Are you hurt anywhere?
At first I was fine.
But nearly died
with a sword at my throat.
If I hadn’t done that,
would we be here eating
while you sass me like this?
I wasn’t blaming you.
Why make a fuss?
I risked myself as a hostage
and still got scolded.
Weren’t you the one
who brought your father to catch Kosol?
Don’t play dumb.
Don’t you accuse me.
Even if he’s my father,
I had nothing to do with it.
If not you, then who?
- How would I know? If you wanna know,
- Enough.
While you’re hiding here,
don’t go out where people can see you.
The Count must have men
searching the city.
But they likely won’t come here.
Unless some loose tongue tells my father.
Who are you calling that, Pandao?
If you’re feeling guilty, take it.
I was just saying.
Just saying? There are plenty
of the Count’s children here.
- If you mean me, just say it.
- So what?
- What then?
Water.
Thanks.
Here, water.
Thank you.
Pandao.
The room might be a bit small.
Not as big as the Count’s house.
But it should do, right?
Of course. It’s fine.
If you need anything,
just tell me anytime.
Get some rest.
I’ll leave you be.
Wait, Banjong.
I…
I have something to ask you.
Sun and moon in the vast sky.
You wrote this verse for me, didn’t you?
Your memories…
they’ve returned?
I found this paper in my room.
Yes.
I wrote it for you myself.
And?
What does this poem mean?
Tell me.
It doesn’t hold
any deep meaning.
Just idle talk
about the weather.
Don’t think too much of it.
I’d better get some sleep.
I’m exhausted.
Wait, Banjong.
If it’s just idle talk
about the weather,
why would you
write me a poem?
Tell me right now
what this thing between us really is.
We work together.
We’re in the same Viwat People group.
We’re good friends.
And one day…
Banjong.
Worradej.
Did you give the tax ledger
to the Count to sign?
I did.
Father is reviewing it now.
It’ll take him a while,
so I came to see you first.
I have something
I want to talk to you about.
What is it?
Go on.
So…
I know what I’m about to say
might sound strange.
And it might make you
feel uncomfortable.
But I’ve thought it through.
I should tell you
rather than keep it
to myself alone.
Banjong.
I love you.
You’re the sun.
I’m the moon.
In the vast sky.
In the day,
I shine bright.
You drift away.
When I fade,
you return to light the night.
It’s always been
and will always be
this way through time.
After that day,
we stayed friends as before.
And no one spoke of it again.
The meaning of the poem is,
Even if the sun and moon
share the same sky,
they can never cross paths.
Why not?
We’re in the same group.
We share the same ideals.
Why can’t we love each other?
Since you’ve asked,
I’ll tell you everything.
So there’s no doubt left.
Back then,
I was just a commoner.
My parents
were taken to serve in
a nobleman’s house.
They were worked to the bone
and both died.
From that day on,
I hated all nobles.
But being born the son of a Lord,
that’s not your fault, Worradej.
It’s just…
a deep wound
for someone who was once a commoner.
That’s all it is.
That’s all I have to say.
Banjong turns down Worradej.
And… Banjong was the first
to find Worradej’s body.
Then Kosol said,
why do you only blame me?
Haven’t you thought
it could be Banjong?
That’s right.
It must be Banjong.
He was Worradej’s lover.
And it was Banjong
who drove Worradej
to take his own life.
And Worradej’s wish
must be around here somewhere.
No need for Conan.
I can solve the mystery myself.
Soon, I’ll be able
to go back home.
Back to my beloved concert.
This is me.
Queen. Mommy.
Mother. Fierce.
It’s me, Jade, my lord.
It’s me.
Jade?
You startled me.
How did you even get in here?
I didn’t want to wake
anyone in the house,
so I snuck in through the window.
Seeing that you’re still safe,
that’s enough to make me happy.
How did you even know I was here?
The Count came back to the manor
and made a scene.
He said you ran away with Lord Kosol.
I guessed you might’ve
escaped to this place.
So I came to check.
My lord,
from now on, I won’t ever
leave your side again.
I’ll follow you everywhere.
Please don’t send me away again.
- Please.
- All right, all right.
Let’s talk about it tomorrow.
For now, get some sleep.
Come, sleep here with me.
I can’t, my lord.
I’m just a servant.
I’m used to sleeping on a plank.
What servant nonsense?
You’re my friend.
Come, sleep with me.
I can’t, my lord.
I’ve never slept on a mattress.
I’m afraid I won’t sleep well.
Better to sleep on a plank.
You go ahead and sleep.
Suit yourself then.
Here, take this.
Take it.
Thank you so much, my lord.
What’s that smell? It’s lovely.
Jasmine, my lord.
If you wake up to the scent
of fresh flowers,
it’ll keep you refreshed all day.
Please wash your face first, my lord.
I’ve prepared warm water.
That Worradej.
Hey.
Are you out of your mind, Pandao?
Where did you take P’Kosol?
Take him where? I don’t know
what you’re talking about.
P’Kosol’s gone from the house.
How the hell were you
watching your master?
Letting that bastard Kosol
kidnap him like that?
Answer me!
I don’t know, my lord.
Have you found the Count, my lord?
Of course I have.
Kosol took Worradej hostage.
But then again…
I think he might’ve gone
and offered himself up.
So where is the Count now?
How would I know where they ran off to?
If you hadn’t let Worradej get caught,
I’d have Kosol by now.
Get out of my sight. Now.
Yes, my lord.
Keep an eye on that Jade.
He might know where Kosol
and Worradej are.
Kosol’s a cautious man.
In a tense situation like this,
he wouldn’t just stroll out
without telling anyone.
I think…
Kosol must’ve been taken.
But how…
is anyone’s guess.
Don’t look at me like that.
I’m this tiny, I couldn’t drag him
more than an inch.
I didn’t see a thing, my lord.
Jade’s just a servant.
He wouldn’t dare touch
Lord Kosol.
If it’s not you two, then who?
This isn’t the time for blame.
Let’s figure out first
where we might find Kosol.
- Banjong.
- Stay here.
- He’s one of mine.
- Banjong.
- Go open it.
Banjong.
The authorities posted at the market.
In two days, Kosol will face
the fire ordeal
to prove his innocence
in King Chaiyached’s murder.
The fire ordeal’s basically
a death sentence.
We have to save Brother Kosol.
Brother Banjong, what do we do?
I’ll speak to King Chaiyached myself.
Sir, wait for me, please.
My lord.
Banjong, letting Worradej
stay this close to you,
aren’t you afraid
there’ll be more trouble?
Kosol’s capture,
that was his doing.
It couldn’t have been anyone else.
Brother Banjong.
We all agree Worradej’s the problem.
He betrayed our group once before.
And now this happens again.
We need to get rid of him fast.
Otherwise, our Viwat People group
will fall apart before we reach our goal.
Just a little, please, dear brother.
Count, please don’t try
to bribe us.
If I say you can’t go in,
you can’t go in.
If I let you in, Count,
my head would surely roll.
I know that.
I’m not trying to force my way in.
I just want to get to know you all.
In case in the future
there’s something we
need to help each other with.
So we know each other first.
Come on, brother, just a sip.
It’s delicious.
We can’t drink on duty, Count.
Just one more watch
and we’re off, please wait.
Oh.
I already opened the jar by mistake.
Oh no.
If I leave it open,
the aroma will fade away.
Hmm. Smells so good, really good.
Here, have a whiff.
This is fine fermented rice wine.
Just one gulp, brother.
Wake up.
Wake up, wake up now.
Sir.
They’re both out cold, sir.
So much for “just one gulp.”
Is this rice wine or a sedative?
With this brew, even elephants drop.
Let’s go.
I forgot, the bolt’s on the inside.
Huh?
Then better climb the wall.
Step on my back, sir.
- Step on you?
- Go ahead.
Go ahead, sir.
Push, sir.
Pushing.
More, go on, sir.
Almost there.
Ow.
Ever since I came to the past,
it’s been non-stop adventure, Prince.
Something new every time.
Jade, climb up.
Yes, sir.
Careful, careful.
I’ll pull the rope for you.
Sir… Sir.
Sir.
Stop. Stop.
Let go.
- Stop.
- Let me go.
Sir.
- Stop. Stop.
- Let me go.
What did you say?
Worradej got shot?
And what did you get from
talking to Kosol?
The fire trial will be
our day of victory.
The reason I came today
is to invite you to break out.
Or if you’ve forgotten,
I’ll refresh your memory
through these bars.
I’ll just take you in
as my page boy.
I’m not fit for that, sir.
Jade, smack my butt.
Kiss me and say goodnight.
Banjong.
Sir. Sir.
Sir.
Cut.
Slate.
Help the Count first.
(The Count’s got blisters.)
(Everyone, look at this.)
(Rope burn.)
(Dedication level: insane.)
I’m fine.
That’s so scary.
Hurry up, you useless thing.
(Don’t scold me, please.)
Prince, come back.
(Please give us Prince back.)
Prince.
Good thing
Etan had men follow King Chaiyached.
(Which Tan?)
Keep rolling.
(It’s getting spicy.)
- First word wasn’t clear, son.
- Sorry.
Okay, rewind, son.