This time, I’ve finally caught you, bro.
Take a good look at yourself.
Why not call all your soldiers at once?
Keep an eye on Jade.
He might know where
Kosol and Worradech are.
Damn Worradech.
Are you crazy, Pandao?
Where did you hide Kosol?
Hide what? I don’t know anything.
Ever since I time-traveled here,
it’s been non-stop chaos, Prince.
Always something new.
Jade, climb up now!
Yes, sir.
I’ll help pull the rope.
M-My Lord…
My Lord.
- Stop
- Stop!
- Let go!
- Stop it, I said!
- Let me go!
My Lord.
- Let go of me!
- Stay still, damn it!
Don’t move.
(Singhanakhon Prison)
Thanks.
Let’s say we’re helping each other out.
But I’ll give you only the time it takes
to boil an egg.
If the master finds out, I’ll be scolded.
Banjong.
How is Worradech?
Did the Count capture him?
No.
He wasn’t caught.
Then where is he now?
Answer me, Banjong.
Where is Worradech now?
He said he was going
to see King Chaiyached.
But…
But what, Banjong?
Tell me what really happened.
Nothing.
Nothing happened.
I just worry about you.
Locked up in prison…
It must be rough for you.
Oh, please.
Don’t spout nonsense to my face.
This is the time
we need to be planning.
I already have a plan.
The day I walk through fire,
will be the day we claim victory.
Hurry up.
I’m giving you only
the time it takes to boil an egg.
Thank you so much, sir.
Lord Kosol, Lord Kosol, sir!
Something happened!
I honestly don’t know
who else I can turn to.
If people outside can’t help you,
how can someone in prison like me?
Please, hear me out first.
The Count just snuck into
the Singhapiman Palace,
begging the King for your pardon.
But suddenly, a gunshot rang out,
and the Count fell
into the palace grounds.
What did you say?
Worradech was shot?
Yes, sir.
I don’t know if he’s alive or dead.
I tried to go after him,
but the guards threw me out.
Here’s how you deal with soldiers,
the second vertebra of the neck.
Fix your aim on it.
Then strike down with force.
He’ll be out cold in no time.
And how hard do I strike
to knock him out in one blow?
As much force as you can muster,
that’s how hard you strike.
Back again?
Looking for another beating, huh?
No, sir. I came to report something.
What happened?
Hey, what the hell is that?
What are you looking for?
I’m searching for Count Worradech.
My desire,
how far have you gone with it?
You keep nagging me.
I already know your deepest wish,
to make Banjong
fall in love with you, right?
Give it time, uncle.
When it comes to men,
I’m a pro.
It’s just right now
I’m caught up dealing with Kosol.
No.
My desire,
it’s not only about Banjong.
It’s about Kosol too.
Oh my god.
Wait,
don’t tell me you want me to…
Two-timing, huh?
Would people in this era
even accept that?
A wife with two husbands?
This isn’t about love.
I didn’t die because of love.
If it wasn’t love,
then tell me what you want me to do.
Stop with the riddles.
I’m tired of guessing.
You already know this.
Because my desire
is the same as yours.
My desire is your desire.
My Lord, you’re alive.
My Lord!
Jade.
Your Majesty.
May I ask, like a heroine
who just woke from a coma,
where am I?
And how did I end up here?
This is the Singhapiman Palace.
You climbed over here yourself, didn’t you?
The guards said you were shot,
but only grazed on the arm.
So I had the royal physician treat you.
It is Your Majesty’s boundless grace.
No need for formality, you’re still hurt.
At that moment,
I couldn’t remember a thing.
I suddenly blacked out.
You must’ve hit your head when you fell.
That’s why you lost consciousness.
Who hates you so much
they’d want you dead?
This is the second
assassination attempt, isn’t it?
Seems you and I share
the same enemies.
That’s true, Your Majesty.
But let’s put that aside for now.
The reason I climbed into the palace tonight
was to deliver something important.
Lord Kosol is not the one
trying to assassinate you.
Please cancel the trial by fire.
I already know that.
Kosol would never wish me harm.
In fact, he’s been nothing but loyal.
Then why…
why would you still send him
to the trial by fire?
That’s like sending him
to die for nothing.
Because of Lord Singhanakhon,
your father.
He kept pestering me, insisting
Kosol tried to kill me.
While he himself plotted
with King Saenyakorn.
I didn’t know what else to do,
so I sent Kosol into the trial first,
planning to find a way
to save him later.
So that means…
you already have a way
to save him, right?
What’s the plan, Your Majesty?
I haven’t figured it out yet.
Help me think of one.
Wait, you can do that?
Hurry, Count.
I’m giving you only
the time it takes to boil an egg.
Then make it an ostrich egg, darling,
so I get more time.
Kosol.
Was Worradech shot?
No one knows if he’s alive or dead.
Kosol, are you all right?
They didn’t torture you,
force you to confess anything, did they?
Worry about yourself first.
Weren’t you the one ambushed?
How bad is it?
It’s nothing serious,
just a graze.
Lucky King Chaiyached found me.
so he had the royal physician treat me.
Hmm, fine then.
So why are you here?
Don’t you know
you’re disturbing my training?
Hey, I came out of concern.
Why must you speak so coldly?
The reason I came,
Come here.
Kosol.
What?
Come closer.
Just say it already.
I don’t like secrets.
This can’t be said out loud.
It has to be whispered.
Quickly.
King Chaiyached
knows you’re not the one
who tried to kill him.
But he must hold the trial by fire
to keep the nobles fooled.
He’ll find a way to save you later.
For heaven’s sake,
I thought it was serious.
Go back and tell him,
there’s no need to trouble himself
finding a way.
I’m ready to face the ritual.
Whether it’s fire or water.
I’m always ready.
Hey.
Don’t get cocky, Kosol.
The reason I came today
is to break you out of prison.
I won’t go.
I choose to stay here.
Ugh!
What kind of man
actually likes staying in jail?
Or do you already have
a plan of your own?
No plan.
Tch.
Hey, Mister Electricity Authority,
you sure love killing the vibe.
Brother Banjong.
Any word on Worradech?
I shot him.
When he was on the palace wall.
He fell into the palace grounds.
By now, he’s probably dead.
Let him be dead for real,
so we can finally rest easy.
And when you spoke with Kosol,
what did you find out?
The day of the trial by fire
will be our day of victory.
A grand move indeed.
I’ll tell you the plan later.
For now, we need to move
into Kosol’s house.
Because the Count already knows
I’ve sided with Kosol.
Hurry and pack only the essentials.
Go.
I’ve finished packing.
Take only what’s necessary.
Once we reach Kosol’s house,
we’ll regroup.
I still doubt Worradech’s fate.
I have a feeling he’s not dead yet.
I shot him with my own hand.
Are you saying I missed?
That’s not it.
And this isn’t the time
to argue over it.
I heard news,
the Count’s men are heading
to our house.
We need to go, now.
Go!
Lord Banjong, open the door now!
If you don’t, I’ll break it down.
Kosol,
tell me your plan straight.
I don’t believe
you’d just surrender and burn
without a scheme.
My plan is to slaughter a cow,
skewer it, and roast it in my place.
Then I’ll hand it out
to the villagers to feast on.
Oh, come on,
that’s not funny.
Be serious.
Haven’t things always gone well before?
Or if you’ve forgotten,
shall I refresh your memory
through these bars?
Don’t think you can just
force yourself on anyone.
You do it to me,
I’ll do it right back to you.
Eye for an eye.
Tooth for a tooth.
Hey!
What are you two doing?
Give me a little more time.
Go boil ten more eggs
if you have to.
I’ll pay you in full.
That’s impossible, sir.
The Lord is already on his way here.
Lord Kosol.
Stand and pay your respects
to the Count right now.
Lord Kosol, did you hear my command?
Forget it.
He’s already as good as dead.
Let him do whatever he wants.
Kosol,
I’ve captured Banjong and his men already.
If you don’t want your friends to die,
you better tell me
what you were planning
while gathering your forces.
If you’ve already caught them,
then ask them.
Why bother asking me?
You’re supposed to be a grown man.
Lying doesn’t suit you.
I know,
Banjong and his men escaped
before you even got to their house.
Don’t play games with me.
No food or water for him
starting today,
until the trial by fire.
Darling.
Kosol,
Kosol.
Even if you act cold
and pretend you don’t care,
I still can’t help worrying about you.
So I’ll ask you one last time,
will you run away with me?
Fine.
If you won’t leave,
then I’ll stay here with you.
Hey, hey, wait.
What are you doing?
Come here.
Ow, ow, easy, darling!
Ow!
Please, go ahead.
Next time, be gentle with me, darling.
- No rush, no pressure.
- Hey!
Worradech,
how did they manage to lock you up?
What happened?
If I tell you,
don’t get jealous.
I just…
stole a couple kisses
from the guard’s cheek.
So they threw me in here with you.
Ugh, what a mess.
Turns out,
loving the same sex
is as serious as treason here.
It’s done, Your Majesty.
If there’s nothing else,
I’ll take my leave
and report to the Count.
You’ve been gone so long,
I was really worried.
Jade.
Yes, sir.
I’ve watched you many times.
You’re loyal, devoted,
and love with your whole heart.
Enough to even die for it.
I’ll take you in
as one of my royal pages.
Uh,
I’m just a fool, Your Majesty.
I can’t even read.
If I serve by your side,
I’d only become a burden.
You’re already surrounded
by so many able men.
I’m not worthy, Your Majesty.
It’s those around me
that I fear the most.
The reason I came to Singhanakhon
is because in the Grand Palace
someone plotted against me.
I had to flee, pretending
I came to visit my brother.
See, even the royal guards
who’ve followed me for years
cannot be trusted.
The river bend ahead,
that’s where the nobles
have hidden assassins, waiting.
Prepare yourself well.
Your Majesty.
Please, board the boat.
So we can continue the journey quickly.
I fear nightfall will catch us.
Ugh!
Wait here a moment.
I’ve got a stomachache.
Need to step into the market
for a quick errand.
Uh, please don’t, Your Majesty.
I’ll hang a cloth for cover.
Then Your Majesty may relieve yourself
in the royal chamber pot.
No way, I hate chamber pots.
Sitting on them chills me to the bone.
Don’t follow me.
I’ll be back in just a moment.
Thief! Thief!
Thief! He stole the cloth!
Stop! Stop right there, you thief!
From king to common thief,
can you imagine
how tragic my life has become?
Even here in Singhanakhon,
no one can be trusted.
These days,
I don’t sleep peacefully at night.
Wherever I walk,
I must watch my back.
Every meal I eat,
I first toss to the dogs to test.
Jade,
Be my personal page, Jade.
But I belong to Count Singhanakhon, sire.
Whatever your ransom may be,
I can pay it, don’t you worry.
I’ve served Count Worradech
for decades, faithfully.
I don’t want to…
- I don’t want,
- I am the King.
Everything in this land is mine.
Would Worradech really defy me?
If I can’t take you from him,
then so be it.
Why that look on your face?
You don’t want to be with me?
I wouldn’t dare disobey, sire.
Good.
Then from this moment on,
you will serve only me.
As you command, Your Majesty.
Your first duty,
rock my cradle.
Yes, sire.
Jade.
Harder.
Jade, harder.
Why that face again?
Can you manage?
Harder.
Careful, you’ll fall in the water!
How deep could it be?
I’m scared.
Oh, oh,
Jade.
Go fetch me the cicada.
Yes, sire.
Are you hungry?
Not at all.
Then what’s that growling
in your stomach?
Don’t tell me it’s thunder.
Stop distracting me, will you?
I’m hypnotizing myself.
Full. So full.
Stuffed. Ugh!
Serves you right.
You really think
prison life is fun, huh?
It’s because of you.
I even threw myself in here
to be with you.
Will you finally tell me your plan?
Why should you know?
Because I care about you.
I don’t want you to die.
If you’re planning
something reckless,
I need to stop you.
Even if I know I can’t stop you.
I’m glad,
that you worry about me.
But the reason I can’t share my plan
is because I worry about you too.
So,
that means…
your plan is really dangerous, isn’t it?
Tell me right now, Kosol!
The more I love you,
the less I can tell you.
Then stop loving me
and just tell me already!
I can’t stop,
my heart’s already yours.
Ugh, I just want to grab your hair
and kick you both legs at once.
Wait, wait!
What?
Don’t be stubborn.
I’m starving.
Hang in there a bit longer.
My Lord.
Jade.
How did you end up in there, sir?
What happened?
Forget that for now.
Do you have any food on you?
I haven’t eaten anything
since yesterday.
I brought some with me,
my Lord.
Knew you’d been gone
all night.
You must be starving.
Here, my Lord.
Perfect timing too.
Had to sneak it past
the guards.
Thanks, then I’ll
dig in first.
- Here.
- I’m not hungry.
Just shut up
and eat already.
Thanks.
So tell me...
How did you end up
locked in here, my Lord?
Did you break some rule?
I was trying to squeeze
a secret out of Kosol.
So I kissed
the guard’s cheek.
And he threw me
straight in here.
Did you get the secret?
Hmph.
Got nothing at all.
Then...
How long will you
be stuck in here, my Lord?
Probably a while.
I don’t even know myself.
Ouch.
What the hell are you doing
Go
Jade
What have you been up to
I won’t let my master suffer
Wherever my master goes, I go
Always ready to serve
Jade, where are you
Jade
Have you seen Jade anywhere
He left the palace at dawn
Said he was heading to
the prison to find Count Worradech
Still clinging to his old master, huh
Of course
Guess I’ll never mean
as much as Worradech
So, what about the plan
Same as I told you
The Fire Trial is in two days
Are all sides set and ready
Our allies have all replied, brother
And we’ve prepared everything we need
Good
Then all that’s left is waiting
Once the whistle blows
Everyone, follow the plan now
Ready?
Lord Banjong, surrender yourself now
Stay back
Why must Lord Banjong surrender?
We found Lord Kosol at your estate
You’re guilty of sheltering
a traitor of the Crown
And thus, treason yourself
If you want me,
then break down the door
Smash it open
Come in
- Come on
- Wait
Stop
If we clash with the law today
it could ruin
everything two days from now
I will surrender
Brother Banjong
- But our plan,
- Pandao
I can’t afford to fail this time
I leave it to you now
Unbolt the door
Open it
Put the chains on me
I’ll go willingly
Banjong
Worradech
Is that really you?
How did you end up here?
I should be the one asking.
How did you get here?
I was arrested
for hiding Lord Kosol.
But tell me,
are you alright?
I’m fine.
Why would you even ask that?
Worradech.
Tell Banjong about the ambush.
When I was climbing the palace wall,
some lunatic took a shot at me.
Lucky for me, his aim was off.
The bullet just grazed my arm.
I’m so damn glad, Worradech,
that you’re still alive.
Was it you who fired?
I told you once,
never lay a finger on Worradech.
And you dared defy me?
Do you have a death wish?
I had no choice.
Worradech could blow our plan.
But you saw it yourself.
He chose to be locked up with me.
That means he's on our side.
Hey.
What are you talking about?
Are you plotting something?
Banjong, tell me right now.
No.
There’s no plan.
Kosol just asked me
what I had for breakfast.
Oh, please.
I’ve been nothing but honest with you two.
And you’re still hiding things from me?
Fine.
Do whatever the hell you want.
I’m done with this.
Worradech,
Don’t.
If you say Worradech is with us,
then he deserves to know the plan.
The fewer people who know, the better.
I won’t risk dragging him
into danger with us.
Master.
You can rest your head on my lap.
Thanks, love.
Banjong.
What is it?
Lie down.
I want you to rest easy.
Don’t resist.
Hey.
Lie down.
Jade.
Stroke my hair for me.
Uh… I shouldn’t.
The head is sacred.
Come on.
When I can’t sleep, I like
someone stroking my hair.
Then… may I?
You really like me stroking
your hair like this, Banjong?
Not really.
So you like it or not?
Well… I kinda do.
Jade, spank me a little.
Yes, my lord.
Go to sleep, Banjong.
I’ll lull you myself.
Lullaby, lullaby
Peek-a-boo
Jade, give me a goodnight kiss
What do you want me to do, My Lord?
Kiss me and say sweet dreams
I don’t dare, My Lord
Come on now
Don’t you want me to dream well?
I do, My Lord
Then go on…
Sweet dreams, My Lord
Sweet dreams, darling
Banjong
Tomorrow’s fire trial
must go flawlessly
Ready the troops
in case of any emergency
Count
Right now, Lord Kosol, Lord Banjong, Jade
and Count Worradech
are all locked up together
What?
Worradech too?
Yes, My Lord
Good
I’ll throw them all into the fire trial
What a damn stroke of luck
Two fools handed to me on a silver platter
And the other two waltzed
into my cage themselves
Perfect
Tomorrow I’ll drag you all
into the fire ritual before the crowd
Now that’ll be a show worth watching
The one who must walk through fire
to prove himself
is me and me alone
Why drag the others into it?
Because you’re all in the same pack
plotting rebellion together
Did you think I wouldn’t know?
And you, Banjong
While you worked by my side,
you spied on me
Did you really think you could fool me?
If I were a fool
I wouldn’t be Lord of this city
If you want to punish me
then do it
But please
let Worradech and Jade go
They know nothing of this, I swear
Worradech…
you ungrateful bastard
You’re coming with me.
I’ve got a special punishment just for you.
Let Worradech go.
- Don’t
- Come out
- Don’t come closer
- Get out now
Let go, let go!
Let go, I’m not going.
Let go! Let go!
I’m not going.
I’ll stay here with my friends.
Open the door!
- I said open it!
- Worradech!
Ungrateful brat, I broke you out
and you want to run back and die?
Do I need to beat some sense into you?
Hah? Hah?
Father and son fighting?
Now that’s entertaining.
Ta-da!
Worradech, what are you doing?
I’ll use science to craft a miracle.
My beloved stans,
give Mama a minute.
I’ll be back on stage real soon.
Where are you going?
Then I’m heading back home.
I don’t even know how to get there yet.
Or which way to go.
Why’s it so damn hard being a trans girl?
Sexy Naughty Bitchy
(Count, you’re serving beauty)
Oops, grabbed my boob.
Jade, don’t mess with the Count.
- Cut.
- Why only his hand turned black?
And why right in front of my face?
Didn’t touch / Can you wipe first?
(just playful teasing)
Now he’s grabbing my hair.
Sleep well, Banjong.
Lullaby.
Lullaby
(Sweet dreams, Banjong)
All of you, sleep well too.
I want sweet dreams for you.
Lullaby.
Lullaby
(now it’s my turn to soothe)
That’s it.