[Fight for You]
Sometimes it's not about right or wrong.
Don't you have anyone you care about?
For them,
I'm willing to do anything.
[File 1: A relationship that starts with cohabitation]
What color do you want for the sofa?
I want black.
White.
White gets dirty easily.
Black hides the dirt.
In terms of physics,
black and white are not colors,
but chroma.
In other words,
white is the presence of all light,
while black is the absence of it.
It absorbs all the surrounding light,
which makes it appear black.
Just like coal — an excellent light absorber,
which is why it looks so black.
Also, why am I the one in charge of the bathroom?
Because I'm in charge of other areas.
That was your own decision.
Did you ever ask me?
What do you want then?
Since you both have no objection, forget about the sofa.
Let's go upstairs to see your rooms.
-I want this one.
I already stated that I wanted a room with sunlight.
I paid the deposit first.
I should choose first.
Are you doing this on purpose?
Who would be that childish?
The other room doesn't get sunlight. I don't like it.
Since you both like this room,
how about...
sharing a room?
The room is big enough, and it's a double bed.
Sharing a room
might even help you get along better.
Hengsi, what are you doing?
What took you so long?
It's just renting a place, not buying a house.
Or are you giving them a hard time?
They were arguing about the sofa's color just now,
and now they're fighting over the room.
I just suggested they could share a room
to improve their relationship.
They're a couple?
Who's a couple with him?
Why are you two so in sync then?
It's okay.
If you share a room,
I can give you a discount.
I'll give you three minutes to think about it.
No need to force yourselves if you don't like it.
Time should be spent on love,
not arguing.
By the way,
if you decide to rent,
don't touch anything here.
Bai Zhouqi, what are you doing?
Have you forgotten why you came here?
Where are you going?
I'll let you have this room. I'll find another one.
Don't waste time.
Finding another one is such a hassle.
Take that room.
Come. Look.
This room is perfect for me.
Didn't you say you don't like rooms without sunlight?
It suddenly occurred to me I'm afraid of getting tanned.
Besides, first come, first served, right?
You can have that room.
I'm okay with cleaning the bathroom too.
Fate brought us together.
Since we'll live in the same place,
we should get along.
Right?
Besides, the environment here is peaceful,
the rent is cheap,
and the space is nice.
Why should we give it up to someone else?
It's better to make friends than enemies.
Why don't we rent it together
and negotiate a lower price with the landlord?
Okay.
Hello, my name is Bai Zhouqi.
You can just call me Bai.
What a coincidence.
I'm Hei, Hei Yubo.
Hei?
Nice to meet you.
You're going out so early?
To work.
Work?
By the way, what do you do?
I work for someone.
Where do you work?
Aren't you going to school?
I don't have class today.
Oh.
Wait.
This is for you. My treat.
I don't owe others favors.
And... I'm allergic to milk.
Jump.
You go... left. Left.
Yeah.
Press A?
A. Yes.
Wait.
One, two, three.
[Answer] [Refuse]
[Grandma]
Hello, Grandma.
Have you forgotten me since you moved out?
You haven't even given me a phone call.
No.
There's just been too much going on with the move.
Too much to do, or too annoying?
What do you mean?
You moved out to live with your girlfriend.
You're so busy, yet you still need to take care of her.
Isn't that annoying?
Grandma,
I never said you couldn't come.
It's messy here right now.
It's not that she doesn't want to see you.
You've watched too many dramas.
[Hei Shilin] [Hei Yubo] [Girlfriend]
Very filial.
But he used living with his girlfriend
as an excuse to move out.
[Hei Yubo] [Hei Jiali] [Sister]
[Hei Yubo] [Hei Jiali] [Sister] [Hei Shilin]
Is it necessary for him to move out
to save up for medical expenses?
[Answer] [Refuse]
[Jiali]
Pretty girl, how's your health?
[Mic on/off][Camera on/off]
Brother, the new medicine makes me uncomfortable.
Can I switch back to the old medicine?
Be good. The doctor said the new medicine works better.
You'll get used to it.
[Mic on/off][Camera on/off]
But I heard this medicine is very expensive.
It's not that expensive.
By the way,
I told Grandma
you went abroad for a training camp.
She scolded me for ages.
Come back soon, okay?
[Mic on/off][Camera on/off]
I don't want to get caught.
Right.
[Mic on/off][Camera on/off]
Your favorite claw machine just got a new set of prizes.
This time, I got one for just 120 NT dollars.
I'll bring it to you next time.
Okay.
[Mic on/off][Camera on/off]
[Braised Food]
Okay.
Here, enjoy. Your drinks will be ready soon.
Mr. Dou?
[Braised Food]
Long time no see.
I thought you were dead.
Or were you imprisoned?
Ms. Hei, you missed me, right?
Why would I miss you?
I'm right here. You can look all you want.
Who wants to look? What do you want to eat?
The same as usual.
Okay.
Wait.
Madam.
I want the same.
The same? What do you mean?
The... The same as that.
It's a limited edition. You can't afford it.
Here. Order here.
Order whatever you want. They're all delicious.
I want this.
Okay.
Go find a seat. Suit yourself.
Wait a minute.
Health insurance doesn't cover it?
Huh?
Valve repair without sternotomy?
May I ask how much the valve replacement costs?
Self-pay?
No problem.
Okay, thank you.
Mr. Dou.
Ms. Hei, can I borrow someone to help carry some goods?
Get lost.
[Dou Keyi Convenience House]
Have a seat.
Does your grandma know about this?
I don't want her to worry.
My sister doesn't want her to know either.
How much?
I asked how much.
After deducting what health insurance covers,
I still need about 400,000 NT dollars.
Stop playing.
Go take care of it.
Us?
Should I go?
Okay.
This is for Jiali.
Temper isn't meant for moments like this.
[Dou Keyi Convenience House]
Don't think I don't know
you've been working as a sparring partner.
How much can you really make
by enduring physical pain?
Don't force me to tell your grandma.
I don't owe others favors.
I'm one of the others?
Then treat this money as an advance on my salary.
Please let me work here
until I pay it back.
Do you even know where this is?
I won't ask or interfere.
Whatever work you and Di give me,
I'll do it.
Aren't you short-handed?
If your grandma knows, she'll skin me alive.
It'll be fine if she doesn't know.
If you don't agree,
I can't accept the money.
You're as stubborn as Ms. Hei.
I'm sorry.
I didn't see you.
Aren't you going to eat the breakfast I made?
I'm not in the habit of having breakfast.
But you need breakfast to have energy for the day.
Come.
Come here.
Have a seat.
Here.
Eat more.
Juice. Have some juice.
What's the rush?
You're acting like a child.
What? You don't want to leave now?
For food and necessities,
I'll give you the money at the end of the month.
Why split hairs?
We live together.
Thank you. I'm going to be late.
It's easy to handle him.
These two bouquets. These two.
-Both?
-Yes.
This one too.
What a pity.
So handsome.
Can I ask you for a leaflet?
Sure.
Thank you.
Can I have your Line ID?
Line ID?
[Answer] [Refuse]
[Personal number]
Excuse me.
Hello?
Dou Keyi Convenience House?
Yes.
Please come quickly and help me
look for my Grass.
Your grass?
Hurry up.
I'll send you my location. Come quickly.
Okay, wait for me there.
Grass!
Grass! Grass!
Hello, I'm from Dou Keyi Convenience House.
Hurry up and help me!
What grass is inside?
My cat.
A cat?
Yes.
Okay, I'll go in and take a look.
Grass?
Your Grass.
Grass.
Grass, I'm glad you're fine.
Why did you run around?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What's wrong?
A cockroach!
You're a big guy and you're afraid of cockroaches?
Where is it?
Over there.
Has it left?
Not yet.
What about now?
Has it left?
It hurts.
Be gentle.
Don't laugh. Everyone's afraid of something.
A cockroach!
You're afraid of cockroaches, but you got into a fight.
I didn't fight. I went to work.
Give me your hand.
What kind of job
gets you hurt like this?
Today, in order to save a cat,
I fell off a wall.
A cat?
Yes.
A pet shop?
A convenience house.
A convenience house?
Is it the same as a convenience store?
Anything.
What?
As long as a client requests it,
we take on any task.
Any task?
Even illegal ones?
What?
I'm just kidding.
What kind of tasks do you usually take on?
Walking a dog.
Buying flowers with an elderly lady.
Wearing a mascot costume to hand out leaflets.
Looking for a cat.
Today... just those four.
If I need something in the future, can I hire you guys?
Yes.
[Investigation Report on Hei Yubo]
You're going out so early?
To work.
Where do you work?
No prohibited items found.
[Hei. Hei Yubo's nickname is Hei. He's a new member of Dou Keyi Convenience House.]
Excluding grocery shopping and dog walking
as potential behavioral patterns.
Regarding the disguise as a large mascot,
although there was contact with multiple individuals there,
[Person in charge: Bai Zhouqi] [Investigation location: Dou Keyi Convenience House]
no further suspicious interactions were observed.
At 2:30 p.m.,
Hei Yubo snuck into a house
and handed over a tightly wrapped package
to a woman.
The distance was
too great to ascertain their conversation.
[Investigation Report on Hei Yubo]
[Responsible Unit: Training Department of Intelligence Bureau]
[Subject of Investigation: Hei Yubo]
[Investigation Report on Hei Yubo]
Was it really just a cat?
How can I get closer to him?
From now on,
you should follow the chief's guidance.
Yes, sir!
Call me No Sir.
Hei Yubo is inexperienced.
Is there a way
to make him one of us?
Where is she?
Who?
The woman who wouldn't let me come.
Where is she?
So?
I'm pretty useful.
Why don't you consider making me your boyfriend?
Hmm?