[Fight for You]
People around me always say I have an overflow of sympathy,
but I just feel
behind every situation, there's a reason for it.
Isn't that right?
[File 2: Become one of yours]
My family, just like my surname,
cannot tolerate any stains.
But there are times
when you have to accept things.
Such as me,
Bai Zhouqi.
If your surveillance target
and a colleague from the Intelligence Bureau both fall into the sea,
who would you save?
Is the other party elderly, weak, or a child?
Can the other party swim?
Is the other party injured?
Bai Zhouqi!
There are only two kinds of people in this world.
One is the righteous side like us,
and the other is the enemy side.
Yes!
If you encounter a situation during a mission,
how would you solve it?
Can right and wrong
be judged without even understanding
the situation first?
Bu Xing.
Yes.
Bai Zhouqi has always been
too soft-hearted and indecisive
since childhood.
Help him get back on the right path.
Advisor, you're being modest.
Zhouqi is your grandson.
He must be outstanding.
He inherited neither my traits
nor half —
no,
not even a third — of his brother's caliber.
Discipline him strictly.
Don't worry about my feelings.
Yes.
From now on,
you should follow the chief's guidance.
Remember,
your actions
represent the Bai family.
Yes.
I won't disappoint Grandpa
or Chief.
Bai Zhouqi.
When I came here from Hong Kong,
it was your grandfather who trained me.
I didn't even dare to breathe loudly in front of him.
But you don't need to be like that in front of me.
Relax.
However, I will still speak my mind.
Understand?
Yes, sir!
Call me No Sir.
No Sir.
[Leader] [Dou Keyi Convenience House]
Come here.
Oh.
[Dou Keyi, the leader]
Dou Keyi?
It's said that as long as you pay,
the owner of Dou Keyi Convenience House
can solve any problem for you.
Any problem?
It's actually crying up wine and selling vinegar.
On the surface, he's a good neighbor,
walking dogs and looking for cats.
But behind the scenes,
he's involved in smuggling, murder, and serving as a middleman.
He plays both sides.
[Smuggling origins: Thailand, Myanmar] [Contact person: Xiong]
I've been unable to find concrete criminal evidence against him.
Those who got caught all have the same story.
Even the informants we sent couldn't gather any solid proof.
It's as if nothing is connected to him at all.
[Dou Keyi Convenience House]
Do you know what that means?
It means he might be innocent.
It means
Dou Keyi is far more meticulous and subtle
than we thought.
Understand?
Mm.
Someone who seems harmless on the surface
but is secretly using others for his gain
must not be spared.
We must bring him to justice.
Arrest him!
That's your surveillance target.
[Hei Yubo
Nickname: Hei
Fitness coach]
Hei Yubo.
His nickname is Hei.
He's a new member of Dou Keyi Convenience House.
He's treated like a younger brother by Dou Keyi.
He looks like a small fry.
He's about your age.
Get close to him first,
gather information,
and then we'll take them all down
at one stroke.
Mm!
All tasks are of the same importance.
It's all about how much effort we put in.
Understand?
Yes, sir!
No Sir!
Go.
Advisor Bai's precious grandson,
just collect information.
If anything happens to you,
I can't afford to take the blame.
I've been following him for a week.
Looks like Hei's tasks
are really...
ordinary.
Will these reports help No Sir?
At this rate,
when can I find solid evidence
of Dou Keyi's crimes?
And
if the distance is not close enough,
I can't even catch a single word
of their conversation.
How can I get closer to him?
No, no.
Don't misunderstand.
This is so embarrassing!
Does he think I...
Yeah, I'll double-check for you next week.
How have you been lately?
Not bad.
What about your sister?
The doctor has scheduled the surgery.
Let me know if you need anything.
Okay.
Mr. Dou,
actually, I've been wanting to tell you...
Hey.
Save me the nagging stuff.
Here.
What's wrong with your hand?
Nothing.
If Ms. Hei finds out,
we're both dead.
Don't worry.
I won't implicate you.
What I meant is
it's just a job,
so don't take it so seriously, okay?
Isn't being an elementary school PE teacher nice?
Rest assured.
Hei Yubo and Dou Keyi's relationship
is really special.
He must know something.
Be careful on the way.
Bye bye.
Who are you?
No.
-Come!
-I was just passing by.
Come here!
You were sneaking around. What are you up to?
I want to make a request for help.
Bai?
What are you doing here?
Hey.
You know him?
He's my roommate.
Hello.
I heard Dou Keyi Convenience House can help solve any problem.
You heard?
Where did you hear that?
There.
[Dou Keyi Convenience House]
Kid,
what's your request?
I want you to accept my interview.
-Interview?
Mm.
What are you doing?
What interview?
If I can't finish my interview,
I won't be able to graduate.
Then my grandpa will beat me to death.
Hey!
What do you want to interview us about?
The topic is
the pros and cons of multi-business operations
for community workers
and the importance
of ethical education and cultural influence.
Wait. I need to take this call.
Hello?
Di.
He's a postgraduate.
He's writing his thesis.
So you knew each other before?
We knew each other after renting the place.
Renting the place?
That was when you just joined the convenience house, right?
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
Hey.
What about your thesis interview?
Of course I'll do it.
I'll come to you next time.
See you.
Make a request?
He didn't even ask about the fee and just ran off.
I hope I'm just overthinking it.
Our business is very complicated.
Many people on both sides of the law want to take Mr. Dou down.
Stay sharp.
Spacing out?
Let's go.
No Sir.
The informant told me
you approached Shi Difen at the convenience house.
Do you know why
I called you back?
You must have your reason.
But I just don't quite understand.
Before you,
some of your seniors also lurked around.
But one by one, they got exposed.
They are more cunning than we thought.
I don't want you to walk the same path.
Understand?
Just focus on Hei.
Thank you for the warning, No Sir.
[Surveillance Report]
I think Hei Yubo is inexperienced.
[Unusual Behaviors or Events]
Is there a way to make him one of us?
One of us?
I'll do my best.
Okay.
[Answer] [Refuse]
[Personal number]
Hello?
Mr. Hei,
the boss is going abroad for a while.
Training sessions are on hold for now.
I'll let you know when he's back.
Okay. Got it.
What's that sound?
What is he doing inside?
What were you doing at the door?
I saw a cockroach.
I wanted to help you get rid of it.
Where?
[Answer] [Refuse]
[Grandma]
Recently,
has he been a little...
weird?
Here.
Open your mouth.
What kind of job
gets you hurt like this?
How can I get closer to him?
No, no.
Don't misunderstand.
If I can't finish my interview,
I won't be able to graduate.
Am I imagining this?
Why do I feel...
he is...
Grandma?
Why are you here?
I can't come?
That's not what I meant.
Why didn't you tell me before you came?
I called, but you didn't answer my call.
Where?
Where is what?
Grandma.
Where?
Where is what?
Where is she?
Who?
Grandma. Grandma.
The woman who wouldn't let me come.
Where is she?
No such thing.
No?
She didn't forbid me to come?
Or...
there is no such person?
If there is no such person,
I...
I wouldn't have needed to move out.
It's just...
It's just she's not here.
Not here?
Okay, I'll wait for her here.
Grandma.
No, she...
She...
She might come back very late.
How about this?
I'll take her to the braised food stall to see you.
Okay?
Come on.
Let's go.
Why are you so flustered?
I just want to see
what kind of woman my grandson likes.
Are you shy?
Grandma, go home and rest first.
I'll introduce her to you when I have time.
Don't be so flustered.
You'll scare her.
Why are you so nervous?
Isn't she almost one of us already?
Grandma, it's not that fast.
Then you need to try harder.
Make it faster.
No, Grandma.
Why aren't you opening the braised food stall today?
Go back to take care of your business.
Right.
Since I don't know how to make him one of us,
I'll just become one of them first.
Hello, Grandma.
I'm Hei's girlfriend,
Bai.
What are you doing?
Grandma, I'm sorry.
I told Hei not to tell you.
Because I was worried you wouldn't accept me.
What are you doing?
I'm being kind enough to help you out.
It's fine if you don't appreciate it,
but you pushed me away.
Help me out?
You're a man.
Do you have a better idea?
You're the one who lied.
I'm the only one in the house now.
Then just stay in your room.
You scared Grandma.
I'm sorry.
I scared Grandma because I'm a man.
Why don't you go to Dou Keyi Convenience House
to hire a girlfriend?
I forgot you're an employee of Dou Keyi Convenience House.
That way, Grandma would think we're...
That is wonderful.
If Grandma can't accept your boyfriend,
we'll just break up.
Wouldn't that be great?
Or...
you really have a girlfriend?
Then I should stay out of this.
Hey.
So...
you really have a girlfriend?
Or do you think I'm not good enough?
Then why won't you accept me?
Because I don't like lying.
What if...
it's a white lie?
What's wrong?
There is a cockroach.
Really?
Really.
Is it still there?
We can only get closer.
Has it left?
Yes.
It has left.
So?
I'm very useful.
Why don't you consider making me your boyfriend?
Are we going to keep pretending
to be a couple from now on?
Is it convenient for you?
Now, we are...
on the same team?
I think the way you are now
is great.
Why did you get hurt?
Although I'm not that capable,
as long as you need me,
I'm here.
Go exchange the tie for lace.
What are you doing here?
I'll call the police!