[Fight for You]
Right and wrong stand clear,
a chasm wide and sheer.
No doubts,
no gray areas.
The last thing one should do
is to betray justice
and go against its path.
[File 3: A two-faced life riddled with flaws]
You moved out
because of him?
I'm sad and disappointed.
You thought
I couldn't accept this,
so you moved out without a word?
Hei,
what kind of person do you think I am?
In your eyes,
I'm a stubborn old woman you can't reason with.
Is that it?
No.
I didn't want you to worry.
Go away.
Come.
Look, he's always like this.
He keeps everything to himself, carrying it all alone.
Did you ever ask me?
How did you know I wouldn't accept him?
He
is all height,
no brains.
Once, a scammer called, saying
something happened to his sister.
He cried so hard and he almost sold himself.
I was scared because I was ignorant.
I'm not stupid.
Bai, you look much smarter than him.
I'll leave my grandson
to you.
Since you are in love,
you two should get along well.
Your grandma is so open-minded?
How are we supposed to break up then?
Grandma,
we are both men.
Aren't you worried that others would think...
think we...
Hey.
What?
There's a cockroach.
What's there to be worried about?
You've met someone who you can show your weakness to.
I'm happy for you.
All right.
What's with this look?
It's okay.
Whether it's a man or a woman,
who you love is what matters most.
I'll always support you.
Bai, come.
Let's add each other on Line.
Come to the braised food stall
when you have time.
I'll cook something delicious for you.
Okay.
Grandma.
I'm sorry.
In order not to make you worry,
I lied to you.
All right, I'm leaving.
Go back.
Remember to bring him along.
Don't stand there.
Just go in.
I feel your grandma
is different from other people's grandma.
Since I was little, if she ever found out
I was bullied at school,
she'd go seek justice for me.
All my classmates knew they shouldn't mess with me.
She
loves you very much.
She loves me and my sister very much.
But she's scary when she gets angry.
Then how dare you lie to her
about living with your girlfriend?
It's my job.
I come home with injuries every time.
In order not to worry her,
I moved out.
Isn't the work at the convenience house
about helping people solve problems?
Why would you get hurt?
I don't just work at the convenience house.
I have another job.
You seem to be very interested in the convenience house.
I'm just concerned about you.
Forget it if you don't want to tell me.
Anyway, I'm sorry that I got you involved.
If your grandma really takes you back,
who should I keep an eye on?
Oh, right.
Well,
since Grandma didn't object to us,
should we continue
to pretend to be a couple?
Are you okay with that?
What do you mean?
Well...
do you have someone else to report to?
Or is there someone else who would care?
Don't worry. I'm single.
Helping you is no problem.
Okay.
So...
we are on the same team now?
For now.
We're on the same team.
We're on the same team, right?
Let me help you.
Let me ask you.
Are you...
Very nice to you.
Right?
I'm very nice to you.
I'm very nice to you. I'm very nice to you.
Hey.
Actually, I envy your relationship with Grandma.
My brother and I were raised by our grandpa.
His word is law.
But I've never met his expectations.
The gap between us
is this big.
No.
It should be this big.
I think the way you are now is just fine.
[Investigation Report on Hei Yubo]
Why did I tell him
so much about myself?
I think the way you are now is just fine.
That was the first time someone told me
I don't have to try harder to be someone else.
The way I am
is just fine.
Bai Zhouqi!
There must be something wrong with the surveillance target.
There are only two kinds of people in this world.
The righteous side like us
and the enemy side.
Bai Zhouqi.
Don't forget your mission at the Intelligence Bureau.
Your purpose
is to get information from him
and catch the bad guys.
Good morning.
Morning.
Yes.
I won.
[Refuse] [Answer]
[Shi Difen]
Hello?
Screwdriver No. 3.
What's wrong?
Sorry.
I thought it was my phone ringing.
I picked up by mistake.
Who was it?
I didn't see it.
It was not your girlfriend anyway.
Because the real one is here.
Right?
Did he say anything?
Screwdriver No. 3.
But he hung up after he said that.
Did a regular customer ask you to buy something?
Yes.
The client asked me to buy some tools
and deliver them later.
[Dou Keyi Convenience House]
What are you doing here?
You're spying on Dou Keyi?
Who would be that bored?
I was looking at a bunch of ants over there.
What's so interesting about ants?
They were carrying a bunch of big cockroaches.
I'm here for my thesis.
Thesis?
You came all the way here for your thesis?
You have no idea how exhausting writing a thesis is.
I was hungry,
so I thought of Grandma's braised food stall.
Grandma asked you to take me there.
Why haven't you taken me there?
I...
Just so happens.
Look.
[Come. I'll cook something delicious for you.]
[Grandma, I'm Bai. I'm hungry.]
Grandma said she'll cook something delicious
for me.
Do you want to go with me?
Come on. Let's go.
I don't know where the braised food stall is.
Let's go.
Lead the way.
Which way?
That way?
[Braised Food]
They look delicious.
Grandma, these look delicious.
Eat as much as you can.
Okay.
What do you want?
Order as much as you can.
I want mini sausages.
One portion of tofu skin.
I'll give you a little more.
Okay.
Grandma.
Here.
Business is really good.
When business is good,
I worry Grandma might get too tired.
When business is slow,
I worry she can't make enough money.
Eat.
Grandma is watching.
What was your major?
Physical education.
Physical education?
Why did you choose your current job
instead of being a teacher
or a fitness coach or something?
I did.
I was a PE teacher.
But something happened to my family later.
I need to make more money.
So you can make a lot of money
at Dou Keyi Convenience House?
I just want to know how much you need.
I can lend it to you.
No need.
Talking about money with friends can ruin the friendships.
Friends?
Yes.
We're friends.
And I'm your boyfriend.
Your grandma's braised food is really delicious.
Yes, listen,
the pig's trotters she makes are absolutely amazing.
But I like kelp sprouts.
Kelp sprouts are delicious, right?
I haven't been so relaxed for a long time.
I don't think you've been that busy.
You don't understand.
Being forced to do something you're not good at
is really painful.
So...
being a postgraduate is not what you want?
This is life.
Not everyone is like your grandma.
Grandma
always told us
life is short.
So,
just don't have regrets.
What about your sister?
Grandma said you sent her abroad.
Why put so much pressure on yourself?
Didn't you want to watch the game?
Let's go.
Hurry!
So why did you send your sister abroad?
I'm sorry.
Hei.
Take off your clothes.
What do you want to do?
To do the laundry.
Hey, what are you doing?
You really know how to get hurt.
Why do you have such a huge bruise on your waist again?
It looks like a fresh one.
Did Screwdriver No. 3 hit you?
Perhaps I accidentally bumped into something
when I was moving goods.
It doesn't hurt.
No wonder you're worried Grandma would worry.
It's easy to get bruised while doing sports or moving goods.
It's okay.
Come on. Let's play another round.
With you being so careless,
why do you still do this job?
For your sister.
Looks like
Dou Keyi lent him money.
He owes him a favor.
With his straightforward personality,
he'll definitely do his best.
Although I'm not that capable,
as long as you need me,
I'm here.
Hey.
[Dou Keyi Convenience House]
Do you want some water?
No?
Let's go.
Morning, Di.
Hey.
I know Mr. Dou has always been protective of you,
but
there are things that still need to be done.
Di, give orders anytime.
I won't let Mr. Dou know.
Wait a minute.
Go swap the tie bear for a lace bear.
Be careful.
The lace bear must not get dirty.
Come back as soon as you get it.
The client will check it personally.
Be careful.
Come on. Let's go.
[My love for you is endless]
[Wrench No. 11]
Handsome guy, are you waiting for someone?
I'm not waiting for a person.
Are you waiting for me?
Or anyone will do?
You're so boring.
Lower your head.
Otherwise, how am I supposed to tell you the password?
My love for you is endless.
Where is it?
What's the rush?
Bai?
Why are you here?
You're bleeding a lot.
Blood?
I think Hei Yubo is different from the others
of Dou Keyi Convenience House.
You think?
That day, you said our relationship
started to be different.
How?
Although we're not a real couple,
we live together and shared weal and woe.
Isn't that different?
Just friends?
Because you said
you are my boyfriend.
That's why you're so nice to me.