[Fight for You]
At Dou Keyi Convenience House,
we can take care of anything for you.
Anything.
[File 4: Their Relationship Begins to Change]
There may be evidence...
of illegal transactions inside that bear.
But how can I get it?
Is that his contact person?
Wait a sec.
Why does she look so much like that girl who was looking for her cat?
[Are you talking about me?]
Why is she standing so close to him?
I'm calling the police!
How dare you rob him
in broad daylight?
Why are you here?
Are you okay?
I just happened to be passing by...
Doing street interviews for my thesis.
Your job is so dangerous.
Is this bear covered in diamonds or something?
He was holding a knife.
Why did you rush over here?
That's nothing. Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you hurt?
You're bleeding a lot!
Blood!
It's okay.
The wound shouldn't be deep.
But you,
protecting this bear like that.
Should we drop it off somewhere first?
I'm taking you to the hospital first!
No need!
I'm allergic to hospital disinfectants. I'd faint.
I'll see what's hidden inside this bear
that made you protect it like that.
How can you still be smiling? You nearly scared me to death.
Calm down, calm down.
Just treat me to something delicious tonight.
My colleagues will likely come to pick it up later.
Let's go.
Where to?
Bathroom.
I'll go with you.
No need. I can go by myself.
Wait for me there.
Are you mad at me?
I saw someone rushing toward you.
I just wanted to block him.
How could I have known he'd pull out a knife?
And you still rushed out despite the knife.
So now are you blaming me?
Who would be foolish enough to only care about that bear?
It wasn't foolishness. It's work.
Work means you have to get the job done at all costs.
Better to sacrifice your life for work, right?
You let yourself be a punching bag,
kicked and beaten.
You might be able to endure it,
but I can't stand watching this.
Why can't you stand it?
Because friends help each other in times of need.
Are we just friends?
Not just friends.
Because you said...
you are my boyfriend.
That's why you're so good to me.
What are you doing?
Rehearsing in advance for Grandma
so we won't slip up.
Who would practice
this kind of thing for their elders?
Hei Yubo,
are you drunk on rubbing alcohol or something?
You can't drink cold drinks.
I'll make you some fish soup.
It helps wounds heal faster.
Did you finish this bottle?
Just a soda.
I can handle a soda.
This is beer.
Do you not drink alcohol?
Teachers don't have freedom,
so I chose to become a sparring partner.
A sparring partner is the kind of job...
where you get hit but can't hit back.
So...
don't worry about me.
I'm tough.
Thank you.
Thank you for standing in front of me.
Get up first.
Trading your body for money
and boasting about being tough?
I'll get you a towel.
Where are you going?
You got hurt for me.
You bled for me.
I have to take care of you.
Just one bottle of beer, and you're drunk like this.
No wonder you say you can't drink.
I'll make you some sea bass soup.
It helps the...
wounds heal faster!
Be careful.
Watch your step.
Sea bass soup!
It'll help you heal faster!
Watch your step.
No, go to your room and rest.
Sea bass soup!
Good thing we didn't get tricked
by those two teddy bears.
There was really nothing inside that tie-wearing bear?
We even had it tested.
It's just polyester fiber and glass beads.
So we should focus on that lace-dressed bear.
Anyway,
try to find a way to trick
Hei Yubo into telling you what's inside that bear
and how the transaction works.
I don't think Hei Yubo knows anything.
That's why he got played.
Don't make assumptions! Verify it!
Bai?
Bai Zhouqi.
Yes!
Let me ask you:
Did you get hurt when you followed him today?
No, no.
No Sir,
I'll report back if anything comes up.
Did you see a cockroach again,
or are you drunk and fell?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Did our floor do something to you?
I still can't figure out
what could be inside that bear
that would make someone try to rob it with a knife.
You delivered it back just now.
The people at the convenience house saw you being beaten up like this
with blood stains...
They didn't say anything?
Got hurt?
I'm fine.
Someone tried to rob the goods,
but the bear is safe.
It's intact.
Good job.
Go back now.
Don't let Mr. Dou see you.
Thank you.
This is for you.
I'm sorry you got hurt because of me.
What's the point of giving me money?
Before your convenience house assigns you tasks,
don't they tell you if they might be dangerous?
It was just a delivery.
You trust them that much?
You didn't even ask about the contents before accepting the task.
When you mail something at a convenience store,
the staff won't ask you what it is either, right?
What if... there's something shady in the package,
and you end up getting arrested?
You're overthinking.
Dou Keyi Convenience House
is not as simple as it seems...
right?
The convenience house handles all kinds of requests.
Many different kinds.
Any more, and it'll break.
If you don't want to tell me, I won't push you.
But there are so many other job options out there.
Why the convenience house?
If, as you say,
the tasks are that simple,
how could you earn so much money from it?
More than being a sparring partner?
Even I was scared to see you hurt.
Imagine how worried Grandma would be if she found out.
Actually, I don't have a choice.
My little sister has had a heart condition since she was a kid.
She's always getting hospitalized.
Being a regular sparring partner could tide me through at first.
But now, she needs a heart valve replacement.
The cost is too high.
I didn't dare to tell Grandma,
so...
I lied and said my sister went abroad.
Doesn't she have health insurance?
Her condition isn't covered by it.
The artificial valve is self-paid.
Mr. Dou was kind enough to help me.
I know the risks of the convenience house.
But Mr. Dou wouldn't harm me.
And, more importantly, it's to save my sister.
Just doing some physical labor.
Don't you trust people too easily?
One day, if you
found out the real reason I approached you...
would you be angry
and ignore me,
or beat me up?
No Sir.
Didn't you say that you were fine?
I'm fine.
I just accidentally fell while tailing him.
I'm okay. Look.
Protect yourself.
In our line of work,
not being calm enough is a fatal mistake.
About what's inside that bear...
Hei Yubo doesn't know what's inside!
I'm warning you again!
Be skeptical of everything.
How can you be sure that he knows nothing?
Since childhood, our Bai Zhouqi has always been
easily influenced and indecisive,
and his convictions have never been firm enough.
Help me straighten him out.
Yes, sir.
According to the internal report,
there's a ring inside the lace-dressed bear.
Pure gold, weighing 2.74 grams.
The market price is less than 	$8,000.
It's just a ring?
Then why all the fuss?
It's a token of love
from a mistress to a mob boss.
Why make such a big deal out of it,
even going so far as to send people to steal it?
Based on what I know about Dou Keyi...
this deal...
might be just a test.
Test?
Didn't you run into Dou Keyi at the convenience store?
Yeah, but I don't think he saw me.
Are you sure?
Dou Keyi is sly.
He was testing whether you were sent by me.
Now... he's telling me through this message...
that he already knows you're mine.
What should we do now?
If the enemy doesn't make a move, neither will we.
Since they're suspicious...
you need to be extra careful.
Yes, sir.
Has Hei Yubo been up to anything lately?
No Sir,
I feel that Hei Yubo
is different from those people
at the Dou Keyi Convenience House.
You feel?
He... seems to trust you quite a bit, right?
Find a chance
to go on a task with him.
Me?
Join him on a task?
Since you said his tasks are so simple,
then asking to
experience one together
wouldn't be too much, right?
What if he refuses?
Doesn't that mean he's just like those people?
What? Is there a problem?
Bai.
Those who know are as guilty as those who commit the crime.
Don't be soft-hearted.
Where's Dou Keyi?
I asked him to watch the store for me...
No Sir?
He ran away before he finished the pot!
Gosh!
Why did you come here?
What else could I do?
You've been avoiding me these days,
so I had to come chase after you.
Not really.
I... I've been busy.
I thought
things between us
changed after that day.
Wanna breakfast?
Mm.
Sobered up and back to your gloomy face.
Looking at me is supposed to fill you up or what?
Well...
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Sorry for what part?
Grabbing me and not letting go?
Or jumping on me?
Or...
What?
You think you can just kiss people when you're drunk?
You kissed me, and now you're running away.
Didn't you say we should practice for Grandma?
When I get drunk, I get a bit...
confused about the situation.
I'm sorry.
Are you going to take responsibility?
So are you going to take responsibility or not?
I'm going to be late.
Say it...
say that our relationship has changed now.
Don't ignore me.
So now
who is ignoring whom?
Grandma,
he won't let me accompany him to work.
Isn't it good to have someone to work alongside you?
What's wrong with you?
Yeah. A couple should experience life together
to build better rapport for the future together.
That's right!
Madam.
Coming!
I'm leaving you two.
Come on, let's go home.
That day, you said our relationship
started to be different.
Different how?
Even though we're not really dating,
we live together,
we've kissed,
and we've gone through hardships together.
That changed our relationship, right?
Why are you backing away from me?
Why are you leaning in so close?
What do you want me to do?
What kind of task is it, really?
[Preview]
Seduction?
If there's a task, we'll do it together.
Look at that man.
From now on,
we're 100% on the same side.
The beginning is always the hardest.
The initial contact is crucial.
Which parts are real
and which parts are fake?
If this continues,
I might really fall for you.