[Fight for You]
We're all pretending.
No one can predict
when the pretense will become reality.
Don't be stubborn,
thinking you are definitely clear-headed
and fully aware.
[File 5: After All This Acting, What's Real and What's Fake?]
That day, you said our relationship
had started to change.
How?
Although we're not a real couple,
we live together,
we've kissed,
and we've gone through hardships together.
That changed our relationship, don't you think?
Why are you backing away from me?
Why are you leaning in so close?
What do you expect me to do?
The chicken feet are sold out today.
I'll give you some for free next time.
Okay, no problem.
Remember to remind me.
Okay.
Let's go home.
Alright.
As a man,
I won't hold you responsible for a kiss
and my injuries.
Grandma likes you so much.
When the time comes for us to tell her we're breaking up,
I'm sure she'll be very sad.
This is why I don't like lying.
Because you have to use more lies to cover it up.
Which part is real,
and which part is fake?
Once the convenience house matters are settled
and my sister's surgery goes smoothly,
everything will go back to normal, right?
Bai?
What's wrong?
Got a new mission?
Yes.
We told Grandma that
we'd experience life together, didn't we?
If there's a mission, let's do it together.
It'll be faster.
What kind of mission is it?
Manual labor?
Kind of.
But also... Kind of not.
Seduction?
Stop laughing.
Can you do it?
I really can't.
I understand.
You got all flustered after kissing me once,
let alone seduction.
Bai Zhouqi.
Don't be sarcastic.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
You take care of the physical part,
and I take care of the soul.
Don't think too much.
It must be because you're handsome
that you got selected for this mission.
Will the convenience house reimburse you if you buy clothes?
Is the size okay?
Yes.
Let me adjust it for you.
Is it too tight?
Pardon me.
Also,
during the date,
remember not to take her on your motorcycle.
Your mission target likes working out?
That's almost like having home-court advantage, isn't it?
Check out that guy.
He's so handsome and charming.
Attracting so much attention.
Guess you don't need my teaching.
What was that? I didn't hear you.
[Taste on the Tip of the Tongue]
Here are your dishes.
-Here.
-Thank you.
Sorry that
I can only afford to treat you to these.
It's okay.
All food is just calories anyway.
Here.
Thank you.
You're actually very considerate.
Maybe I'm just used to taking care of my little sister since childhood.
How old is your sister?
She's in high school.
But she's been on leave for six months.
When she was born,
our father died due to an accident.
Two years later, our mother passed
from a heart attack, too.
Later, when she was diagnosed
with heart problems,
she kept asking
if she would become an angel
like our mother.
You know what?
Grandma was so scared that she cried for a long time back then.
So when my sister underwent surgery this time,
I dared not let her know.
So that's why you lied to Grandma that your sister's abroad?
You know what?
Hei Jiali is very smart.
Although her health is poor,
she always teases me,
saying that I only grow in height,
while she grows in intelligence.
When you visit Jiali next time,
can I go with you?
But you don't know her.
She has to meet her brother's boyfriend eventually.
[Taste on the Tip of the Tongue]
Hey.
If you keep doing this,
I'll take it seriously.
[Taste on the Tip of the Tongue]
Bai.
Those who know are as guilty as those who commit the crime.
Don't be soft-hearted.
Well, how about we have a serious discussion
about your seduction plan?
Let's finish eating first.
Come on. Eat.
The first step of seduction is crucial.
But I really can't do it.
No buts.
Don't you want to
repay Mr. Dou's favor as soon as possible?
Only after you repay his favor
can I complete my mission
and get out of here as soon as possible.
From now on,
we're 100% on the same side.
Come on.
I'll start with
the teaching of flirting, which is the most important part.
The first step is always the hardest.
The first contact with your mission target
is especially important.
Success or failure will be determined at first sight.
[Flirting: Take 1]
The target is a 22-year-old woman
who likes shopping.
Seize the "six-second first sight" attraction rule.
Baby.
Are you addicted to kissing?
I didn't mean it.
Be more serious.
I haven't even got to the point yet.
Alright.
But can you please
stay away from my ears?
What?
Is that your sensitive spot?
Alright.
I won't touch your ears.
But don't you kiss me sneakily again.
Turn around.
Come on.
[Flirting: Take 2]
Baby.
Sir, you got the wrong person.
I did.
That's because
she
cannot compare to you.
Wait.
How could you possibly succeed
with this kind of flirting technique?
Who did you learn it from?
Isn't this what the performance training course
at the Intelligence Bureau teaches?
How can you complete the mission
if you keep holding yourself back like this?
I can't drink.
A little of this and I'll be drunk.
You'll get drunk,
but you'll remember what happens,
right?
It's just a soda.
I can handle a soda.
I'll go get you a towel.
Where are you going?
I want to take care of you.
Bass soup.
You should go take a shower.
You're more relaxed when you're drunk.
So, have a drink to boost your courage.
But you need to remember how you feel.
[Flirting: Take 3]
Baby.
You got the wrong person.
No, I didn't.
It's you.
Do you want to continue?
Enough!
No need to continue.
Does this wine
have aphrodisiac effects,
or are you pretending to be innocent to get what you want?
You should sober up.
I'll go use the bathroom.
If No Sir knows about this,
he'll definitely send me back for retraining.
Why am I so easily affected?
Baby.
What in the world is Hei Yubo's problem?
Did he do it on purpose or not?
You're quite well-behaved when you're drunk.
I believe you didn't do it on purpose.
Sleeping like this.
How can you navigate this world
with such a lack of vigilance?
You better
not get caught.
One more time.
Why did you suddenly get up?
Or should I have informed anyone beforehand?
I should be asking you.
Why were you leaning on top of me like a ghost?
I came to call you down for breakfast,
and I saw your mouth moving.
I... I was just curious.
Curious?
Why should you be curious?
Don't you drink again from now on.
I drink?
It was you who asked me to drink.
You know very well I can't hold my liquor.
Fine.
Are you blaming me now?
Why are you so badly-behaved when you're drunk?
You just kiss around when you're drunk, right?
Tell me.
How many people did you kiss
before you confirmed you can't hold your liquor?
It's not like that.
You're the only one.
The first time you kissed me, it was an act in front of Grandma.
The second time was for the mission.
If you kiss me the third time,
does that mean...
The dishes are getting cold. Come out and eat.
He's really different when he's drunk.
It feels like he's suddenly turned into a CEO from a student.
Wait for me.
You look so similar to my boyfriend...
She has a necklace on her which was given to her by her boyfriend.
Once you get it,
the mission will be completed.
Does he even need to seduce her?
Why do they have to get so close?
[Find a way to switch that thing Hei Yubo got and take it back.]
Besides me, did No Sir send
someone else to watch Hei as well?
Or has someone in the convenience house
been tipping him off?
No Sir should know that business matters cannot be overstepped, right?
I'm in charge of Hei's matters.
[When are you coming back?]
[Did it go well?]
[Where are you?]
[Watching a movie.]
[Where are you going now?]
[Hei]
Why hasn't he read my messages?
He's not caught, is he?
If he gets caught, as his supervisor,
I should be notified.
Are you waiting here for me to come home?
Who's waiting for you?
I just came back.
I texted you just now
to see if you wanted to have dinner together.
Why didn't you reply?
Did the mission go well?
That woman asked me
not to be distracted during the date,
so she snatched my phone and turned it off.
So you went for dinner after the movie?
What did you have?
Some French cuisine.
We waited forever for the food and I didn't even get full.
I'm so hungry.
Hold on.
Hello, matron?
What trouble did my sister cause this time?
Okay.
I'll be right there.
What happened?
It's my sister.
Let's go. I'll go with you.
[Room 2] [Room 3]
You said you didn't eat enough for dinner.
I know you're allergic to milk.
You can have soy milk, right?
At least drink some.
The doctor said
she'll be fine.
Do you want to lean on me for a while?
It's getting late.
You should go back first.
I slept all day today.
I'm very energetic now.
Or
am I bothering you by being here?
Didn't you say last time that
you're allergic to the hospital's disinfectant,
and you'll faint if you smell it?
You remember it quite clearly.
But in order to keep my boyfriend company,
I'm okay with it.
Come on.
Close your eyes and get some sleep.
Hei, if you have dark circles
and look pale tomorrow,
your pretty little girl will be worried.
Go to sleep.
I'm really scared.
She still has a lot of things she wants to do.
Every time she saw me,
she'd tell me
what she wanted to do after she was discharged.
It's been a long time since she last played the claw machine.
But I can't help her with anything.
Who said that?
You are her bravest brother.
You're tough and strong.
There aren't many people like you in this world.
Moreover,
she's going to meet
the best match for her brother, his boyfriend, tomorrow.
Do you think
Jiali will be able to tell
whether we're a real couple or not?
How about
I sing you a song?
♫Open the door, little rabbit♫
♫Open it♫
♫I want to come in♫
♫No, I won't open it♫
What's your intention in approaching my brother?
[Preview]
He's not rich.
It's not because you covet his body, is it?
You're so good at it.
Let me see if that woman
will be so impressed by your handsome face that she doesn't want to leave.
Kiss me.
I'm jealous.
Then...
What about when you're with me?
Everything feels right when I'm with you.
If you kiss me again,
I'll take it seriously.