[Fight for You]
A person should have self-knowledge.
If you can't afford it,
just admire it from afar.
But what if one day,
someone gives you the apple?
Would you be willing to give it back?
[File 6: Does this mean we're together?]
[Doctor's Profile]
Why did I sleep so soundly?
Why didn't you wake me up?
Did they do the morning rounds?
How is your sister?
Don't worry.
We can go in to see her soon.
How about...
singing you a song?
♫Open the door, little rabbit♫
♫Open it♫
[Doctor's Profile]
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'll buy you breakfast on the way.
Don't threaten the doctor into hiding things from me from now on.
Nothing really happened.
They were too nervous.
I'm okay.
What if something really happened?
You didn't tell me anything either.
Your brother was worried about you.
He didn't sleep at all last night.
He waited outside the whole time.
So... you accompanied him?
Grandma said my brother has a boyfriend.
Yes.
It's me.
Since when did my brother start liking men?
He's so busy. How could he have time to date?
What's your intention of approaching my brother?
He's not rich.
Do you covet his body?
You look young.
What do you do?
Jiali...
The Intelligence Bureau should
hire someone like her.
I wonder if she's willing to work there.
Don't zone out.
The head nurse will kick you out
in ten minutes.
I'm Bai Zhouqi, a postgraduate working on the thesis.
Fate brought me under one roof with your brother.
From roommates to lovers.
In true love, gender doesn't matter.
Money doesn't matter either.
Besides, I've got both the looks and the brains.
Right,
I met your grandma too.
She likes me a lot.
Who would praise himself like that?
Because I'm worth it.
Brother,
I want some juice.
Did the doctor say you can drink it?
Yes.
I'll go.
You stay with your sister.
It's okay.
Let my brother go.
He knows what I like to drink.
You stay with me.
What's wrong?
My brother doesn't trust others easily.
He brought you here.
That means you're different to him.
Can I ask you for a favor?
Go ahead.
Don't let him do bad things.
He's at his wits' end because of my illness.
I'm sure he'll go to Dou Keyi.
I'm worried he'll be dragged into their mess.
Help me stop him.
Otherwise, I'd rather die.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
If he doesn't behave,
I'll spank him.
Then take him away later.
And call the doctor here.
What's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
I'm going now.
Just a little discomfort.
Don't tell my brother.
He gets nervous easily.
He won't leave if he knows.
Have a good rest.
We'll fight through this together.
The doctor said
as long as there's no rejection to the new medicine,
Jiali can have surgery soon.
You can worry.
But don't forget
you are not alone.
I'm with you.
I've been accepted by both Grandma and Jiali.
If this continues,
it'll become increasingly real.
What's wrong?
That woman just asked me out again.
Once the convenience house's matters are settled,
and my sister's surgery goes smoothly,
everything will go back to normal, right?
Help me stop him.
Otherwise, I'd rather die.
Make it quick,
so that there won't be more trouble.
If I go with you,
at least I can protect you
if anything happens.
You look like her ex-boyfriend.
You just want to get something back
from her, right?
No more hesitation.
Just mesmerize her.
Mesmerize her?
Just being around her makes me uncomfortable.
Then...
what about when you're around me?
I like it very much.
When I'm around you...
everything feels just right.
Why don't you teach me again?
I can just pretend
she's you. Right?
You want me to drive your car to pick her up?
Yes.
You can't ride a motorbike for a date, right?
Do you have a license?
Yes.
What?
Handsome, right?
What are you doing?
Unbuckling your seatbelt.
In case I don't want to get off because you're so handsome.
You're so good at this.
Then you try it.
Let me see if that woman will be so impressed
by your handsome face that she doesn't want to leave.
So?
Did I pass?
Not bad.
But you were not hot enough to keep me in the car.
You're back.
You're all dressed up. Where are you going?
I thought the date was tomorrow.
Just now, there was a case
about profiles on a dating website.
They said I should wear formal clothes.
It's rare to see you dressed so formally.
I went to the monthly meeting.
It really gave me a headache.
So annoying.
There were a bunch of professors.
Old-school.
Did you drink?
No.
You told me to learn how to mesmerize people, right?
I just realized you look great when you take off your clothes.
You try it.
Take off my clothes?
Should I continue?
Enough!
Enough.
Is that okay?
I'm going to the bathroom.
To the bathroom again?
You want to use the bathroom?
You can use it now.
Do you want to be with me for real?
Can I be with you for real?
Don't say no.
If I'm with you because...
If you like someone,
just...
do it.
Do you want to be with me for real?
Impressive.
You're not bad even without drinking.
Go like this tomorrow.
Wish you success.
Bai Zhouqi!
You know I was not kidding.
[Training Department of the Intelligence Bureau]
[Dou Keyi Convenience House]
[Refuse] [Answer]
[No Sir, Bu Xing]
[Missed call]
[Refuse] [Answer]
[No Sir, Bu Xing]
Bai Zhouqi.
I just came back from a business trip.
[Dou Keyi Convenience House]
I've read your routine meeting report.
It's quite concise.
I thought
there was no need to go over the mundane stuff.
Why waste words?
So...
no progress?
If I'm not the only one
sent by No Sir to tail Hei,
he must know his whereabouts.
I can't lie to him.
He's made contact with the target,
but he didn't get anything back.
They're expected to act again tomorrow.
But from what I've observed,
they don't really know what they're doing.
Hello?
That's it then.
You can choose how you want to do it.
But...
don't let us down.
You said you'd treat me to a meal
to cheer me up.
This is it?
Mm.
Why don't we terminate the mission?
Why?
Didn't you ask me to repay Mr. Dou's favor
as soon as possible?
But seeing you seduce someone
makes me feel like you're cheating on me.
I'm jealous.
There must be something fishy
about the call from No Sir.
It might be safer to make you
fail early.
So you still want to go?
Yes.
I've come this far.
I don't want to make things difficult for Mr. Dou and the others.
Mr. Dou, Mr. Dou.
Maybe your Mr. Dou has never
wanted you to get involved.
That Shi wants to drag you into this.
I don't want to owe them.
Whatever.
You won't listen to me,
but you do whatever they tell you to do.
Once this case is closed,
we'll go our separate ways.
Back to strangers.
You're not eating?
I've lost my appetite!
He drove my car
to pick her up for dinner.
And in a romantic environment...
That woman probably won't make the delivery today.
I'm sorry.
Grandma?
You should watch where you're going!
Sorry, I didn't see you.
Let me help you.
Right,
why are you alone?
Hei is working.
Grandma.
Have you seen Hei in a suit?
No.
He looks amazing.
Really?
Yes, let me show you.
Come. Sit.
Look.
Bai.
Talk to him when you have time.
I know money is very important,
but as long as we don't starve, that's enough.
I've never spent a penny of the money he gave me.
I've saved it all.
I'll give it back to him
before I die.
Grandma.
You know in my family, it's all men.
Grandma couldn't stand Grandpa.
My mom couldn't stand my dad.
We grew up being beaten and scolded.
It was that kind
of iron-blooded parenting.
So,
I really envy you and Hei.
I'll do my best to help him.
Don't worry.
After his parents passed away,
I forced Hei to bring his sister
to live with me.
How could a teenager know how to live alone?
You know his temper.
He's stubborn.
He didn't want me to be tired from running the braised food stall,
so he told me to shut it down.
My business was fine.
Why should I shut it down? Right?
He even got mad and said
he'd earn the living expenses himself.
He just won't listen.
He listened.
But he didn't take it to heart.
Yeah.
We haven't known each other for long,
but I think
you are my destined lover.
What about your boyfriend?
He's already dead.
Why are you mentioning him?
You're still wearing the necklace he gave you.
How are you going to prove
he's not important to you anymore?
What will it take for you to believe me?
Give me the necklace. I'll throw it away.
Tell me you love me.
Then I'll give you everything.
Kiss me.
Where did you come from?
He's mine!
Hei, who is he?
Hei?
Tell her who I am.
He is my...
You adulterers!
Don't beat him!
Don't!
You are the other woman!
You homewrecker!
Be gentle!
I almost succeeded.
Why did you suddenly show up?
[We'll just take a walk by the riverside.]
[On this dark and windy night, which romantic place will you go?]
[Humph! Don't cross the line!]
We haven't known each other for long,
but I think
you are my destined lover.
You're still wearing the necklace he gave you.
Give me the necklace. I'll throw it away.
Kiss me.
I told you
I don't want to see you with anyone else,
even if it's just an act.
Why?
You helped me so much before.
I regret it.
I feel uncomfortable seeing you with someone else.
What?
You want to go?
Go ahead.
I asked you
if you want to be with me for real.
Your answer is...
Were you serious or not?
This is the third time.
If you kiss me again,
I'll take it seriously.
I just want you to know
[Preview]
it's great to have you.
Bai,
what do your family members do?
Move out of your current apartment immediately.
I gave you a chance!
I'm so disappointed in you, Bai Zhouqi.
I order you to withdraw from the mission immediately.
You should dress appropriately during work hours
to demonstrate your demeanor as the chief.
If you get to know more about the real me,
you might regret it.
Are you hiding something from me?
What do you mean?