[Fight for You]
Who would have thought that glutinous rice mixed with pig blood
would become this dish?
Then, add peanut powder
and cilantro.
This flavor...
The people we meet
are all predestined.
The longer we spend together, the harder it is to tell
whether we're meant to be or meant to suffer.
[File 7: Meeting You, Is It Meant to Be or Meant to Suffer?]
Last time, I asked...
if you wanted to be with me for real.
What is your answer?
Are you joking or serious?
This is the third time.
If you kiss me again,
I'll take it as you mean it.
What do you mean?
You haven't answered yet.
I want to know what you really think.
I mean it.
I hope you're not joking.
Let's give it a try then.
Give... give it a try?
You mean dating?
What else would we be trying?
Then, we start from now?
You want to schedule a start date?
I'm afraid you're gonna say
"just friends" in the next moment
and push me away, pretending nothing happened.
The deal is sealed.
Now I can't run away anymore.
Do you feel reassured now?
This is more reassuring.
Things will always work out somehow.
Hello?
Okay.
Go, go, go.
Yes, it's very strong.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's go.
[Teppanyaki Burger]
What flavor should we get?
That one, that one.
That beef patty in the middle
has something really yummy inside.
It has truffle sauce.
Give it to her later.
Okay.
This is my first time.
-Hello.
Your order's here.
Thank you.
Easy enough, right?
Twelve.
Super duper many.
Twelve...
Hold on a sec.
That's a lot.
Hello?
Okay, got it.
Where should we go next?
Let's go.
What should we do?
Which one does the client want?
[Happy Land]
Come on.
Come on, I'll help you.
Can you do it?
Do you even know how to hold it?
You were like a secret agent in the movies.
Well?
Isn't your boyfriend cool?
Why did you...
I just want you to know...
it's great to have you.
[Braised Food]
[Mic on/off] [Camera on/off] [Hang up]
Grandma, I'm sorry.
I've just been so busy lately.
Jiali,
what's so good about being abroad?
Look at you. Without me taking care of you,
you've become so skinny.
[Mic on/off] [Camera on/off] [Hang up]
Grandma, I miss you so much.
If you miss me, come back to visit me.
Grandma!
Your brother is here.
I have to go.
Bye-bye.
Take good care of yourself.
[Mic on/off] [Camera on/off] [Hang up]
Bye-bye.
Here, Grandma.
Okay, good boy.
Thank you.
You can eat this, right?
Bai.
What do your family members do for work?
They're civil servants.
Then, has Hei met them yet?
Not yet.
Grandma, why did you suddenly ask that?
Nothing. I just...
hope that we can become a family soon.
It's too soon.
He'll feel pressured.
That's right.
It's nothing.
Bai, I just want to know more about you.
Eat up.
Let's dig in.
Okay.
Grandma, let's eat.
Madam! I'd like to order.
[Braised Food]
Coming, coming.
If
I can't even honestly answer
these simple questions,
how will I explain things to him later?
What's wrong? Something up?
My thesis advisor
wants to see me.
What about this?
Take this home for me.
Okay.
Then, I'll stay and help Grandma.
Go.
Move out of your current apartment immediately.
Our surveillance operation has been going smoothly lately.
Why all of a sudden?
Explain it.
Did this happen all of a sudden?
I trained you myself.
You can't fool me.
No Sir...
I warned you before!
Don't let us down!
Intelligence Officer Bai Zhouqi,
because you have developed personal feelings
for your surveillance target, Hei Yubo...
you have lost the ability to judge right from wrong.
You've deceived your superiors
and betrayed our trust.
As per regulations, you must be dealt with severely.
I hereby order you to withdraw from the mission immediately.
All subsequent matters will be arranged and taken over by others.
I do...
have feelings
for Hei—no, for Hei Yubo.
I'm so disappointed in you, Bai Zhouqi.
I gave you a chance.
Hei Yubo is always on guard
and doesn't easily trust others.
At first, to get intel from him,
I did everything I could to get close to him
and gain his trust.
That's why I slipped up and crossed the line.
I've watched you grow up since you were little.
This is the first time I've seen you so brave.
I know that Hei Yubo is my mission target.
I also know I shouldn't have other emotions toward him
to cloud my judgment.
But since you've been having him and me followed,
you should know
that he, like me,
is just a cover.
Getting smarter, huh?
So?
If you've only been using us
as pawns from the beginning,
you might as well continue.
If you bring in someone new now
who has to build a relationship with him from scratch,
all the effort invested in him previously will go to waste.
Instead,
you continue with your plan,
and I'll continue with mine.
You keep digging for your leverage,
and I'll be responsible for confirming
whether the person I like
is worth my doing all this.
I believe
that with Bai blood running through me,
I promise I'll hand him over myself.
Brother?
You still remember that you have a big brother?
The thing you want.
Honestly,
our family is a bit stuck in the past.
It's a new era now.
And you?
Still trying to have it both ways like in the old days.
Appearing obedient on the surface
while stubbornly doing whatever you want behind the scenes.
Zhouguo.
You heard, right?
Then... does Grandpa know about this yet?
These things haven't reached his ears yet.
The chief wants me to withdraw from the mission.
You know Bai is easily softhearted.
When he sees that young man doing
whatever it takes for his family,
of course, his sympathy overflows.
What?
No drinking during work hours.
What a pity.
It's vintage '61 Macallan inside.
This whisky...
stored in a container like this... is such a waste.
Just like your Bai,
being with you all... is such a waste.
Then, try to understand from the perspective of someone who's been there.
Weren't you the same with Dou Keyi before?
You were thick as thieves with him.
That was different.
How was it different?
You two were always together, inseparable.
Back then, rumors about you two were also spreading everywhere.
I... I mean,
judging people clearly is something
you only grasp after having experienced it yourself.
Don't
always use my grandfather's approach
of resorting to severe punishment for everything.
It's hard enough to recruit new people these days.
As far as I know,
you don't have
anyone around to replace Bai, right?
Anyway, our Bai
is just a smokescreen in your plan.
If you pull him out now,
what if my grandfather finds out?
What if it catches Dou Keyi's attention?
Aren't you afraid...
this could blow up?
What if he makes a mistake?
We don't dare to trouble you, Chief.
Our Bai family
will bring him back and discipline him strictly ourselves.
You've given your word.
Yes.
What?
During work hours...
proper attire...
brings out your aura as the chief.
This flask is for you.
I'll treat you to something even better next time.
Thank you, Zhouguo.
But please respect your work.
If something is wrong,
remember to correct it.
Correct it?
Zhouguo, he's really not a bad person.
It's not up to us to determine whether he's a bad guy or not.
Yes.
The higher-ups determine
who is good or bad.
Even though I can understand your feelings,
remember,
everything you say and do
represents our Bai family.
Keep your head clear.
Don't let emotions mess things up.
I'm off.
Be good.
Got it?
Who was that guy?
What are you doing?
Why did he get to touch you like that?
You mean that really handsome guy just now?
You're calling another man handsome?
Explain yourself clearly.
He...
is pretty good-looking.
Don't forget that you have a boyfriend.
Who was the one who went out
to eat with that girl before?
We're even now.
It can work like that?
Idiot.
That was my brother.
He is your brother?
Then, let's ask him to come back...
He had something to take care of.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Well... does your brother know we're together?
I didn't get a chance to tell him.
When can I meet your grandpa and your brother?
You will.
Don't worry.
You need to introduce us to each other.
Okay.
You want surveillance gear,
but you wouldn't apply through the department
because you are afraid of being bugged yourself?
Zhouguo, do you know
why No Sir assigned me this mission?
He has his reasons. Not our place to ask.
Why can you all
trust the organization's orders
so unconditionally?
Just doing whatever they instruct you to do.
Perhaps it's the subservience that's been passed down
through our Bai family line, etched into our bones.
I know you can't accept it from the bottom of your heart,
but...
do you dare to defy Grandpa?
What's wrong?
I have a cold.
I wanna some medicine.
Why are you up drinking alone
in the middle of the night?
I was scolded by my thesis advisor this afternoon.
So I'm drinking some beer to relieve stress.
Are you hiding something from me?
What do you mean?
Whether it's me almost being caught in a lie by Grandma
or me encountering difficulties on a task,
you're always there to help me.
You're involved in everything in my life.
But when it comes to your matters, you won't let me get involved.
Aren't I your boyfriend?
Getting scolded by my advisor happens all the time.
It's really just a minor thing.
Then why don't you rely on me more?
Or do you think I'm not someone you can trust?
Of course not.
I just don't want
to trouble you with my problems.
I know you're holding something back from me.
Bai,
what do your family members do for work?
They're civil servants.
Then, has Hei met them yet?
Not yet.
Maybe I still have a long way to go before I earn your trust.
But give me a little more time.
I'll definitely become a better person
so you can feel more at ease with me.
You're already great.
You love your family.
You're loyal to your friends.
I'm the one who's not good enough.
Bai.
Tell me what you're actually thinking.
If...
you get to know the real me someday,
you might regret it.
How could I?
You really trust me that much?
Of course.
How much do you trust me?
Other than my family,
you're the first person I've ever trusted.
Whenever I encounter a problem,
you're always the first one there to help me.
When I'm in danger,
you stand in front of me.
No matter what worries or past you have,
I'll accept them all.
Bai.
You must believe me.
Wait for me a second.
I need to use the bathroom.
I'm not that smart.
I can't guess if you don't tell me.
It shouldn't be just you giving me everything
while I give nothing back.
Or do you think...
I have nothing to give?
Bai,
[Preview]
did you put this
on my ear for me?
It looks great on you.
If you've done something wrong for my sake,
I'd rather not have the surgery.
Hei Jiali.
What kind of task pays enough to cover an entire surgery bill?
You'd have to risk your life for that, right?
I need more tasks.
Why don't you let me help you?
Why draw such a hard line between us?
Then why haven't you introduced me
to your family?
Are you afraid they won't approve of me as I am now?
You don't know me at all!
Looks like we won't be able to find common ground.