[Fight for You]
I lie every day.
For justice,
I fabricate identities.
For missions,
I concoct lies.
But there's a kind of lie
that I tell to protect the person I love.
[File 8: Lying Is My Way of Protecting You]
Prepare yourself for this.
I'm actually an intelligence agent
tasked with following and monitoring you.
The goal is to eliminate Dou Keyi
and his convenience house.
Our encounter wasn't a coincidence.
All the coincidences were not accidental.
They were all meticulously arranged.
But my feelings for you...
Between us...
Falling asleep at this kind of timing?
I finally mustered up my courage.
You must report all the information
to the higher-ups from now on.
This is your last chance.
Staying by his side,
at least I can find a chance
to help him get away as soon as possible.
If someone else were to follow and monitor him,
Hei would really get caught.
Bai.
This thing on my ear...
Did you put it on me?
It looks great on you.
It's just I've never worn this before,
so I'm a bit not used to it.
You'll get used to it if you wear it every day.
Well, it's all because someone said
he felt insecure since I didn't rely on him.
So I specially chose a couple gift
to express my feelings.
Forget it if you don't want to wear it.
Give it back to me.
Since it's a gift to me, it's mine now.
These are matching cartilage earrings.
Don't you take it off.
Okay.
I want to give you a gift too.
Can I choose?
You have something you want?
No matter what it is,
you'll give it to me?
As long as it's something you want,
I'll find a way to give it to you.
I want a wish.
A wish?
I'll save it for now and tell you later.
I see.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes, to the convenience house.
What about you?
I'm stuck on my thesis.
I need to stay at home and work on it.
Be good and work hard.
By the way,
I took that cold remedy yesterday
and it made me drowsy.
Did you have something to tell me?
Hold on.
Hello?
Really?
Okay, thank you.
What is it?
It was the hospital,
saying there's a chance for
Jiali's heart surgery.
They want me to come over for
a face-to-face meeting.
Really?
That's great.
What did you want to say to me just now?
It was nothing.
I'll go to the hospital with you.
No need. Just focus on writing
your thesis at home.
Okay then.
See you later.
Okay, bye.
Yubo, why are you here?
The doctor wants to see you?
Your gift, pretty girl.
Bai didn't come with you?
Bai?
You should call him Brother, okay?
He's busy today.
What?
You prefer him to come?
You've been talking about him since I came.
I'm the one who treats you better, okay?
So ungrateful.
I thought you broke up.
After all, you have no sense of romance.
Then get better soon to get discharged, so you can
keep an eye on us yourself.
I've improved a lot.
I may not be able to get discharged.
A couple of days ago, I dreamed that I died.
Hey.
What kind of nonsense was that?
Listen to me.
The doctor said your condition is fine,
and the surgery can be scheduled
in the next few days.
The medical field is very advanced now.
They say there's a method where
an artificial valve can be implanted
using a catheter.
And after a short rest,
you'll be able to get discharged in a week.
Don't be afraid.
The wound will only be 1 cm long,
and the surgery will only take two hours.
How much is it?
I've heard the doctors talk about it.
Yubo.
Where will you get the money?
Don't worry about that.
Are you going to sell yourself again?
What are you talking about?
Every time you come to see me,
you're always covered in bruises.
Have you ever thought about my feelings?
These minor injuries are nothing.
You always say it's nothing.
These are all
out-of-pocket expenses.
If you do something bad for me,
then I'd rather not have the surgery.
Hei Jiali!
How much money have you spent on me
since childhood?
It's not like I'm ever going to recover.
I might as well just die.
Are you really not going to do the surgery?
No.
I don't want treatment.
[Grandma]
Then speak to Grandma yourself.
Tell her you're actually in the hospital,
not abroad,
and you'd rather die than ask her for help.
If Grandma found out about this,
how heartbroken would she be?
You know how much I love you.
Do you really want to make me worry?
Be brave.
Money can be earned again,
but I only have one sister.
[My surgery requires a lot of money. I'm worried he's going to do something foolish again.]
[Bai, keep an eye on silly Hei for me!]
We recommend that your sister undergo
a catheter-based
artificial aortic valve implantation.
We suggest using a durable biological valve
to reduce the use of anticoagulants.
Regarding the items that require
out-of-pocket expenses,
as her family, we need your confirmation.
Di.
I need more work.
Didn't I already give you some?
Alright then, I'll add some more.
Happy?
What now?
The recent quests have all...
They've all been too simple.
Simple?
You know, I haven't even settled the score
with you for failing the mission last time
because of your relationship.
Do you know what I had to do to complete
that mission later?
I even...
It was my fault last time.
I'm sorry.
Forget it.
My expectations of you were too high.
It's better for us to count on
ourselves out here.
Di.
I promise I won't make any more mistakes.
Promise?
How can you guarantee that?
You might as well ask me instead of him.
You two seem to be really idle, huh?
How's Jiali been doing lately?
She's fine.
You're even lying to me now?
I've asked the hospital.
Why would they tell you?
How much more do you need?
I'll transfer it to you.
Mr. Dou.
He hasn't even paid off his previous debt,
and now he's asking for an even bigger sum.
Did he ask?
I'm the one who asked, right?
You always protect him.
Remember to give me your account number.
Mr. Dou.
I can't take your money anymore.
Just think of it as me buying
a car for Jiali, alright?
I've had you work here and
advance your salary.
All I do is buy flowers, act as a purchasing agent,
and walk cats and dogs.
How much of this do you think I need to do
to pay off my debt?
Mr. Dou.
Are you taking pity on me?
I only take money for work.
Or I'll figure something else out myself.
Alright.
I heard you.
Go back first.
Don't think I don't know what kind of job
you were planning to give him.
Being all presumptuous.
It's not like that, Mr. Dou.
Didn't you say Bai
works for Bu Xing?
I thought I'd send Hei to confuse them.
Who would have known he was so clueless?
He didn't even realize he was being watched.
He's not cut out for this line of work.
Don't drag him into this.
Are you still mad at me, Jiali?
Alright.
I promise you.
I'll be good.
Jiali is worried about you.
Alright, I admit it.
Jiali told me
about your fight.
She complained to you?
You talked to her on my behalf, right?
This time,
I'm on Jiali's side.
Let me ask you.
Why did you move out to live alone
after arranging for Jiali to be hospitalized?
It was because to save Jiali,
you might have to take risks,
and you didn't want Grandma to worry,
right?
What are you trying to say?
Have you ever considered the feelings
of the people around you?
Your grandma, who doesn't know
what he grandson does out there;
your sister, who always sees her brother
covered in bruises during hospital visits;
and
me, who's always been by your side.
We're all worried about you.
Don't worry.
Look at me. I'm so tall.
I'm tough and resilient.
Physical injuries are nothing.
I can share it with you.
I have a suggestion.
Jiali is like my own sister.
We're so close anyway,
so how about you let me cover
this medical expense first?
I'm doing this
out of selfish thoughts.
I want you to focus on our relationship.
You can take your time to pay me back.
I appreciate your kindness.
Why are you rejecting me?
Because I don't want my own matters
to affect our relationship.
Are you really going to
make me watch you worry?
You don't need to worry.
This matter has been solved.
How?
Mr. Dou will arrange work for me.
You mean the convenience house?
You call that work?
You do whatever they tell you to do,
going there blindly without
knowing anything.
Even when there's danger,
you can't avoid it.
This is my choice.
Can't you respect me?
Do you know how stupid this is?
Making such a dangerous decision
for your ridiculous pride.
Your family is my family.
Why can't you let me help you?
Why draw such a hard line between us?
Then why don't you want to
introduce your family to me?
Are you worried they won't approve of me
as I am now?
My ridiculous pride?
This is the only thing left
that's been supporting me to this day.
I'm not like you,
who grew up in a privileged environment,
living in an ivory tower,
unaware of the hardships of the world.
You don't know me at all!
Right.
Come to think of it,
I've told you everything about me,
but I don't know you at all.
Hei.
It seems we won't reach a consensus.
You promised me a wish.
Don't get involved with the convenience
house anymore.
If you still want to be with me,
then don't go.
I don't understand.
You've always been so supportive.
Why are you suddenly insisting that I quit now?
What kind of work pays enough to
cover an entire surgery bill?
You'd have to risk your life for that,
wouldn't you?
Okay.
I promise you.
I won't let anything happen to me.
But don't misuse your wish.
Next time, make another wish
on something that can make yourself happy.
Just don't put yourself in danger,
and I'll be happy.
This is your last chance.
I'm sorry.
I said something harsh yesterday,
but I know you meant well.
Hei.
Think about Grandma and Jiali.
Don't make one mistake after another
and get involved deeper and deeper.
Let's talk when I'm back.
After I come back, I'll listen to you on everything,
okay?
Where are you going?
To find Di.
That Shi again?
I'll go with you.
After the seduction plan failed last time,
he still gets a bit angry whenever
I bring you up.
I'll be right back.
Okay. Got it.
By the way, can you do me a favor?
What is it?
Jiali is still mad at me.
Can you go to the hospital and keep
her company for me?
And...
And put in a good word for her brother,
right?
Yes.
What's your relationship with Bai?
[Preview]
I'm Bai Zhouqi's supervisor.
I've been following you for so long,
only to find out you're of no use at all.
So all of this was not because you like me,
and it was all just a mission?
What were you feeling
when you did all this?
They fell in love pretty fast,
but they turned against each other
just as quickly.
Hei!
So confident as to dare come alone?
Aren't you worried I might do something
to you?