[Fight for You]
Your kindness to me,
the days we spent together,
and those happy memories —
I don't know
which parts are real
and which parts are fake.
I only know that I've always been sincere.
Thank you for showing up.
[File 9: Everything is fake]
[Braised Food]
Don't eat spicy food if you can't.
I'm not like someone,
who had gastric perforation due to eating spicy food.
Bai
is Bai Zhouguo's younger brother.
You should've trained him before sending him here.
You planted an inexperienced person
around me.
What?
The Intelligence Bureau is training green hands?
Your fledgling
has been tagging along
behind my newbie all day long.
Does the convenience house
like to use such green rookies on missions now?
So, that Bai —
am I supposed
to deal with him or ignore him?
Then that Hei —
am I supposed to let him go
or should I bring him in?
Did you eat too much chili?
You're at peace sometimes,
and sometimes, you're against each other.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
The worst thing is being confused
and unable to let go.
Just like pig's blood cakes —
if you stew them too long, they'll stick to the bottom of the pot.
That smell...
Wait.
Wear this shirt.
I think something's wrong with the deal.
Be careful.
Bai Zhouqi, I order you to stay.
How dare you disobey me?
Don't go there. Do you hear me?
I can't do that.
Sorry, No Sir.
I told you he's my responsibility.
You go get the person you want.
I'll take care of my man.
Dou Keyi, not bad.
You're so confident.
You came alone.
So this is what Di meant.
Aren't you worried I might do something to you?
Or is there an ambush outside?
I'm so scared.
Who are you?
Where is Dou Keyi?
I came in his place today.
I thought I could get rid of Dou Keyi.
I didn't expect a pretty boy to show up and get himself killed.
And I paid for this.
Can I get a refund now
or a discount?
It's okay.
Give it to me.
[Two people are sharing locations]
Your boss sent you here to die.
I can spare your life.
Stop!
Run!
Bai?
Bai.
Let's go.
Let's go to the hospital.
No.
The police will investigate you.
Why are you
here?
If
you know why I'm here,
will you forgive me?
[Hospital]
Hei Yubo.
Everything's arranged at the hospital.
The police won't come asking questions.
Go back and take good care of Bai.
It'll be over once he recovers.
Over?
What do you mean?
What's your relationship with Bai?
I'm Bai Zhouqi's supervisor.
As for the rest,
think about it.
Or
ask him yourself.
Hei.
Hei!
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
Hei.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
The bad guys have been caught.
The doctor said you need a good rest.
Be good.
It won't hurt so much after you get some sleep.
This is the second time you got hurt for me.
This time,
did you happen to pass by again?
You're awake.
Nothing good happens when you run into me.
Last time, it was a knife wound.
This time, it's a gunshot wound.
I really...
This is called a sympathy ploy.
I can
take advantage of this
when you're angry in the future.
Nonsense.
Listen.
Don't do that again.
It's not very hot.
Here.
Slowly.
Why were you there yesterday?
[Professor]
Aren't you going to answer the call?
I'm tired.
Get some more sleep then.
It won't hurt so much after you fall asleep.
I didn't touch Hei Yubo.
I'll deal with you
after you deal with him.
I give you two options.
You come back, and I'll let him go.
Or
you stay with him,
and I'll investigate you both.
Why are you up?
Feeling unwell?
I have something to say.
It's late.
Let's talk tomorrow.
You asked me
why I was there yesterday.
I said let's talk tomorrow.
This...
is for wiretapping and tracking.
My mission
is to keep an eye on you.
What do you mean?
I was sent by the Intelligence Bureau
to work undercover around you.
I'm here to investigate Dou Keyi and the convenience house's
illegal dealings.
So...
So since the very beginning,
you've been with me
just to catch Mr. Dou?
You should've continued to lie.
Why are you telling me now?
I've been following you for so long,
only to find out you're of no use at all.
I don't want to waste any more time.
Then why did you save me from the knife and the bullet?
Why were you worried I'd be arrested for interrogations?
And what about this?
All of that was not because you love me,
but because they were your missions?
From beginning to end,
you've been an intelligence agent playing your part,
and I've been forced to play
the role of a fool who's been kept in the dark.
Thanks for the show.
Thank you
for making me believe this love foolishly.
Don't do this.
It's not like you.
Then what am I like?
Silly and cute?
Did you have fun watching?
You had to date your target
for your missions.
It must have been tough.
How do you want me to cooperate next?
Switch my side and help you catch Mr. Dou?
Or arrest me and imprison me?
Just tell me!
If you do this again,
what if you can't wear a ring in the future?
Then I'll do it after wearing a ring.
I won't take it off anyway.
Who's it from? You cherish it so much.
I'm waiting for you to give me one.
How did you feel
when you did all that?
Ridiculous
or pathetic?
I'm sorry.
That thing is fake.
No big deal. It's fine.
Also,
Bai was actually sent by...
the Intelligence Bureau.
The whole game
was just a mutual test
between me and the Intelligence Bureau.
You and Bai
were like this crispy chicken wing,
a dish served
with the wine.
So...
you knew everything from the beginning?
Do you know why
I only asked you to do trivial things
like walking dogs and looking for cats?
Once
you enter this industry,
no matter how careful you are,
your shoes will get wet.
Once your shoes get wet and dirty,
no one would
care about what they used to look like.
I won't trouble you with the convenience house's things anymore.
But the Bai family has been intelligence agents for generations.
Bai Gangzheng
might come and force you and Bai to cut ties.
Prepare for it.
It won't be necessary.
Even our love was fake.
I was just his target.
Fake?
Then why
are you sitting here unharmed?
Why is Bai the one who got hurt?
I don't agree with you two being together.
After all, the Bai family is too crafty.
It'll be hard for both of you.
Maybe he doesn't care at all.
Maybe he's dying to break free from me.
People lie,
but their eyes don't.
Think about
the way he looked at you.
So never
lose yourself
or misjudge others because of anger.
Hei.
Hei!
I admit
at first, I approached you with a purpose.
But I don't know when
I started to hate who I am
after seeing you work
so hard for Grandma and Jiali.
So,
I wanted to help you finish your missions quickly
and end everything.
But...
I somehow fell in love with you.
I wanted to tell you the truth many times.
But I knew
as long as I said it,
it would all be over between us.
Don't you want me anymore?
You're such a nice person.
You're supposed to say,
"I forgive you,"
or "It's okay,
we'll figure it out together."
Or at least wait until I recover.
And I didn't mean to say that.
I just didn't want you to be investigated.
Hei.
[Pay rent on the 15th day]
[Have a birthday feast on May 26]
[Reminder: utilities must be paid today]
Wait a little longer.
[Preview]
At least let me say...
Do you think he still wants to talk to you?
From the very beginning, you two were destined to stand on opposite sides.
If my presence is a burden to him,
is it better to let go
no matter how much I love him?
Hei.
Tell me,
what are these?
Was it for your mission?
I didn't complete the mission.
Because I fell in love with him.
What did you say?
I want to be the one who protects Bai
and shoulder everything for him.