[Fight for You]
People always say that good and evil cannot coexist.
But can the right and the wrong
be absolute?
Whether we're a match or not,
we decide for ourselves.
There is a kind of willingness...
that exists because that person is you.
There's a kind of persistence that lasts until the end
because that person is you.
[File 10: I Won't Give Up on You]
You still changed the bandages for me.
That means even if you're angry,
you'll still forgive me, right?
I admit,
at first, I approached you with ulterior motives.
But I don't know when it started—
watching you work so hard for Grandma
and for Jiali,
I started to hate who I was.
So I wanted to quickly help you finish the task
and end everything.
But somewhere along the way, I fell for you.
I wanted to tell you the truth many times...
but I knew
that the moment I did,
it would all be over between us.
Don't you want me anymore?
Hei...
Just wait for me a little longer.
At least let me say goodbye...
You think he still wants to talk to you?
From renting this place
to becoming his roommate to surveilling him—
from the very beginning, you two were destined to be on opposite sides.
Now, you just say, “Sorry, it was for the mission.
Let's just be friends?"
Bai Zhouqi,
are you the idiot here, or is he?
I don't know,
and I don't want to know
just how real your act with him became.
But let me give you a piece of advice:
don't challenge our grandfather.
Stop struggling.
Or you'll reopen your wound.
Okay.
I'll go pack up.
No need.
I'll send someone to pack for you.
Don't keep Grandpa waiting.
Zhouguo...
Let's go.
-Zhouguo...
-Go!
Zhouguo...
Outlier.
How could our Bai family have an outlier like you?
Rumors at the Intelligence Bureau say my grandson
has lost control over a target
and has even fallen in love with him!
And now you've even taken a bullet for such a person!
What kind of person?
Grandpa, you've never seen Hei
and don't understand him.
How can you deny everything about him
just because he's on the other side?
Since ancient times, good and evil have always been enemies.
People like him are a threat
and the source of chaos.
They shouldn't even exist!
Hei is the most loyal
and kind-hearted person I've ever met!
Still talking back?
This is the first time in our family's history
that someone has been suspended as punishment.
What a disgrace!
Grandpa, stop clinging to those outdated ways of thinking!
You think you're clear-headed
about right and wrong, but you're not!
What did you say?
Grandpa!
Bai hasn't recovered yet.
You can wait until he's better
before disciplining him.
[Loyalty, Compassion, and Integrity]
How are you being his brother?
Don't tell me you know nothing.
And that Bu Xing.
What kind of boss is he?
That convenience house has been around for years, and we still haven't caught them.
[Loyalty, Compassion, and Integrity]
Is he incompetent,
or is he deliberately letting them slide?
Understood.
I'll relay your message
to Bu Xing.
[Loyalty, Compassion, and Integrity]
Are you alright?
I told you
not to go head-to-head with Grandpa.
Hei!
Zhouguo.
I'm here to get his things.
Is Bai alright?
Even if he wasn't, what could you do about it?
Don't be too hard on him. He's injured now.
You really care about him...
and don't hate him?
He lied to you.
He's suffering just as much from having lied to me.
This job was never right for him.
That's the mission of a man from the Bai family.
No one cares whether you want it or not.
If he hadn't met you,
he wouldn't be in such a difficult position.
He had never been in a relationship before,
and his sympathy runs wild.
But you...
you look tough enough.
Hold back and don't contact him.
As time goes by,
he'll forget.
Hei,
the drinks in the fridge are all mine.
You drink water.
I found it.
It was right underneath. How could you not see it?
Look!
I managed to keep it alive.
For you.
We sent our Bai to the Intelligence Bureau all safe and sound,
and now he returns home with a gunshot wound.
Chief,
don't you owe us an explanation?
Forget it.
Seeing you like this
is worse than scolding you.
You got beaten up too?
It really hurts!
You would have been beaten too if you had been there.
So, after all that trouble,
did you catch them?
Yes.
The thing they were trading that day.
Isn't this...
Sweet potato starch!
Dou Keyi is really something.
My poor Bai took a bullet
for this small bag of sweet potato starch.
Right,
how are you going to handle Hei Yubo?
What about him?
He showed up at the scene with a box of sweet potato starch
and was ambushed before he could do anything else.
And your brother has defended him like that.
So, I've asked Bai to deal with him.
What a joke, right?
Yeah.
Dou Keyi got away clean
and even got the Intelligence Bureau
to get rid of the man he was planning to double-cross.
Two birds with one stone.
Dou Keyi really is a genius.
What?
Hand Dou Keyi's case to someone else.
Do you know that you're mixing
in too many personal feelings?
If it had been Dou Keyi standing there
that day instead of Hei,
would you still have let them open fire?
I heard
what you said outside my door that day.
Are you okay?
Shall we talk properly?
Just remember
that unfulfilled wish of mine.
You promised me a wish!
Don't get involved with the convenience house anymore.
If you still want to be with me,
then don't go.
Why don't you eat?
You said
as long as I cut ties with him,
you would leave him alone.
Why are you still having people investigate him?
If he hasn't done anything wrong, why should he
be afraid of being investigated?
Every time I mention that Hei guy,
whatever I say, you argue back.
You're hopeless!
Tell me, what is all this?
Was all of this just for the mission?
Isn't your boyfriend cool?
It's great to have you.
Don't forget,
you have a boyfriend now.
I know. You have strong empathy.
Combined with your guilt,
it's making you unable to move on.
It's understandable.
All right.
The mission is done.
I failed the mission!
Because I've fallen in love with him.
It must be that Hei guy who taught you these bad ideas!
Grandpa,
I'm the cruel one.
I'm the one who fell in love with him!
Shut up!
Both of you are men.
What love?
How can two men be together?
How inappropriate!
Times have changed, Grandpa.
Why can't we?
Why can't my love for someone
simply be accepted?
Zhouguo, it hurts.
Be gentler!
Didn't you just act all tough earlier,
not making a peep?
That was different.
In the heat of the moment, I had to hold it together!
You're so brave, huh?
Is it worth it?
What if he doesn't want you anymore after all this?
Hei is not that kind of person.
You sure trust him, don't you?
How's Grandpa doing?
Finding out you've fallen in love with your mission target—
and a man at that—
is a huge shock
for him.
Do you understand?
I know it's hard for Grandpa.
But a little bump
won't dent a steel wall.
If you want to break through, go big!
You...
you look harmless on the outside,
but you're actually
the most stubborn one in our Bai family.
You're already like this,
and you're still going on a hunger strike protest?
If only Hei were here.
Sorry to disappoint.
I'm not Hei.
I never thought
I'd do this behind Grandpa's back.
I'm helping you not because I approve of you,
but because our Bai Zhouqi
is the type who never gives up once he's made up his mind.
I'm afraid if you ignored him,
he'd blame himself
and might even come to resent others.
But I...
I'm also afraid that he doesn't want to talk to me.
I'm more afraid that he'll run away from home because of you.
If Grandpa really goes berserk, no one can stop him.
He's really torn, too.
Grandpa forced him to cut ties with you
by offering to let you off.
He's worried that you'll keep getting tangled up with the convenience house.
To be honest,
you are just two kids
who know nothing.
You two kids
just behave yourselves for a while.
Wait until we adults sort things out,
and then you can date or break up however you like.
We won't break up.
I want to be the one who protects Bai
and shoulders everything for him.
Let me just say this:
if you're going to do that, wait a bit.
Don't be impulsive.
Picked this up while passing by.
I heard
that this stall is pretty good.
What are you cutting?
Dried tofu.
You're cutting it so neatly.
Let's play tic-tac-toe.
Here.
Your turn. Which spot do you want?
Is this how you're gonna play?
Yes.
I'll go here.
My turn. I choose here.
You can't use that spot.
Why did you eat it?
Grandma's cooking is amazing.
In the future, we should start a chain.
Let's start with home delivery.
From now on,
we'll be the braised food stall duo!
[Hei]
[No Answer]
[Bai]
What are you doing here?
I...
Shh. Come in first.
Hurry.
Idiot.
Why were you standing in the rain outside?
Take off your clothes.
Isn't that moving a bit too fast?
Just keep your voice down.
It must hurt a lot.
I owe you an apology.
Okay.
You give me your apology,
and I'll give you our future.
Be good.
Save this for next time.
We can make mistakes,
[Preview]
but we can't miss out.
What you can't let go of, hold on to
with everything you've got.
Please approve of our relationship.
I will never accept it.
Then I'll prove it to you through my persistence.
As long as Bai wants me by his side,
I will do everything I can.
Did Hei help you do something?
Grandma!
Stop hitting him!
Who's making a scene in my house?
Hei...
Hei what?
I hope our love lasts a long, long time.