The Marvel universe is pervasive.
It's a gigantic part of pop culture.
Marvel is a powerhouse today,
but most people don't realize
they almost didn't exist.
People think that Stan
Lee just came on the scene
and created these great
characters, not realizing he had
already been there in the
industry for a couple of decades.
You start to unravel the history,
and realize that it all began
with Stan Lee going,
"I just don't want to do this,"
almost walking away from comics.
I had wanted to quit working there.
I wanted to do a lot of things
that were different.
Marvel had a lot... a lot of luck
in its corner as far as timing.
If you didn't
have Stan Lee and Jack Kirby
in the right place at the right time,
we wouldn't be talking
about Marvel Comics today.
When you think about Stan Lee
and Jack Kirby
writing all of these comic books
that have now become these
iconic movies, it's just amazing.
Stan and Jack coming
together was a monumental
turn in the history of pop
culture that nobody saw coming.
There wasn't anything
that would lead you to think
that these guys are going
to change the world.
_
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
My name isn't Stan Lee,
it's Stanley Liebert,
and I cut my last name in half
to make it Lee
because I figured someday
I'm going to write
the great American novel,
and I don't want to use this name
that's going to be so famous
someday, use it on comics.
Stan Lee had
aspirations of being a great writer.
He had aspirations of telling
the great American story,
but he also had to make a living,
and he made a living
in the family business,
which was called
Timely Comics at the time,
but eventually it would
change its name to Marvel.
Well, I think I was
about 17 at the time.
I heard that there was a job open
at a publishing company
that was owned
by a cousin of mine,
and when I got there,
I found out that the job opening
was in the comic book department,
and I use the word
"department" loosely,
'cause it consisted of two people,
Joe Simon and Jack Kirby.
I walked in, and I said,
"I'm applying for a job here,"
and they barely looked up
from what they were doin'.
They said, "Okay, okay,
we need some help,"
and they had me go down
and get 'em a sandwich
at the drugstore down below,
and that sorta started the, uh...
the story.
Jack Kirby
was a blue-collar guy.
He came out of
the Lower East Side ghetto,
and, whereas a lot of people
used comics as a stepping stone,
Jack Kirby embraced comics.
This is what he wanted to do.
The newspapers at that time
were very large, colorful,
and I loved the comics because
of the brightness displayed
by the fellows who drew them.
They remain...
remain with me always,
and when comic books
first came into being,
it drew me to them.
Jack was a great guy,
and it was incredible to watch him,
'cause it was as though he had
already drawn it in his mind.
Whatever he put down
seemed to be really perfect.
Captain America
was a pretty quick hit.
It came out just before World War II,
and, you know,
it has that famous cover
of Captain America
punching out Adolf Hitler.
But what happened was
Joe Simon and Jack Kirby,
the creators of Captain America,
left Timely Comics
due to the fact that they felt
that they were not financially
being compensated
for all the work
that they'd been doing,
and suddenly an errand boy,
Stan Lee, becomes editor.
I was the only guy left
in the department,
and the publisher, he said,
"Do you think you could
take care of running this place
until I hire a grown-up?"
I said, "Sure, I can handle it,"
and he probably forgot
to hire the grown-up,
because ever since then, I was
the guy doing the comic books.
For 20 years,
under Stan's editorship,
the company was pretty much
devoted to, like,
chasing whatever fad
was out there, you know?
They did Westerns, they did horror,
they did romance.
Stan wanted to
write things other than comics.
Everybody who wrote comics wanted
to write things other than comics.
They were disposable items.
They were not meant to be reprinted.
It was an industry where,
no matter how good you were,
you couldn't get that famous,
you couldn't get that rich,
and Stan was just staying in it
because that was the job he had,
and he had a relation to
the owner of the company,
and it's tough to say,
"I'm going to turn that aside now."
Because he was working
so many hours,
he couldn't take the time away
from comics to write a novel.
He was kind of trapped,
in a certain way.
The thing about Jack was
he, you know, had kind of
fallen on evil times in the '50s.
The comics changed.
His kind of vitality was no
longer really wanted in comics.
They became very bland.
He ended up at DC,
and he was doing something like
"Challengers of the Unknown."
He was doing
"Challengers of the Unknown"
and a couple other things over there.
DC let him go.
They thought that some of his
stylistic works were bad drawing.
He had a family to feed.
Jack was scurrying around
to different publishers,
trying to find work.
There wasn't much.
In the 1950s, there was
a big backlash against comics.
There was a senate subcommittee
hearing for juvenile delinquency
that pointed the finger
at comic books.
You know, churches were
holding comic book burnings,
and sales just
kind of bottomed out.
Stan had
a midlife crisis, for sure.
He was already about
40 years old at that point.
He realized, "I had these dreams,
that hasn't happened because
I've been here all this time
just coasting along."
At that time, DC started
really coming alive
in superheroes, with this
genius stroke they had
of putting their main heroes
together in one big group.
The fellow who was then
the publisher, he said to me,
"You know, Stan, I found out that DC Comics
has a book called "The Justice League,"
and it's selling pretty well,
and maybe we oughta do a book
with a lot of superheroes."
And my wife said to me,
"Stan, if you want to quit anyway,
why don't you do one book
the way you'd like to do it?
The worst that happens is you'll be
fired, but so what? You want to quit."
When your back's against the
wall, that's absolutely...
when you're crisis is often
when the best ideas come.
I decided I would try to
do them a little differently,
and I wanted Jack Kirby
to do the first one,
'cause I felt
he was the best there is.
It must have been strange
for Jack Kirby to come back
and be working for this kid
who had been his assistant
almost 20 years earlier,
but there weren't
a lot of options for an artist.
He was pretty much forced
to come back to Marvel.
At the beginning
of the 1960s, the idea that
these two guys would be able
to create something special
that would be remembered
in a year,
much less decades later,
was impossible to fathom.
DC became
the establishment in the '50s,
and really the big corporate
comic book publishing company
that everybody recognized.
Because DC had the trinity,
Superman, Batman, Wonder Woman,
they were already well established
20 years ahead of Marvel Comics.
They had
the distribution agreements
that got their magazines out
into the newsstands,
but they also played it
as safe as humanly possible.
As a result, the stories that
came about in the comics
were really designed
for very young kids.
They were written
for 7-year-old kids.
There was no thought, really,
of characterization,
of personality,
so on the first one,
which became "The Fantastic Four,"
I was trying to take
these comic book characters
and treat them
as if they were in a book
by some famous author,
by Charles Dickens,
and make them real characters,
as much as possible,
in the comic book medium.
Even the villains are people.
There is something in their lives
that makes them become
a problem to others.
They were not like
The Justice League over at DC.
They had issues.
They had problems.
I honestly don't believe that they
thought it would be successful.
I remember seeing
"The Fantastic Four"
on the stands in the summer of '61,
so I picked it up,
and I really found
that it was quite different
from the DC comics.
The art was more exciting,
but the writing
was even more strange,
because the characters were
a little more realistic.
It took those comic book tropes
of heroism and so forth,
and kind of turned them on their head by
having these characters
not like each other.
Plus, the villain
was even sympathetic.
This guy was a tortured guy
who could barely see,
a rather pitiful creature.
You know, these comic books
are really about people
who are flawed humans,
and I think that Stan Lee
and Jack Kirby
really brought those characters,
and made them very complex
from the beginning,
and ultimately,
it resonated with people.
The idea that a team of superheroes
would have fights and break
up, it just blew my mind,
and it's immediately better
than the Superman
and Batman comics I was reading.
Luckily, the book sold,
and my publisher said,
"Gimme another, uh, book, Stan.
We're goin' strong,
let's do some more."
Stan thought
he was going to quit comics
when he wrote Fantastic Four,
and I think he was as surprised
as anybody by its success,
and so all of a sudden,
things were working,
and Stan and Jack were able
to dig a little bit deeper
into their ambitions.
Bruce Banner is a nuclear scientist
who sees some teenaged greaser
driving on the test site,
and he goes out to rescue him
and gets bombarded
with gamma rays.
The result of that is
that he occasionally
turns into this huge, angry monster.
It's a Jekyll-Hyde situation,
as much a horror story as anything.
Around that time, Stan Lee also decided
to change the name of the company.
Originally, years ago,
we were called Timely Comics.
Then we were called Atlas Comics.
I couldn't do enough
with the word "Atlas"
in advertising, and I said, "Gee,
I'm gonna change the name
of our company to Marvel,"
because I could get so much
out of it, like sayings like,
"Welcome to the Marvel age
of comics."
In a very short
amount of time in the early '60s,
Lee and Kirby created
a huge cast of characters
that, to this day,
is just still amazing.
It was a magic
between the two of them
that I don't think has ever
been reproduced.
Jack, his work very
over the top and exaggerated,
and Stan's strength
was creating characters
and writing dialogue for them
that was very, very human,
and maybe they do sound conflicting,
but on the page, it took that
over-the-top situation
and suddenly
you could identify with it,
because of the way they acted
and the things they said.
It was suddenly very human.
As they grew, as they expanded,
especially during
that two-year period, you know,
when they were creating
these characters,
people started to sit up
and take notice.
You know, another aspect of it
is it's great art.
Jack, he created
an in-your-face way
of telling a story that,
if you look at comics
prior to Jack Kirby's work,
there's no evidence.
It's very flat.
DC Comics,
very rarely would you see
exaggerated close-ups,
or, um, if someone was hit,
there was still that adherence
to a middle distance.
What Kirby would do
is subvert that incredibly.
He would have close-ups,
points of view.
Jack had drawn for DC Comics.
They kept telling him,
"Don't draw like that.
Draw more like the serious guys."
Stan recognized that Jack
was exaggerating for a purpose,
and he lets Jack soar.
Nobody could draw
the way Jack drew.
It was incredible
watching him work.
They were pushing each other
to get to new creative places
that nobody'd gone to before.
When I first came up with
the idea for Spider-Man,
it was natural for me
to want Jack Kirby to draw him,
but after Jack had done a few pages,
Peter Parker looked too heroic.
I think Jack
was so used to drawing
handsome heroic characters,
so I gave the book to Steve Ditko,
who I felt
could draw the character
looking a little less like a superhero.
Steve Ditko, he wasn't interested
in the violent action so much.
He emphasized the human
aspects of things.
That's why he was so good
at people's expressions
and their attitudes.
Peter Parker is this wimpy kid
who, you know,
has real-world problems,
and, and... those...
those don't go away
because you get bit
by the radioactive spider
and, you know, suddenly become
this... this superhero.
I think, uh... I think...
it's just a great dichotomy,
and always has been.
They inserted human foibles
and phobias and weaknesses.
His first thought isn't, "I'm gonna
change the world and be a do-gooder."
His first thought is,
"I'm gonna cash in."
Isn't that how most people
would first think,
and they created
an amazing morality tale
by showing the thug go by
when he could have
made a difference,
and this ends up
leading to the death
of an important person in his life.
They showed a moral consequence
in a way that had real weight
that people could relate to.
Peter Parker,
his personal life,
that was the star of the book,
and even when he did have
the costume,
it was still Peter Parker that you
were identifying with in that costume.
That was a big change.
Marvel Comics, at that time,
had created so many
revolutionary characters,
but they had one problem,
which was their distribution.
In the 1950s, in order to survive,
Marvel signed a really bad deal
with DC's parent company,
which now gave them the power
to suppress distribution.
They had
problems with distribution,
and I think DC was very specific
about making sure
that they had problems.
There were only a handful
of drugstores
that you could actually find
their comic books in.
And this is the time where the war
between DC and Marvel really started.
Through the '40s and '50s,
DC was the 900-pound gorilla
in the room,
and so for Marvel to kind of figure out
a new way of doing something,
it was obviously a big deal.
When I worked at DC in the '60s,
they just couldn't understand it at all.
"How could these things
possibly be selling?"
I mean, I remember being
in a meeting once
where somebody was holding up
a Spider-Man.
He was saying, "They have this kid
talking to his aunt for two pages."
He says, "The readers are going
to be bored out of their minds."
He kept looking for the gimmick.
DC definitely knew
that Marvel was a threat,
and they definitely
suppressed their distribution.
Stan really had to find new ways,
almost grass-root campaigns,
in order to really bring up the
popularity of his characters.
I started writing a column
called "Stan's Soapbox"
just so that the fans
would get to know me,
and get to know what's happening
at the Marvel bullpen,
as I referred to it, and I
tried to make the credits funny.
For instance, "Drawn by
Jack Kirby with great gusto"
and "Leaded by Art Simek
with a scratchy pen point,"
anything we could do
to make the readers feel
they knew us, and liked us,
and we started getting
a lot of fan mail,
and even then I had fun with it.
A key difference, if you wrote
to... a letter in, as I did,
to the DC Comics, you
wrote to "Dear Editor."
If you wrote to the Marvel books,
you wrote to "Dear Stan and Jack."
They were on a first-name basis
with you automatically,
even though I was a teenager,
and they were adults.
"Hey, Stan, how've ya been?
Read this story, that story,
boy, it was terrific.
From your pal, So-and-So."
We're a bunch of friends
talkin' to each other.
We're not stiff, dull people.
That kind of gave a forum,
a kind of a pre-Internet community,
where, you know,
kids from different towns
could connect with each other.
They used to print the
addresses, and kids would
then write to each other
and start fan clubs.
The Merry Marvel Marching Society.
It was a club.
I actually... I think I still
have my little stickers for it.
# You'll belong, you'll belong
you'll belong, you'll belong #
# To the Merry Marvel
Marching Society... #
After a while,
I would get
the kind of letters you'd get
from a classmate in college
whom you hadn't seen for a while,
and he was just kidding around
with you in the mail.
Marvel definitely, they hit something,
you know, where they were...
they became popular
with college kids.
I think the reason a
lot of these characters caught on
was because it was written
at a much higher understanding,
rather than just the very flat, childish
superhero comics that went before,
and also
you've got to credit people
like Kirby and Steve Ditko and
their art for being so cosmic,
and so out there, that, at
that time, it just fit in
perfectly with the counterculture
and the hippie movement.
The University of California's
humor magazine, The Pelican,
recently called Marvel Comics
"the greatest revolution
in literature on campus
since the fold-out nude,"
but I don't understand.
Well, there is a little revolution
that we like to think that we've started.
We're offbeat enough to appeal
to the college crowd, to
the so-called "in" crowd.
As a matter of fact, Esquire, a few
issues back, referred to the 28 people
who were most important to those
on campus, and among the 28,
which consisted of politicians
and celebrities and so forth,
they had The Hulk
and Spider-Man,
two of our ever-loving characters.
Marvel came in and
disrupted with kind of a new voice,
where they took
all this ancient mythology
and reiterated it into today's world.
I think that a lot of it
had to do with the times.
Marvel's approach
to creating these neurotic,
relatable superheroes
was riding right alongside
rock 'n' roll
becoming a real force.
None of this stuff
happened in a vacuum.
Pink Floyd using Dr. Strange,
that's disseminating
Marvel Comics into the culture,
and having them take hold
beyond your core audience,
and for a lot of us
who loved comic books,
having somebody reference
something you know,
you're like, "Oh, my god...
A, you're cool,
B, I know that as well,
and C, it's great that you
brought it into this thing."
There was Peter Fonda calling himself
Captain America in Easy Rider...
This here is Captain America.
What is the story of Captain America?
- What kind of a cat is he?
- Well, we revived him
from the so-called
Golden Age of comics.
He's become satirical
because we play him straight.
It must have been
really cool for Jack Kirby
to bring back Captain America
and really do his character
in a whole new way.
He became kind of
this disillusioned American.
We see this growing ambition,
in both Stan Lee and Jack Kirby,
that it becomes almost
a social criticism.
X-Men were created in the '60s
in a time of civil rights,
uh, turmoil and awareness.
I mean, most of all, The
X-Men is about tolerance
and not pushing away outsiders.
One of the things I've
always been against is bigotry,
and The X-Men, fans have
told me that that series
is one of the greatest battles
against bigotry
that I could have written.
You can see
how the civil rights movement
influenced some of those early X-Men.
You've got senators,
like, speaking out
against these people
who aren't like you and I,
these giant robots
called the Sentinels.
This story came out shortly
after there were armed guards
assaulting black people.
It's hard to not see the parallels.
Our fan mail,
about one-third of it,
very seriously, would be
from college kids who'd say,
"I'm doing a dissertation about
this, a doctorial thesis about this,
and Stan, really, what was
behind thus-and-such happening?"
I'd probably visited
more college campuses
than any living being.
As the decade progressed,
Stan came into inventing himself
as much as he would invent
any other character.
He started as this bald,
nebbishy guy,
and he ended the decade
this larger-than-life figure
that went around college
campuses exclaiming all of these
ridiculous alliterative things.
Life is so insane
that if you try to do anything
that is the way things
would be in real life,
it has to come across like satire,
so all of a sudden
I learned that I'm a satirist.
In a lot of ways,
Stan's life became Stan's art,
and him taking center stage
may not sit as well
with somebody like Jack Kirby,
who regards, "Hey, I'm
doing the real work here."
Jack was known and
respected within the community,
and by hard-core
comic book aficionados,
but, you know, if you go
to the average person and say,
"Who's Jack Kirby?"
they might be like, "I don't know."
If you say, "Who's Stan Lee?" like,
"Oh, Spider-Man, Marvel Comics."
This was the problem
in Stan and Jack's relationship
in a big, bad way.
Initially, Stan and Jack
worked really closely together
to create
all of the Marvel universe,
but as Stan became
more and more busy
with Bullpen Bulletin
and also Stan's Soapbox,
his time was really stretched
out, and so a new method
of how he would write
and create comics was born.
The Marvel method was a new way of
doing comics that they developed,
which essentially
transferred a lot of work
that was traditionally the
writer's to the artist.
So I'd say, "I'll tell you
what the plot is.
You just go home
and draw anything,
and I'll put the dialogue
and the captions
on your artwork."
In that way, I was able to keep
a lot of artists busy at once.
They would draw anything.
I never knew what to expect. Sometimes,
I didn't even recognize the story.
It was different
than what I had told them.
I think that in
the Stan-and-Jack relationship,
it can't be underestimated
that Stan's dialogue
and spokesmanship
helped define what Marvel was,
but the Marvel method
for the first time
put artists in the driver's seat
of the storytelling process
of comics.
The Galactus trilogy
that is fondly regarded
as a turning point in comics
was imagined almost
wholecloth by Jack Kirby.
I had given Jack the plot,
and he drew it magnificently,
as he always did,
but towards the end
of the story,
I saw that he had put a guy
on a flying surfboard,
and I said, "Hey, I didn't
put that in the story. Who's that?"
and Jack said, "I figured a
guy like Galactus ought to have
a herald who goes ahead of him
to find those planets,"
and I thought
that was a wonderful idea.
"Let's call him the Silver Surfer,
and we'll make
a regular character,
we'll make a star out of him."
So he was really a joint creation
of Jack's and mine.
In terms of a creative
team, they were co-creators.
They were amazing
when they worked together,
but when it came
to the public eye,
that's where
they really diverged.
Jack had a weird,
quirky way of talking,
especially when you put him
on camera.
He was terrible in front of a camera.
It's becoming American folklore,
and, of course, uh,
I can foresee uh,
a lot more, uh, valid,
uh, roads ahead for comics.
His interviews and everything,
he was a lot more shy
and not as outspoken
as Stan Lee,
which in the long term,
would hurt him.
By the end of that time,
Jack has gotten lost
in Stan's shadow.
One of the big
flashpoints was, uh,
an article in the New
York Herald Tribune...
which basically portrayed Stan Lee
as, you know, kind of
the genius behind everything,
and was... was gently mocking
of Jack Kirby's demeanor.
The article
referred to him as looking like
an "assistant manager
in a girdle factory,
with a cheap cigar,
a cheap suit, and dark eyes,"
and really just saying only that,
while dedicating so much
of the article to Stan.
And Steve Ditko,
who was probably
one of the seminal creators
at Marvel Comics at the time,
was not even mentioned
in the article at all.
For Ditko, that article
really aggravated the tension
that they already had
behind the scenes.
They already had huge creative
differences regarding Spider-Man.
By the time I was there,
Steve Ditko, you know, never
came by the office, except for
a couple of minutes to drop something
off, because Stan had decided
that there was just no sense
in the two of them speaking.
That was
the weirdest thing of all.
It was two people doing their
second-most successful
book at that time,
they had been
not speaking to each other
for several months already.
Steve Ditko's story and
Jack Kirby's story are very similar
in that they both assumed
really creative control
of the comics
that they were drawing,
stories that were credited
solely to Stan Lee, in many cases.
Clearly, if you had a comic
that said, "Written by Stan Lee
and drawn by Jack Kirby,"
that was giving Stan
an awful lot of the credit
for what the artist was doing.
Ditko got out because he just
couldn't work like that anymore.
Jack kept at it, believing
that at some point, someone
would recognize that he was
not just filling pages up
with somebody else's ideas,
and somehow that didn't happen.
For years, I mean,
Jack Kirby didn't care
that, you know,
that he wasn't being listed
as a writer.
Later on, when something becomes
successful, then everybody starts saying,
"Well, you know, this percentage of it's mine."
"That percentage of it's mine."
With great power comes
great responsibility,
and with money
comes great problems.
I do think it is a huge shame
what happened between
Stan and Jack's relationship.
One of the great partnerships
in comics history
dissolved into one of the
greatest feuds in comics history.
When did I first
become aware of Jack Kirby?
It's sort of like saying,
"When did you first recognize
that when the sun came up
in the morning,
it got brighter," you know?
It's that, it was, like,
that level of, like...
He was, to me, Marvel,
and to see the way he was
treated, it actually just hurts.
So, by the late '60s,
Marvel Comics was a hit,
but Jack Kirby wasn't happy.
It wasn't just about credit,
it was also about the money.
When the sales went up,
their paychecks didn't go up,
and their security
at the company didn't go up.
Jack used to use the term
"chained to the board."
"I was chained to the board
all that time,"
and he worked in a cellar,
which he referred to as
"the dungeon."
They didn't let these people
have lawyers.
When Jack was given a contract,
he had to just sign it in the office.
He said to them, "Well, I want
to show this to my lawyer."
They said, "We don't let
lawyers look at our stuff."
The problem there is,
Ditko, like Kirby,
was work for hire.
On the day that they decide
they don't need you anymore,
"See ya."
On the day
that they make something
out of The Fantastic Four,
you don't get anything.
Around '65, '66,
when they started licensing
a lot of the intellectual property,
and I think
that the animated series
was a real kick in the teeth.
Those steel doors behind us,
they're closing.
They're trying to lock us in.
We can't let that happen.
- Quicksilver, it's time for your speed.
- Too late.
Because the comic books were
so lively, the producers thought,
"Let's just use the artwork
from the comic book pages
and kind of move those around."
No, no! No, wait!
There are more behind me.
When he said, "Jeez, shouldn't I get
some extra compensation for this?"
it was kind of like, "Just shut up,
and go back to drawing stuff."
The publisher wants it all.
The creative people
are on a certain plane,
and the publisher
is on a certain plane.
He lives with his lawyers
and accountants,
and he says, "Well, let's make...
Let's get toys out of this.
Let's get sweaters out of this."
You know, and it's very understandable
it might have made him bitter.
I think sometimes it got misplaced
against Stan to the extent that...
as if Stan was his oppressor
more than, say, the publisher
or something, but it's very hard.
He saw Stan advancing
and so forth,
and being considered the prime
mover of the Marvel universe.
Stan Lee found a
way to be inseparable from Marvel
while not actually owning Marvel.
Marvel was always controlled
by other corporations,
but he found a way
to be that key man
that was inseparable from
what the Marvel brand was.
It was his own canniness,
it was his own street smarts,
it was his own business acumen,
and it was also the character
that he made up.
And unfortunately,
the other people who
would buy the companies and
trade them back and forth
never valued Jack
as they should have.
I guess you don't
have a legal obligation to them,
so where does the moral
obligation come in?
If somebody gave you their
sweat and blood for decades,
gave you all these characters
you're exploiting,
like, just... so what?
Throw them a few crumbs just to say
"thank you," not "[bleep] you."
He created all of
these revolutionary characters,
and at a certain point,
Jack had had enough,
and he literally just walked up,
threw down the towel,
and he just quit.
Why did Kirby leave Marvel?
I'm going to be very honest with you.
I don't know.
I was not... I don't believe
I was there at the time.
I think I was in Europe
or somewhere,
and I had heard he had left,
and nobody ever gave me an actual
reason that I could live with.
It was the same thing with
Steve Ditko when he left one day.
To this day,
I don't know why he left.
Things happen.
I always think of it
as the "Ub Iwerks syndrome."
You know Ub Iwerks?
Ub Iwerks was Walt Disney's, you know,
his second-in-command
in all the areas that...
He's the guy
who probably actually drew
more of Mickey Mouse, and
knew more about the animation,
but Ub Iwerks got to feeling
unappreciated after a few years.
He went off, and he founded his
own animation studio. It failed.
Kirby went to DC,
and he did a series of stories
that are kind of known
as The New Gods.
At the time, there was a lot of criticism
of the storytelling and the dialogue.
You know, everyone loved the
art, but it wasn't Stan Lee.
The thing about Kirby
is he couldn't write.
We found out for sure.
He had a terrible ear for dialogue.
Just, you know, off-putting,
clanky dialogue.
And then he parodied Stan
as Funky Flashman
in a couple of his books,
kind of a glib salesman-type guy,
makin' fun of Stan's persona.
Stan and I
had an argument one time.
I felt Jack Kirby was very...
was mistreated at the company.
He was basically telling me,
"Well, yeah, but it...
I wasn't the one who did it,"
and I said, "Did you ever see
one of those Dean Martin
and Jerry Lewis movies?"
I said, "There's always a scene
in those movies
where Dean Martin says to somebody,
"Hey, you can't do that to my pal."
I said, "Stan, I wish
you'd said that more often,"
and he didn't speak to me
for a long time after that.
These two middle-aged men
basically started
from almost desperation,
and created all these popular
and revolutionary characters.
Unfortunately, along the way,
their relationship fell apart.
The tension that they had
behind the scenes
really put all their good work
into jeopardy.
I think, despite later conflicts,
I think there was a fondness
that they had for each other.
Needless to say, a great synergy
in terms of the creativity.
It was on his birthday,
Jack Kirby was doing
an interview on the radio,
and one of the callers was Stan Lee.
It'd be interesting to know whether or
not Galactus's exit speech in FF #50
was an example of Jack's
dialogue or Stan's, but you...
Well, I'll say this.
Every word of dialogue
in those scripts was mine.
I can tell you that
I wrote a few lines myself
- above every panel that I...
- Yes, I've seen those...
They weren't
printed in the book!
All right, look, both of you...
Hey, kids...
I really think...
and look, Jack, nobody has
more respect for you
than I do, and you know that,
but I don't think you ever felt
that the dialogue
was that important,
and I think you felt,
"Well, it doesn't matter.
Anybody can put the dialogue in.
It's what I'm drawing that matters,"
and maybe you're right.
I don't agree with it,
but maybe you're right.
You feel like you're
intruding on a heavy talk
between an ex-husband
and an ex-wife or something,
and the semi-reconciliation
is playing out in real time.
You know, Jack, you were
talking earlier about your drawing,
and people sometimes
criticized your figures.
I always felt that the most important
thing about your drawings,
I remember when I was a kid,
and I first saw Captain America,
it wasn't the correctness
of the anatomy,
but it was the emotion
that you put in.
Nobody could convey emotion
and drama the way you could,
and nobody could ever
draw a hero like you could,
and I think that's something
you can be very proud of,
- and I'm proud of you for it.
- I have to thank you for,
uh, helping me to keep
that style, Stanley,
and, uh,
whatever we did together,
we, uh, we got sales
for Marvel, and I...
I think it was more than that, Jack.
We certainly got the sales,
but whatever we did together,
and no matter who did what,
and I guess that's something
that'll be argued forever,
but I think there was
some slight magic
that came into effect
when we worked together,
and I am very happy that
we've had that experience.
Well, I was never sorry for it, Stanley.
It was a great experience for me.
It's easy to cast
real people and human decisions
with the brush of intention,
and with the brush of,
you know, heroes and villains,
but it really just came down to
these were people
with all of the messiness
of human dynamics.
They were working in the underclass
of the publishing business.
There wasn't anything
that would lead you to think
that these guys
are gonna change the world
with what's goin' on
inside their heads.
It was Marvel's 25th anniversary,
and I invited him,
and he came,
and Roz, his wife, came.
Stan and I were standing in the
back of the room when they came in.
Stan had a glass of wine,
and you know how Stan talks,
he's waving his hands around
all the time.
He waves his hand,
slams it against a pillar,
hand is slashed, bleeding.
He gets a handkerchief out.
He said, "Oh, my god, oh, my god."
And I said, "There's Jack!"
so I run over to Jack and Roz,
and I bring them over to Stan,
and here's Stan, like this,
and Jack sticks out his hand,
and Stan goes...
And he shakes his hand,
and then he's wiping
the blood off Jack's hand,
and they talk for a while,
and they were friends.
They were talking about
how great it used to be,
and it was fun, you know, and
all the good times they had.
And then Stan said, "You know,
I don't care who gets credit.
I don't care who owns it."
He says, "I just want to do
one more time with you,
one more job,"
and Roz said, "Forget it,"
and dragged Jack away.
So it didn't happen.
While they remained cordial,
unfortunately, they never
worked together again
before Kirby passed away.
There's a few
different people that can play the
Moses role in the history of comics,
and Jack Kirby's one of them.
He was able to lead us
to this promised land of story,
but he didn't get to enjoy it himself.
I think when you look at people
that have come up
from that environment,
creators negotiating for a
fairer piece of what they create
in the way that Rob Liefeld
gets a piece
of every piece of Deadpool,
whether it's Robert Kirkman
controlling his own destiny
creating something like
The Walking Dead,
they were informed by the fact
that Jack Kirby didn't receive that.
And it was those stories
that made me go into my career
with my eyes wide open, of going,
"If they can do it to Jack Kirby,
they can do it to anybody."
They called him the King,
rightfully so,
and if there was
a bigger word than that,
- I'd give it to him.
- I don't think anybody
was as much a master of the art
as Jack was.
He was just the greatest.
In fact, I'm the guy
who gave him the nickname
Jack "King" Kirby.
He was the king of the artists
to me.
My name isn't Stan Lee.
It's Stanley Liebert.
Someday I'm going
to write the great American novel,
and I don't want to use this name
that's going to be
so famous someday,
use it on comics.
Stan Lee.
It's funny to think
maybe in an alternate universe,
Stan did write
the great American novel,
it flopped, and he was
never heard from again.
Stan did create something
akin to the great American novel
by creating
this huge Marvel universe,
and by "creating," I mean
being part of something
that all these other people
were involved in
to help shape it into what it is.
I worked with Steve Ditko,
and I worked with Jack,
and it was very clear
that Stan more than
pulled his weight.
He was the glue
that held it all together.
He was conducting the orchestra.
I don't think
he took too much credit.
I think he created
the whole thing. Sorry.
Obviously, he could not have
done it without Jack Kirby
or Ditko, or the other artists,
but, you know, certainly without
Stan Lee, no Marvel Comics.
He's got, like,
a spark of youthful energy to him,
and, and, and there's
a curiosity inside of him
that doesn't seem to die out,
and I think that that is
the true key to long life,
and he's just
the perfect archetype for that.
It's really incredible
when you think through
what Stan Lee and Jack Kirby
have accomplished.
X-Men, and The Hulk,
and The Avengers,
they are our biggest stories
of today.
You know, they're stories
about outsiders,
and I think that Stan Lee
and Jack Kirby,
they were just like them.
They were different,
they were ostracized.
They didn't fit into society.
Stan Lee and Jack Kirby
are the Lennon and McCartney
of Marvel Comics,
and just like The Beatles,
eons from now,
people will still be talking
about these characters
and the people who created them,
akin on the same level.
They're the gods
who created the gods.
I love them all.
I love Thor, I love The Hulk,
I love Daredevil,
The X-Men,
the Avengers, Spider-Man,
The Fantastic Four, Dr. Strange,
The Black Panther...
To me, they're all part of a family.
I tried to put them all
in the same world
so that they could meet
and have adventures together,
a universe of characters
that would entertain
readers who were young
and readers who were old,
and if I've succeeded in that,
then I'm very happy.
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~