sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
Wonder Woman is awesome.
What I cared about the most
was trying to make a movie
true to the character
that has lasted for 75 years
for a reason.
But, for many years, I've been saying
"There is a massive following
of Wonder Woman,"
and it was baffling to me
that she, the biggest
female superhero in history,
was not on-screen.
We think today of
seeing an action heroine
in a movie as a big risk.
But can you imagine, back in 1941,
at the start of World War II,
how risky it was
to be encouraging women
to be powerful?
It still astounds me that I never
thought to explore earlier,
"Well, who was it that made this
character? Why does she exist?"
When I learned
a little bit about the creators,
it made me love the comic
even more.
It definitely wasn't the conventional.
If you look
at the history of Wonder Woman,
especially in the '40s,
there was so much of these three
people put into that character.
Their life journey
inspired a comic book fantasy.
That had to have been pretty
spectacular for all three of them.
They created one of the most
iconic characters of our time.
But what strikes me is the
salaciousness of his personal life.
I know the real story...
and that stunned me.
I said, "Excuse me?"
_
Before she was
a box-office smash in 2017
and a television hit in the '70s,
Wonder Woman
was a comic book trailblazer
armed with a very unique weapon.
What the hell is this thing?
The Lasso of Hestia
compels you to reveal the truth.
From her earliest days, Wonder
Woman was a character built on truth.
But the irony is her origins
were all about lies and deception.
Cambridge, Massachusetts,
the 1920s...
it may seem an unlikely place
for the birth of the most iconic
female superhero ever...
...but this is where
Wonder Woman began.
In order to understand
how Wonder Woman has
withstood the test of time
and where she came from,
it's important to understand more
about the creator,
William Moulton Marston,
a progressive psychologist,
and the two women behind him.
The more I read about Marston,
the more I liked him, actually.
I thought
he was super interesting.
And he was
a valiant free-thinker.
These are the things
that I really adore.
And he was really into girl power.
Marston met the woman
who would become his wife
when they were very young,
and William Moulton Marston
wouldn't have been anywhere
near the success he was
without Elizabeth Holloway.
Every step of the way,
she was the strength behind him.
This is a guy
who had some sexual proclivities
that would have been considered
scandalous in the day,
certainly considered scandalous now,
who had the good fortune
of marrying a woman
who understood him,
and stood by him,
and saw that they could
be great together.
William and Elizabeth
had both been very heavily
involved in the suffrage movement.
They wanted women
to have the right to vote.
I think that he was, obviously,
a very forward-thinking,
feminist mind,
and he was also
very interested in truth.
Those two things are fascinating
because it's got
everything to do with the
hero that has been created
and everything to do
with what equality takes.
Elizabeth routinely
collaborated with William
on his psychology career,
and nearly 20 years before
the creation of Wonder Woman,
she also inspired
his first notable success.
Elizabeth says to Bill one day,
"You know, I kind of notice
when we girls get excited,
our... our pulse starts racing,
our hearts start beating."
And William says, "Oh, so your emotions
somehow trigger something else?"
He became convinced
that blood pressure could be a way
to tell whether
a person was lying or not,
so he created
the systolic blood pressure test
that is what we now think of
as one of the major elements of
polygraph, or lie detector tests.
By 1925, William is
building an impressive academic career,
and is a professor at Tufts University.
He is a professor
of Experimental Psychology,
and he's a hot professor
on campus, very popular,
and in one of his classes
is a very interesting young woman,
and her name is Olive.
There is something I'd like you
to consider... really think about.
Are you a normal person?
Probably for the most part, you are.
But your biggest fears,
deepest desires,
you keep to yourself,
hidden away... don't you?
Olive Byrne was my grandmother,
and I remember speaking with her,
especially about the time where
we were going off to college,
and she always wanted us
to go to Tufts.
She loved the school.
But aside from the fun
and the parties,
that's where she met William Marston.
However... let me summarize,
as I'm out of time.
I've found people illustrate
their emotions in four ways:
dominance...
inducement...
submission...
and compliance.
And we will focus
on these emotions next class.
Thank you.
That was bold.
Encouraging to hear
from a young lady.
Olive. Olive Byrne.
William Marston.
- If you like, I can show you more.
- Of what?
Of your four emotions.
When she was
at Tufts University,
Olive Byrne introduced Marston
to some of the strange
and unusual practices
that were going on at her sorority.
And anybody
who's been in college
and in a sorority
or a fraternity knows,
there's some strange stuff
that happens.
No, I didn't think so.
You broke each
and every one of them today.
Sit down in the line.
Now!
She introduces him
to these "baby parties"
at her sorority,
where he becomes fascinated with,
you know, these sorority girls
acting like babies
as part of the party.
You were seen on campus
without your bottle.
Bad girl!
This eventually made
it into the pages of Wonder Woman,
where Wonder Woman's
friend Etta Candy
and the sorority girls
of the Holiday College
engage in a baby party.
It was very strange material.
Who's next?
So at this point,
Olive became Dr. Marston's
assistant in his work.
She's fascinated in this work
with the lie detector,
but she's very, very, uh...
unconventional.
She's spontaneous.
She's very alluring.
And then what happens?
You have the professor falling
in love with his student,
and she certainly has fallen
in love with the professor.
They became linked,
both professionally and romantically.
Olive was publicly portrayed
as Marston's assistant,
but really, she was his mistress.
And as we know, younger
people sometimes have more
progressive ideas, and they
might bring things to the table
that even super-progressive
thinkers might not think of,
and so Olive might have
opened some eyes
and opened some doors
in that relationship.
Marston was interested in BDSM.
He was interested
because he had a kink,
because bondage and submission
was sexually exciting to him.
And Marston had
fallen in love with Olive.
Elizabeth saw this.
Had they been found out,
it could've been disastrous
for his career, for everything.
It could have ruined him.
Olive and William,
their relationship grew,
and it was taboo.
It just didn't happen.
But then, as odd as it was,
William Marston
spoke with Elizabeth and said,
"I've fallen in love with her,
and I want her to move in with us."
This is the 1920s, realize.
It was not the time for
any progressive psychologist
to publicly have a wife and
a mistress that all lived together.
It was not only unheard of,
it was possibly dangerous.
Elizabeth Marston
has been happily married
to William for over 10 years,
but now she has
a difficult decision to make.
William fell head over
heels in love with Olive Byrne,
and told Elizabeth Marston
that he wanted her to live with them.
If having another woman
live in the house
is what's going to
make you happy, then...
I'm okay with it.
The story I heard
was that after some time,
Elizabeth told William Marston
that she wanted him to be happy,
and soon after that,
Olive moved in.
To allow the man that she loves
to express love for another woman,
she had to be
a very strong woman to do that.
I've heard inklings of this, uh...
bohemian-like, 1930s figure
who lived, you know,
'70s-style Three's Company
with two broads.
There was an open-mindedness to it,
and if you look
a little bit deeper, you know,
following the conventional
wisdom of what society
is pushing on you
may not necessarily be the route.
Listen, we all have lives,
complicated lives.
They seemed to be living
a really loving, beautiful life,
which was embracing of truth
and in celebration of equality.
Whether there's two of them
or three of them
- is not really the point.
- The trio of them,
the ménage à trois,
the household of three
had to go to great lengths
sometimes to keep the views
of the outside world from
intruding on their family.
We do know
there are deceptions involved
when they would list her
in one census as a cousin,
another census
as a different relative.
It's just so awesome
that they were so not beholden
to society's morals.
They were so, um... honest
about the dynamic
between the three of them.
They didn't let society's norms
define them or their work,
because they were obviously
great partners intellectually.
In 1928,
William is working on his book,
Emotions of Normal People.
He has the lie detection thing,
which everybody talks about,
but there's this D.I.S.C. theory...
"D.I.S.C." for "dominance, inducement,
submission, compliance."
And Olive legitimately
was his research assistant.
Do you know what it became
for William Marston?
I absolutely believe it,
their home became a living
laboratory of human emotions,
and how they interacted,
and behavior...
of jealousy,
of control, of dominance.
Olive and Dr. Marston
are doing some very odd work
with the reactions of women,
to see how they would respond
to these emotional scenes.
From what I've studied,
from what I've read from the text,
is that Marston believed
women were "love leaders,"
and he truly believed
in this idea of loving submission,
which is to say, if men were
to give themselves over entirely
to the power of women,
they would be less destructive people.
I mean, the bondage
is very much related
to his ideas about feminism,
and that kind of happens
throughout the comics,
where Wonder Woman is...
tied up with her own rope,
and then has to obey,
but then she gets power back,
and she forces
other people to obey.
Marston, in his later work,
says not only should women
be emotional leaders,
they should be leaders
in a political, global sense...
that they're better suited
to lead the world as a whole,
and he actually predicts
that a matriarchal
revolution will come about
in the next 100 years.
In the 1930s, the
Marston trio start a family.
At one point, Elizabeth and Olive
are even pregnant at the same time.
Elizabeth gives birth to two children,
Pete and Olive Ann.
So does Olive,
to Byrne and Donn.
But as their family grows,
so does their deception.
Olive creates a husband
by the name of
William Kendall Richards,
and these children
were the sons of this man,
and that he had died.
From all the research I have done,
he never existed.
There was no such person.
But it protected Bill,
it protected Olive and the sons,
so it was done strategically
to make life work.
So the direct result
of having this whole facade
and a fictitious name,
Donn, who's my father,
was teased a lot.
He would walk home from school
and he would be taunted by others,
and he was called one of
the bastard Marston children.
You know, it bothered him.
It bothered him a lot.
He was not a happy person
growing up.
And when the boys were young,
William Marston officially
adopted the children...
but he was their father anyway.
The Marstons
are mostly successful
in keeping their unusual
home life a secret.
But rumors abound
that William carried on
an affair with a student,
and his teaching career vanishes.
Meanwhile, his greatest claim
to fame, the lie detector,
is largely discredited,
and by the late '30s,
Marston's career is at rock-bottom.
Elizabeth is the breadwinner.
Olive's raising the kids.
He's got time to explore
his variety of huckster ideas.
He writes a novel.
He gets work with a film company.
There's a Gillette razor ad
where he hooks someone up
to a lie detector,
and so he's got his fingers
in a lot of pots,
none of them really stickin'.
As Marston struggles
to reverse his fortunes,
the world is on the brink of war.
Hitler is terrorizing Europe...
and the fears are felt in America,
where a new type of hero
is about to come to the rescue.
DC Comics debuts Superman in 1938.
Superman's an instant hit,
and it kind of explodes from there.
You get Batman,
you get Captain America,
Captain Marvel.
Kids are readin' them,
millions a month.
But, um, the backlash
is near instantaneous.
The rebellious nature
of the heroes,
the crime and violence
in some of the stories,
were starting
to concern some people.
The quick popularity of comic
books, it's an easy scapegoat.
The emotional impact of
something they read in a comic book
may be much the same as
a real-life situation they witness.
The overnight
popularity of Superman
has made publisher
Max Gaines a rich man.
But the public backlash
against comics
is threatening to take away
his main audience... children.
It was a Sunday
when Olive and Bill started saying,
"God, it's really quiet in this house.
It's too quiet."
And they realized
the kids were reading comics.
So Bill became fascinated,
and he spent a year studying comics
to understand how it was written,
what were the visuals.
It was not a mistake.
It was strategic.
So William Marston
had Olive write an interview
with him about comics.
They very carefully
construct this interview
between, you know,
a Family Circle writer
who's not presented as a member
of his household on her byline.
She's just listed as "Olive Richard."
That was her pen name.
They constructed this
in order to get the attention
of the comic book company.
Okay, this is how it goes...
I travel to the famed psychologist
Dr. Marston's home for a visit.
Dr. Marston is
approachable and intelligent
- and open with me.
- That's good.
I ask him, "Do you think
comics are good for children?"
And he answers, "Yes. Superman
is certainly the soundest of all.
Mr. Gaines at All Stars Publishing
has done a good job in that..."
Yeah, but what about other comics?
Some of them are filled with torture.
Oh... Unfortunately, that is true,
but when the heroine is tied up...
...the reader is sure
that she will be saved just in time.
So the reader isn't able
to enjoy suffering.
How about a heroine
who doesn't need to be saved?
There's a Superman,
why not a Superwoman?
According to William's
son Pete, it was Elizabeth who said,
"You'd better make that
new character a Superwoman."
William actually named Gaines
in the publication.
So of course,
this reaches Gaines' desk,
and he's very excited
to see his name in there.
"Oh, we need to bring on
this guy as a consultant."
William's plan works.
And once he has his foot in
the door, he makes the pitch
that he's been waiting
a lifetime for.
- A woman?
- Yes! A woman! Mr. Gaines...
It's not gonna work.
Every female pulp
and comic heroine has failed.
But they were just women.
They weren't superwomen.
They weren't superior to men.
Listen.
Let me create something
that has both...
a female superhero
with all the power of Superman,
but the allure
of a beautiful woman.
It'd double sales.
- Double?
- Comics are read by young boys, right?
- Yeah.
- Well, let's hit young girls.
I took a chance on Superman
when everyone else passed on him.
I'll take a chance on your
Wonder Woman, Dr. Marston.
William Marston
wanted to introduce
a strong female protagonist
into the world of comics,
and in 1941,
that's exactly what he did.
William Marston
gave her everything...
power, beauty,
great intelligence.
Wonder Woman
happens to be a woman,
but is a grand superhero for all.
She's a superhero.
She's the real deal.
Wonder Woman flips the paradigm
of how comic books have worked.
All of the successful superhero
comics at the time starred men,
and here's this woman
out there doing the same things
as good as, even better,
than the men do.
Throughout the next year,
she debuted in three different series
because she was
so immensely popular.
The sales figures on her books
went up and up and up,
from 2.5 million to 5 million
copies of her books.
Wonder Woman didn't
look like other superheroes,
and it wasn't written
like other comic books.
While other creators
told action-packed stories
that were pure entertainment
and escape,
Marston filled the pages
of Wonder Woman
with psychological theories
and ancient mythologies.
What's very unusual
about her is her mythic origins.
She's born to a virginal queen
of the Amazons,
and even the deity
that is her other parent,
Athena, is female...
and this is so feminist.
There's no other character in
comics whose creation is like that.
He creates this powerful
but very feminine woman,
following Elizabeth's suggestion
that that's what
the character should be.
The guy was a visionary,
as they all were, clearly.
They were visionaries, and they were
challenging what is
truth and what is love.
They knew they had an
opportunity to do a new superhero
that came out of
their view on feminism.
In the panels of Wonder
Woman, panel after panel,
you can find a blueprint
from their lives.
And Betty and Olive
were very involved
in the creation of Wonder Woman.
It wasn't just
that they were an inspiration.
They had input
to the development of stories.
I saw notes from Betty in Greek!
As she read the scripts,
she gave notes.
She studied Greek and
really fell in love with the language
and the poetry of Sappho,
and one of Wonder Woman's chief
expressions is "Suffering Sappho!"
I remember my grandmother,
she used to wear these
big bracelets on both arms,
and the story that we were told
was that the character Wonder
Woman was based off of her look,
and that's where they got the idea
of the bracelets for Wonder Woman.
Marston
and his wife are credited
with helping create
the lie detector test.
And Wonder Woman's magic lasso,
everyone knows, forced anyone
within its confines
to tell the absolute truth.
Wonder Woman
becomes a comic book sensation,
and William Marston finally has
the lucrative,
attention-grabbing success
he's been chasing his whole life.
But with the attention
came fierce criticism.
The problem came when the
critics started seeing a pattern,
which was that every other page,
Wonder Woman was getting tied up,
or chained up, or gagged,
or tied up, chained up, and gagged.
There was a lot of bondage
in Wonder Woman.
Getting tied up
is kind of an occupational hazard
of being a superhero.
But if you count up
how often people get tied up
in Captain Marvel,
it's about 3%.
If you look at how often
people are tied up
in the panels of Wonder
Woman comics, it's 27%.
It's a quarter of every book
in the Marston era.
If you look at those old comics
when Wonder Woman is tied up,
she's smiling,
she considers it a game.
The "Holiday Girls" were
having spanking parties.
It was kind of a bizarre fantasy world
in which submission
and bondage was fun.
These things
that he was doing in his
personal life has a lot to do
with how those dominance-
submission relationships
were presented in the comics.
I mean, it's kind of amazing
that they got published,
when you think about it.
There's lots of bondage.
There's lots of lesbian overtones.
There's real, sort of like,
ideological feminism,
which I think has also
made people uncomfortable.
Wonder Woman
has been a massive success.
But with critics attacking the comic
as sexually provocative
and inappropriate for children,
the future of Marston's creation
is in serious danger.
Take a look at these.
Max... you can't have
a female character
without setting off a few fantasies.
- Cut down on the chains by 75%.
- It's harmless.
Everybody likes a good fantasy, Max.
Wonder Woman has
five million readers.
It will affect sales, Max.
With growing
accusations that Marston's comic
is exposing children
to strange sexual perversions,
publisher Max Gaines
will have to make a choice...
change William Marston's mind,
or change the voice
behind Wonder Woman.
With pressure
mounting to do something
about his successful but controversial
female superhero,
Max Gaines does the unexpected.
He doubles down on Wonder Woman,
adding her to more
of his comic book series...
only this time, she won't be
written by William Marston.
One of her early appearances
as part of the Justice Society,
writer Gardner Fox doesn't quite
know what to do with the character,
so he decides to make her
the secretary of the team.
All the other male heroes
go about saving the day,
and Wonder Woman stays
behind to keep the notes.
It's a shame that her
position in the Justice League
ever became secretary.
Of course, that's... that's a bummer,
particularly when on paper, she's
the best fighter in the DC Universe.
There have been a lot of men
who have been able to step
into her shoes completely,
and then there are some that just can't.
It was very, very clear
that Marston and Elizabeth
had a vision for Wonder Woman
as this "love leader,"
this transformative goddess,
this powerhouse,
and the creators and editors
of the Justice Society
had a very different idea
about what a woman could be
and what a woman should be.
Match point!
Alice needs this to clinch it.
Marston's
response is to use the pages
of the Wonder Woman
comic that he does control
to make her even more of a feminist,
creating the segment
"Wonder Women of History"
with tennis champion Alice Marble.
Each segment
featured a "wonder woman,"
a real, live wonder woman...
Annie Oakley.
Florence Nightingale.
It had scientists.
It had women writers.
"Wonder Women of History"
really made kids realize
that there had been women
who had done amazing things,
and they had been human beings,
not beautiful, glamorous Amazons.
Like, how cool and refreshing
to have that message being
zoomed out to young girls,
that it's okay for you to be
a woman with... with morals
and friggin', you know,
some backbone to ya.
And so he was using
comic book as a medium
to send out his message
about feminism,
and that feminism was going
to be the path to peace.
Yanks, led by General Eisenhower,
gathered for a joyful
liberation celebration,
as shown by these Air Force pictures.
World War II ends.
Now, this is a good thing
that the war has ended.
His idea with Wonder Woman
from the beginning
was that this is the model
of the kind of leader
who will emerge and run the
world for us after the war.
But after the war,
the guys came back.
They wanted their jobs back,
and women were not so subtly
pushed back to the kitchen.
But he resisted that,
Marston resisted that.
His Wonder Woman
remained a feminist,
and the message was always
that "women can do anything."
While his creation,
Wonder Woman,
stubbornly remained
a strong, feminist force,
William Marston
would soon face his own crisis.
Hey, there's something
you're not telling me.
What's wrong?
I won't be able to keep up.
When this man finally
had the joy of true success,
this is what takes him down
is cancer.
I think it was a terrible,
terrible shock to them
that they were losing
him so young. So young.
Marston was really
dedicated to Wonder Woman,
and he continued to work
throughout his illness,
and was writing Wonder Woman
even until his last day.
May 1947, and one week
before his 54th birthday...
Bill dies.
I do remember
my father telling me
the day that his father died,
that it was hard on him.
Of course, at this time, he didn't
know that he was his father.
It was just
the man who adopted him.
Elizabeth said
that right before Bill died,
she promised him that she would
take care of Olive forever,
and so I think that was
kind of a promise to him,
but, um, you know, to each other,
'cause they were family.
Wonder Woman
was incredibly popular,
but Marston had been so identified
and his voice was so singular
in how Wonder Woman
was being created,
but without his voice to guide her,
what now?
William Marston
imagined Wonder Woman
as a revolutionary character...
but she was about to undergo
a drastic transformation.
With William
Marston's passing in 1947,
Wonder Woman faces an uncertain future.
In 1950s America, women are
expected to live a domestic life,
find a husband instead of a job,
start a family instead of a career.
Wonder Woman
changes with the times.
Suddenly, all she really wants
is to settle down with
her boyfriend, Steve Trevor.
Wonder Woman became
almost like a sappy love comic.
Her creator is gone,
and anyone who wants to
can take her over and change her.
When Marston passed away,
"Wonder Women of History"
was replaced.
The segment became wedding
customs around the world.
But I think
that she was at her worst,
poor Wonder Woman,
in the late '60s.
In 1968, Wonder
Woman lost her costume.
She lost her powers,
and she became
a boutique-owning
super-spy, and it destroyed
everything that fans loved
about Wonder Woman.
Wonder Woman was no longer
this sort of robust,
"Rosie the Riveter,"
world-changing
protofeminist "love leader."
She was a dress shop owner.
She was a romance-column writer.
A lot of the gender politics
disappeared, and that, I think,
would make Marston
turn over in his grave.
Every decade that passed,
people try to second-guess
William Marston's Wonder Woman.
We're afraid of her having
beauty at the same time
that she has strength,
or softness at that same time
that she has toughness.
There's really been
a struggle for her
to maintain all of those things
over the years.
As this new
Wonder Woman developed,
Elizabeth Marston and Olive Byrne
wrote letter after letter
with objections
to the ways in which
they were changing Wonder Woman,
but in the end,
DC owned the concept,
and Marston's voice
receded further and further
into the background.
I believe there is a love
between Elizabeth and Olive.
They raised children together.
The two of them lived together.
I know that we told everybody
they were sisters,
but obviously
there was much more.
I know that there's been stuff said,
I don't know if I should say this,
but I know there's been stuff said about
even if they had
a relationship together.
Olive's son Donn
questioned his mother
who his father was
for years and years,
and she never changed her story.
My dad threatened to sue her
to find out who his father was,
and eventually, Elizabeth
Marston came to my mom and dad
and said if Olive knew
that the secret was out
about who
her children's father was,
that she would take a vial
of morphine and kill herself,
and so Elizabeth Marston told
my mom the whole secret of, um...
William Marston
having these two women,
and who their father was, so...
I don't know if my dad
was ever at peace with that.
I mean, I think that he assumed
that that's probably what it was,
but I think
all the secrets and the lies,
you know, was hard on him.
By the early '70s,
feminism was on the rise.
We're supposed to dig
that we're sexual objects,
and we don't want to be
sexual objects anymore.
Women had to say,
"This is wrong.
We cannot be
discriminated against."
They had to make noise.
The majority of the people
in this country
support the Equal Rights Amendment.
We had all read
Wonder Woman as girls.
Gloria Steinem talks a lot
about that, and she talks about
how they felt they had
to rescue Wonder Woman
from what
was being done to her.
The new domesticated
Wonder Woman of the early '70s
had become one of DC's
worst-selling comics.
But women who grew up with her
longed to see Wonder Woman
return to her feminist roots.
We had gotten the rights to publish
one of the original stories
of Wonder Woman
in our Volume One, Number One
issue in July 1972,
which was an election year,
and Marston had a comic
that had "Wonder Woman
for President" on it.
It was just such a perfect cover.
So you had these feminists
taking a character who was
created as a feminist icon,
and putting her on the cover
of a major magazine
that was being marketed to women
and feminists across the nation.
The feminist message was
equality and peace and strength,
and William Marston's Wonder
Woman represented all of that.
With Ms. magazine
bringing Wonder Woman
back into the spotlight,
DC Comics
gives Diana Prince back
her super-abilities and her costume,
setting the stage
for Wonder Woman
to make her biggest conquest yet...
Wonder Woman's comeback
started with Gloria Steinem
and Ms. magazine,
but in 1975, a television series
would catapult her to new heights.
And for a new generation
of fans,
Lynda Carter would
transform Wonder Woman
from a superhero into an icon.
Being a young actress,
you could be a secretary,
or a waitress, or a stripper,
or some little part, or
whatever, but certainly,
they didn't think a woman
could hold a television show.
Star-spangled bathing suit,
raven-haired beauty, the
lasso, all of it...
like, the fabulousness
of Wonder Woman...
it was that moment
and that actress
and that embodiment
of the character
that turned her into a visual
and pop culture icon.
I was, like, mesmerized
by how damn beautiful she
was in those hot pants,
spinning, like...
"How do you get that figure?"
I was five, I think,
when the show came out,
and it had a huge effect on me.
I found that the Lynda Carter
series was very, very true
to the spirit of the original run
of William Marston's
Wonder Woman.
I got quite a bit
of early blowback.
From the networks, I got
"Oh, there's too many
feminist messages."
And then from the feminists,
I got "Wonder Woman
wasn't feminist enough."
You know?
It's like...
What a country this is.
After a successful run
on television in the '70s,
Wonder Woman
would continue to evolve
in the pages of DC Comics
and in animated series.
And while her male superhero
counterparts dominated the box office,
Wonder Woman
would have to wait until 2017
for her chance
to conquer the big screen.
Thank God I finally have company.
It is kind of astounding.
I know for a fact
how much Gal delved
into the heart and soul
of this character.
The fact that Patty Jenkins
has taken the reins
of that Wonder Woman movie
- literally makes my heart beat faster.
- Cut!
It's a voice of a woman
giving voice to a woman
who's out to change the world.
Like, that's what it's all about!
In many ways,
I think that's Marston's dream.
When this movie came out,
this Wonder Woman movie,
I was just, like, "Thank God!"
We need so much moral
backbone today
that, like, you know, it's refreshing.
It is about that mother,
nurturing, spirit energy
that's guided by love,
unconditional love.
The first movie
was really about
bringing Wonder Woman to our
world, and now she's here.
The future of Wonder Woman for me
is the idea that there's
this incredible character now,
this one, this one
that I'm involved with,
who has many more stories to tell
because now she's here.
Over 75 years after her debut,
Wonder Woman
is more visible, more popular,
more admired than ever
before, and it all started
with a unique bond shared
by three amazing people.
Looking back at the 75
years of Wonder Woman's history,
certain elements have remained solid
throughout all that time.
She's still a heroine
who chose to become a hero.
She's still a strong woman.
She still has the Lasso of Truth.
Those were core elements
to what Marston wanted to do.
He felt that women
were the wave of the future,
and she represented the best of that.
Bill Marston said
"When a woman
is in the White House,
we will have a better world.
We will have a loving world.
Women are the love leaders
of society."
That's what he believed.
That's what he lived.
Two love leaders in his life...
Elizabeth and Olive.
How it has evolved,
what my part in that was,
I pay homage
to Elizabeth and Olive.
I believe that
Elizabeth and Olive's legacy
should be that they
were two very strong,
very bright, very amazing women,
and as for
the Wonder Woman piece,
I believe their names should be
right up there with William Marston.
Whatever
lifestyle they were living,
and however they found
their truth in their love,
is something I have respect for
because what came out of it
spiritually was beautiful and pure.
No matter what the story is,
it doesn't change
what was accomplished.
To one degree or another,
they were his muses and partners.
We don't know all the details,
and we never will,
because they are all gone...
but it's also fun that there
is this lingering mystery,
and it helps us
keep wondering about them,
these people
who created Wonder Woman.
She's not about being a woman
any more than Superman's
about being a man,
and she's doing all of these things,
and the fact that she happens
to be a woman is the victory.
You're like,
"Oh, that's secondary."
Like, "don't worry about that part."
Stay here. I'll go ahead.
What a great
thing for little girls,
to see themselves in that way...
to feel not like they have to be
a "female" something.
They can just be a hero.
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~