sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
Superheroes and Superman...
they are one and the same.
There are no other superheroes
without Superman, he's the first.
An extraordinary being
with extraordinary powers.
That was it. The whole
world of comic books changed.
Superman is really
the all-father of superheroes.
He is the Odin from which
all else springs forward.
See, without Superman,
there's no Marvel
or DC,
no billion-dollar blockbusters.
That logo is one of
the three most recognizable symbols
on the planet,
and it stands shoulder to shoulder
with the crucifix
and the Jewish star.
Like, that's... madness, man!
Superman became
a worldwide phenomenon...
and he was created by two
working-class kids from Cleveland...
Jerry Siegel and Joe Shuster.
Superman... he's for justice.
It's kind of ironic
that there was a great injustice
done to his creators.
Siegel and Shuster
lost everything,
and just like Superman...
...they demanded justice.
_
Cleveland, Ohio.
The late 1920s.
To struggle is to be alive.
Poverty is commonplace.
And to be a dreamer...
is to be an outcast.
Jerry Siegel is a dreamer...
the son of working-class
Jewish immigrants.
Jerry dreams of a world
outside of Ohio...
one full of spacemen,
aliens,
and creatures
from a planet far, far away.
As kids play stickball,
Jerry prefers to stay inside.
A typewriter is his main companion.
Jerry Siegel...
he's a classic geek.
You know... instead of liking
football or liking baseball,
you know, he really
liked science fiction.
I think it really was
escape for him,
because he was very painfully
aware of how others thought of him.
Back then,
people looked at him and said,
"What? Comic books?
You really think there's
a future in comic books?"
At school, Jerry
is surrounded by classmates,
and yet he feels alone.
No one seems to "get" him...
until the day
he meets Joe Shuster.
- You all right?
- I'm fine.
Um, you're Siegel, right?
I'm...
Like Jerry, Joe
lives in a world of fantasy.
The two boys are kindred spirits.
- Is that Wonder Stories?
- Yeah. You know it?
Yeah, uh...
Joe was a super nerd too.
He was really small,
really thin,
he wore the glasses.
So he would get
all these self-help manuals
through the mail
on how to get strong,
and do all these exercises.
He ate raw eggs
and lifted weights
'cause he wanted to be this, like,
bigger person, and stronger...
But the thing is,
it just never worked for him.
He was still really thin,
really short,
really kind of scrawny.
Joe Shuster grew up very poor.
In fact, Joe had to learn
to draw with gloves on.
They couldn't afford heat.
He would take
his mom's bread board
when she was done making bread,
put a sheet of paper...
or anything he could find,
wallpaper,
scrap paper, anything,
and then he would
just draw on that.
He was never really
taught how to draw,
so he was self-taught,
but his eyesight was bad,
so he would get
inches away from the paper
and just scratch it out.
These two guys
just hit it off together,
and they worked on
the school newspaper together.
They found
that they had a lot in common.
An artist without a writer is as painful
as a writer without an artist.
I mean, you can have
these great ideas,
but if you can't translate them
somehow onto the page
and show them to people,
what good are they?
Joe was the perfect person
to translate Jerry's ideas.
In high school, they
worked on the school newspaper,
but they also
put together this magazine.
They called it Science Fiction.
One of the stories
in one of the issues
is called
The Reign of the Super-Man.
Jerry types down this real
pulpy science fiction story,
Joe illustrates it,
and the "super-man" in the story
is a bad guy,
and he's bald, too, in the picture,
so he looks like Lex Luthor,
and that story just doesn't work.
They try to get people to buy
the magazine, and nobody buys it.
And then, a seminal moment...
Jerry's father passes away.
He dies of a heart attack
while being robbed at gunpoint.
Jerry never finds justice
for his father's killers...
and it haunts him.
Jerry really
had it tough after that,
but he persisted, and that's
what Superman grew out of.
There's no coincidence
that a year later,
he creates Superman 's goal...
to eliminate crime.
Maybe we did it wrong.
We shouldn't have
made him a bad guy.
What if he was good?
He can do anything he wants,
but all he really wants
is to... to fit in...
and help people.
Any time
anybody creates something,
there's always
that aspect of themselves
that's in their characters.
You know, Joe, who was
small and couldn't get strong,
that went into, you know,
creating someone
who was big and strong,
like Superman.
With Jerry, it was more personal.
It was his father's death,
so Superman is really
a kind of autobiography
for both of them.
- Come here.
- What?
Tell me what you think of this.
That's our super-man!
In 1933,
Jerry Siegel and Joe Shuster
create a character entirely unique...
special powers,
a secret identity,
a visitor from a distant planet.
None of it had been seen before.
See, in those days,
all comic strips
are cowboys,
detectives,
spacemen.
There is no such thing as superheroes.
Jerry Siegel
had been inventing mythology
since he was a teenager.
Working with Joe, who was,
in many ways, his protégé,
they developed Superman together,
but it was a long gestation process.
It took many, many, many years.
When Siegel and Shuster
got started,
what they really wanted to do
was be able to sell a comic strip...
because back in the 1930s,
the real rock stars of the comics
world were comic strip artists.
Like Milton Caniff
or Rube Goldberg,
or E.C. Segar, who did Popeye,
they were the celebrities of their time.
They were on the front of magazines
and they met with presidents.
At that point, newspaper comics,
that was the way
to make a lot of money.
So they sent their Superman
to all these syndicates,
and they got them back
with rejection notices.
They couldn't sell it to anybody,
because any time
you have a new idea,
everybody thinks it's stupid.
You know, they said,
"Joe can't draw,"
"Jerry has no business writing,"
and somebody said,
"No one will ever believe this stuff."
Let's look at the heroes
who existed prior to Superman.
You had, like, your Flash Gordon,
your Buck Rogers.
You know, Flash Gordon,
at the end of the day,
was a guy who, like, you know,
hey, he luckily got to space.
He didn't have any superpowers.
Buck Rogers... just a guy
who went to the future.
Didn't have any superpowers.
But that genre would be
reinvented by Superman
because he's a god,
he's this strange visitor from
another planet with these abilities.
But newspapers were saying
"It's too far-fetched,"
"It's silly," and they felt that
this concept of a super-man
would never take off.
And, in the meantime,
they did get comic book work,
and so they were getting paid.
They were doing, uh, Dr. Occult.
They were doing, uh, a lot of
federal agent-type strips.
They were actually
building up a reputation
in this new comic industry.
Prior to Superman,
I don't know that you could say
there was a comic book business.
What there was...
was a publishing business.
There were pulp magazines.
There were comic strips,
which were the most popular
part of the newspapers,
and there were people
that were entrepreneurial,
in a way,
that tried to marry the two.
Ultimately, Superman
resided in the slush pile
until Harry Donenfeld
and Jack Liebowitz said,
"Let's give it a shot."
- What about that one?
- Can't put that on the cover.
It's a good story.
Doesn't matter.
It's not gonna sell magazines.
Harry Donenfeld and
Jack Liebowitz run DC Comics.
Donenfeld is a showman,
a bit outlandish.
Jack Liebowitz is mild-mannered,
more even-tempered.
Both men share a common bond... money.
But in 1937, business is bad,
and they are willing to take a risk.
What about that strip those
guys from Cleveland sent in?
Here it is.
- Superman.
- Superman, huh?
Harry and Jack were entrepreneurs.
They were just trying
to sell magazines.
They were just
trying to make a buck.
Let's get a contract
written up right away.
I'll have one sent out
for them to sign immediately.
And the letter
is sent to Jerry and Joe,
offering the grand sum total
of $10 a page,
and there's 13 pages,
so it was 130 bucks.
That Superman idea,
which had originally been formatted
as a comic strip, they said,
"Reformat those strips into a 13-page story."
The thing
that you have to remember
is that the process of creation,
you're putting
all of your energy into that.
You don't think about
if somebody's gonna cheat you.
You just hope
somebody's going to print it.
I told Donenfeld we'd have this
back to him by tomorrow.
You know, maybe they want to do
The Crimson Horsemen instead.
No, they want action.
They want Superman.
When we sign, we'll get our check.
$130.
Here, let me see that again.
Remember,
this process took years.
They had sent Superman to every
publisher. Nobody liked it.
If Jerry
and Joe sign the deal,
their character, Superman, will
be known throughout the world.
It's a dream they've had
since they were kids...
But if they sign, they also give up
all rights to the Superman character.
Okay, give me a pen.
Signing the deal
will change both men forever...
as Superman will become
a worldwide phenomenon.
With World War II looming,
the United States needs a hero,
someone who represents the
very best of American values...
truth, liberty, justice.
When Superman came along,
America was desperate
for a dream they could believe in.
Any story that could
touch them deep down
in a way that made them
feel that things might be okay
was going to ignite,
and Superman
happened to be that story.
Back then, nobody knew
who or what Superman was.
They'd just see this guy
in the tights
and he's lifting this car
over his head,
and that was it...
we have the first superhero.
Within three months,
Superman sold a million copies.
Once that happened...
Boom! Everything blew up.
I was a kid at that period,
and he was my hero.
I mean, it was phenomenal.
Superman
is celebrated within a year
at the New York World's Fair in 1939.
You have Superman
appearing in the Macy's parade.
You have Superman starting to show
up in comic strips and on radio.
- Look! Up in the sky!
- It's a bird! It's a plane!
It's Superman!
Max Fleischer
wanted to do Superman cartoons,
so they did Superman cartoons.
It was an early licensing bonanza.
There was costumes,
there was toys,
there was all kinds of spin-offs.
They didn't own the character,
but they got paid for it,
so Jerry and Joe
got to do their comic strip.
Superman
was showing up everywhere,
so they were doin' great.
They built a studio for Joe,
and they were able to bring in
other artists to help Joe,
because there was no way
he could turn out more than
one or two books a month,
so, uh, he would oversee
these guys drawing Superman.
Curl in the front of the forehead...
That's good.
- Joe, take a look at this.
- Yeah, just like that.
- Joe, so in this next scene...
- Right, this is the train...
- Now, this train has got to be huge.
- Yeah.
They're doing very good.
They were celebrities.
You know, Superman's creators,
Jerry Siegel and Joe Shuster.
So it was a good life.
In 1940, there's a famous
Saturday Evening Post article
where Siegel and Shuster
are held up
as these icons of American success.
Now, our guest tonight
is the man who originated Superman.
He's Mr. Jerry Siegel.
- Good evening, Fred.
- Now, how does he change his clothes so fast?
Well, after all,
he's Superman, Fred.
Jerry and Joe
are being paid well,
but not nearly well enough.
Donenfeld and Liebowitz are making
millions off their creation...
And as Superman's popularity grows,
so does the workload.
To Jerry and Joe...
it's just not right.
They were very unhappy
with what was an inequitable deal.
Something
as phenomenally successful
and wonderful as Superman,
it rankled Jerry and Joe
not getting their fair share.
They didn't get royalties,
really, essentially,
so, as the writer-creator
of Superman...
it would get you mad.
The bombing of Pearl Harbor
forces America into World War II.
Jerry is drafted to the Army,
while Joe stays home
due to his poor eyesight.
For the first time,
someone else writes Superman,
and Jerry isn't as valued
as he once was.
During the war, Superman
is more popular than ever.
He's an American ally,
battling villains
both real and imagined.
Really, what he did
was motivated people
to become a part of the war effort.
Perhaps most famously,
he was the most widely read
periodical on Army bases.
G.I.s and airmen
were putting him
on their tanks and on their Jeeps
and on their airplane nose cones
as a myth that they carried
with them and identified with
that gave them courage in battle.
Superman
is pure propaganda...
and the public can't get enough.
DC Comics capitalizes...
with a Superboy spin-off.
Jerry had pitched Superboy
many years earlier.
He presented this idea,
the adventures of Superman
when he was a boy,
called it Superboy...
and he was told by his editors,
"stupid idea."
While he was in the army,
DC Comics decided,
"Let's do Superboy."
They were in touch with Joe,
but they didn't tell Jerry
or ask his permission.
During the war,
Jerry met a, uh, an attorney,
who convinced him
that they should sue DC
to get out of their contract and try
to get more of a piece of Superman.
You're a lawyer.
They can't do this, right?
No.
No, they can't.
- So what can I do?
- Sue.
He sees himself
not only ripped off, but he thinks,
"This is a sign they want to
take away everything from me,"
so he's going to pursue justice.
Jerry Siegel comes home
from World War II on a mission.
It's 1947.
He's suing DC Comics
for the rights to Superman,
and he convinces Joe Shuster
to do the same.
Jerry is confident
that justice is on his side.
It's a gamble that could
cost both men everything.
The risk was being banned,
basically, from DC after that.
It is the opinion of this court
that the plaintiffs,
Mr. Siegel and Mr. Shuster,
transferred all of their rights
in, and to,
the comic strip Superman,
including the title, names, characters,
and concept to the defendant.
This court affirms that the defendant
is the sole and exclusive owner
of the character Superman.
This court is adjourned.
They lose that case.
They do not get Superman back...
But it then goes on to say
that the Superboy character
was indeed created by Jerry Siegel.
DC Comics should have
bought that character from him,
so they enter into a settlement.
They got a settlement,
but it went to all the lawyers,
and they were fired from
working on Superman at DC.
There's this really
strange thing that Jerry says.
He's in the courtroom, and he
looks over and he sees Superman...
and he disappears.
He knows
that this is the moment
where this thing
they'd worked so hard on
has been taken away...
and now they've been barred
from the character they created.
They're devastated by it,
but they're together,
and they say,
"Let's just do it again.
Let's do something better.
Lightning can strike twice."
And so,
they come up with Funnyman.
They took the humor of, like,
Danny Kaye's movies and
combined it with Superman,
but the jokes weren't very funny
and he wasn't all that super,
and that fell flat after
about a half a dozen issues.
People were expecting
another Superman,
and it was as far from
Superman as could be...
And I think that's where
they really felt it.
"Not only did we lose Superman,
but we lost the spark.
What do we have now?"
In hindsight, they should've
never filed the '47 lawsuit,
because in 1948, it did appear
that they were going to get
another renewal of their contract,
and if they'd taken that renewal,
that would've taken them
into the Superman TV show.
The Adventures of Superman!
That would've taken them
to a whole new era of merchandising.
They could've been set for life.
More powerful
than a locomotive...
The 1950s sees the
dawn of a new visual medium,
and once again
Superman is a sensation.
Alongside I Love Lucy,
The Adventures of Superman is one
of the biggest hits on television.
There can only be one Superman,
of course, but did you ever
think about some of the super
things that you can do for yourself?
Kids were completely enamored of it,
but also a lot of adults were, too.
The idea of someone
who's the best version of ourselves
was very appealing
to us as a society,
especially at the end of World War II.
Here was a guy
who had all this power,
and, unlike people with power
who abuse it,
Superman never abused his power,
and people just really gravitated to it,
so it was a huge hit.
Yes, it's Superman!
The strange visitor
from another planet
who came to Earth
with powers and abilities
far beyond those of mortal men.
Superman, who...
Do you know how many people
are watching this right now?
- Jerry...
- Do you know how much that
George Reeves makes?
How much those crooks,
Donenfeld and Liebowitz,
make off of what we did?
There wouldn't even be
a Superman if it wasn't for us.
How is it that we're sitting
here with nothing?
There's never going
to be another Superman, Joe.
Things for Jerry
got really bad really fast.
He couldn't get work.
His wife, Joanne...
she had Jerry's conviction that
there was an injustice done.
Joanne Siegel was Lois Lane.
She was the physical model
for Lois Lane, first of all,
but more important, later in life,
she was kind of sticking up for Jerry
at a time when he wasn't
sticking up for himself.
Joanne called DC Comics
and tried to shame them
into giving Jerry a job
so he could at least make some
money to keep his family going.
Thank you.
Jerry gets hired as a staff writer.
No celebration of his return.
He's just this anonymous... writer.
Even though Jerry was told,
"We'll never put your name
on these issues.
No one will ever know you wrote it,"
he still found a way
to get his voice into the stories.
I mean, he would write
these wonderful stories
of going back to Krypton.
Superman's return to Krypton,
I think that played into the fantasy
of "Well, if you could fix your life,
if you could go back
and do things over again,
what would you do?"
and here was Superman going back
and trying to save his parents
and finding that things
were not as simple
as he thought they were,
and that ultimately he failed anyway.
There's a funnier story;
Superboy 100,
a milestone issue of the character,
and Superboy's parents come
back, but it turns out that his
parents are evil pretenders
who are not really his parents,
which is a clear jibe
at Jerry Siegel's belief
that he's the true creator
of Superboy...
so he sneaks in these interesting
little jabs at the company.
With Jerry writing for DC,
Joe earns money as an artist...
but not drawing comic books.
What he's doing isn't for kids.
He actually started
doing S&M fetish drawings.
They were the pornography
of their time,
these under-the-counter pulps
that had very racy
inside artwork and stories.
Whether he was specifically
trying to look like
the Superman family as a kind
of a revenge against DC Comics
in these illustrated booklets
that he did,
called Nights of Horror,
I couldn't say, but that's
what Joe had been doing
in those kind of lost years that
nobody knew how he was getting by.
Joe was a jobber.
He had an assignment,
he was gonna do it...
But for Jerry, he felt like
he never had what he deserved.
Jerry was back
working at DC,
and had a rough time of it.
Hey, Siegel. How are
those changes coming along?
I'm just finishing them up
right now, sir.
Jerry would go in and say,
"Hey, I've got an idea about
Superman does this and that."
Sir? Did you get my story
about Krypton I sent you?
It's not gonna work.
Just stick to what the editor gave you.
And he would actually trade
the story off to another writer
and kind of make it as if it were him,
which is sort of the worst
thing you can do to a writer.
It kind of demoralizes them.
It was tough.
So, Jerry Siegel persuades Joe
to go in with him
to try to get Superman back...
again.
For Jerry, the risk was being let go
and losing his writer job,
but he had this core conviction
that they were being mistreated,
and until he had that judgment,
he was not going to be happy.
In 1967,
a new copyright law is enacted.
Jerry and Joe sue again,
trying to regain the rights
to Superman.
We are persuaded here
that the court judgment
of May 21, 1948
effectively stopped
Mr. Siegel and Mr. Shuster
from contesting the issue
of ownership of copyright
of Superman.
What they found was
that the Superboy settlement
had effectively closed the door
on any other litigation.
This precludes the
plaintiffs from contesting...
Leaving Jerry and Joe
without a job,
and without any other possibility
of opening it up again.
- ...the defendants, DC Comics.
- They were out of comics.
They were kind of out of everything.
They were pretty bleak times.
Joe is in New York,
unmarried, without children.
He stays in his brother's
one-bedroom apartment,
scraping by even to survive.
He slept on a cot,
next to a window
that had no curtains...
and had tape
on the broken cracks.
The artist of Superman...
sleeping on a cot.
In wintertime, he couldn't afford,
uh, to buy an overcoat.
For a period of time,
he was a messenger in Manhattan...
And one of his deliveries was
to DC Comics, and he came in
and saw the big painting
of Superman there.
Here he was,
delivering packages.
Can you sign this, please?
Line 17. Right there.
Meanwhile, the people
that were now taking over
Superman were doing
very well for themselves.
- The Sanchez file.
- Hello, Mr. Liebowitz.
Jack Liebowitz said,
"What are you doing around here?"
- He said, "Delivering messages."
- Delivery?
- "You don't have a coat."
- Oh, I don't mind the cold.
You buy yourself a warm coat,
you hear me?
Thank you, Mr. Liebowitz.
There's too many
stories like this. Bad stories.
Jerry is married with
one daughter in Southern California.
He works as a postal clerk.
Very few are aware that he created
the most iconic hero of our time.
Then something happens
that makes Jerry snap,
and it's the news that they're
going to make a Superman movie.
It's going to be this huge blockbuster
with Marlon Brando.
Mario Puzo, the guy
who wrote The Godfather movie's
getting paid
to write the Superman movie,
which Jerry Siegel sees...
and he loses it.
Here's a guy that created Superman.
We're going to be in every major
theatre in the United States,
and this guy has to work
as a mailman for his income.
The person who
won't speak up for himself
finally finds his voice...
...that kind of angry voice.
Jerry is tired.
He's tired of losing.
He's tired of being bullied,
and he's not
going to take it any longer.
Jerry writes letters...
letters full of vitriol and spite,
even putting a curse
on the Superman film.
He curses Warner Brothers
and DC, and says,
"Your Superman is built on lies."
He writes, "My American dream
has turned into an American nightmare."
He said, "I believed people.
I trusted people,
and then they took it all away from me,
and the courts didn't back me up."
He said, "Our system is broken."
Finally, he gets it all out
and he sends it to every
newspaper in the country.
Of course, nobody, you know,
does anything with it.
They don't believe it...
except one guy...
Neal Adams.
Neal Adams infused comics
with a sense of self-confidence and
swagger that wasn't there before.
He understood
the value of creativity,
and he had been around enough
people from the prior generation
to recognize that they were not
getting their proper due.
Ever since I got into comics,
I had been asking about
Jerry Siegel and Joe Shuster,
and, uh, one day, there was
a letter waiting for me,
and it was from Jerry Siegel...
...and it was the whole story
of what happened with Jerry and Joe,
from his point of view.
It was devastating.
The creators of Superman are no
longer associated with Superman?
Hmm...
No. That's not right.
By the mid 1970s,
the United States is hurting.
Vietnam...
Watergate...
and a crumbling economy
have all taken their toll.
Corporate greed has run amok.
Once again, America needs a hero.
The bicentennial is approaching,
and the public wants to believe
that the virtues of America
will be restored.
And that's where Jerry Siegel
and Joe Shuster
come back into the story.
People now, in the comics community,
particularly like Neal Adams,
sense that this is really unfair.
$300,000...
to Mario Puzo?
This guy, Jerry Siegel,
he's spitting ve...
He hates these...
He's just "pshht!"
You can't get a nice word
out of him. He's just angry.
He created Superman!
Joe doesn't have $300!
How does he get all that money,
and we get nothing?
I know you guys are upset
about the movie,
but I think you should look
at this as an opportunity.
- How?
- Well, it just so happens that I talked
to the president
of the International Press Corps,
and he agreed to set up
a press conference for you guys,
and when he does, the world is
finally gonna hear your story.
These guys went to DC
and Warner Brothers,
because Warner Brothers
owned DC,
and just said,
"Look, you can't do this."
For months,
Adams leads a media crusade,
and the public is ready to listen.
Something doesn't
have to be legal to be right,
and it doesn't have to be right
to be legal.
This is about justice.
The people want to
right the wrong of what happened
to Superman's creators.
This is a story of two men
who dreamed up a super idea
and then saw others
race away with it,
faster than a speeding bullet.
There's no courtroom in sight.
It's the courtroom of public opinion.
However much DC
may have been in the right
in the case, legally...
there is this sense in the general
public that this is not right.
We do not want
to live in an America
where people can
create something like this
and other people
can get rich off of it.
And so an agreement is reached.
If there is any story
the American audience loves,
it's the story
of the little man triumphant,
the individual who whups up
on big government or big business.
The publicity for Siegel
and Shuster was so heavy
that Warner Communications,
current owners of Superman,
decided to pay the two men
even though three courts had ruled
that Siegel and Shuster
had no ownership.
They end up
giving Siegel and Shuster
what's essentially a pension.
They got enough to live off of.
They seem pretty comfortable,
they can travel,
and there's a sense that maybe
their fight wasn't in vain.
Joe and Jerry
were fine with the settlement.
They said,
"We love this. This is great,"
and Neal Adams said "No."
He said, "We want the byline."
I said to Warners,
"Look, you take care of these boys,
and you will have
ambassadors of good will
for anything you do with Superman.
They're gonna be your friends.
When you open the Superman movie,
they'll be right there
with you, smiling."
Both men are
invited to the world premiere
of Superman: The Movie.
After nearly 30 years of anguish,
Jerry Siegel and Joe Shuster
have arrived.
Jerry and Joe
had gotten some money...
but on this night,
they would receive so much more.
For on this night...
Superman is theirs once again.
They got their byline back.
You know, for Siegel and Shuster,
after 28, 29 years,
they're seeing
their names on film
as the creators of this character.
That is a big thing for them.
That means a lot.
It's vindication.
Those two guys
who implanted the imaginations
of generations of children since then
and generations of children to come,
finally got acknowledged for that.
Siegel and Shuster believed
creative rights
belong to creative people,
and they had to fight for it.
Everybody who makes
a living dreaming about
people who put on capes
and masks and helping others
bend a knee at the altar
of Siegel and Shuster.
Without them, you have nothing.
Superman: The Movie
is released in December 1978,
and is a blockbuster smash,
earning $300 million
during its theatrical run.
In the decade that follows,
Joe and Jerry are comfortable,
if not content.
They live on the California coastline,
just a few houses
away from each other.
And that's the best, you now?
So at the end,
it's not the court case or
controversy about Superman.
It's just two best friends.
One of the big life lessons from this
is "creator rights matter."
A young person who's aware
of Siegel and Shuster,
they now know what they
have to have in a row.
Everybody now fights for their rights.
The business has changed
because everybody learned
from Jerry Siegel and Joe Shuster.
Out of a kitchen,
two kids create
the world's first superhero.
It's a fable
almost as fantastical as flying.
Theirs is a tale of struggle and
heartache, but also of perseverance.
They made it,
and the world will always know...
Superman,
created by Jerry Siegel and Joe Shuster.
_
__
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~