sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
New York City is the heart
and soul of comic books.
That's where
these guys that drew it grew up.
That's where they created
these characters.
Instead of having them live
in a fictional place,
I plunked 'em right down
in New York City.
Whatever happens in New York
is going to affect comic books
whether you want it to or not.
What is the comic book
industry supposed to do
when you have a serious moral and
political challenge in New York City?
9/11 changed New York City
and comic books forever.
_
New York City is this city of heroes.
When you look at a comic book,
you open it up,
I don't care... if it's The Avengers,
Peter Parker,
you're...
you're in New York City,
and to understand the centrality
of this city to superheroes,
you've gotta go back
to the beginning.
New York
has always been synonymous
with being a place
where dreams come true.
It was the gateway to America.
It's just a place where everybody has
to cohabitate and figure it out.
New York, New York
is so nice, they named it twice.
It's the Earth, you know,
sort of crammed onto
this one little island.
New York has always been that,
and it was especially that
in the 20th century,
when comic books were becoming
a part of popular culture.
New York was geographically
central to comic books.
The American comic book
was born in New York
by creators that had their roots
in the ghettoes of New York.
I was born on Essex Street,
New York's Lower East Side.
I lived in the Bronx, in New York.
I was a poor kid, very poor,
and a tough neighborhood,
too, I lived in.
You have
all these writers and artists
in this city in and amongst
the turmoil of the great wars
and the Great Depression,
and dreaming up
these larger-than-life figures
who come in and make it right.
What Action Comics
with Superman did
is it used this low format
as a vehicle
to tell a story that ignited
the popular imagination.
Presenting America's
number-one comic strip character...
Yes, it's Superman.
American superheroes are... are
really kind of a wish fulfillment,
but they're also a way
of facing our fears.
They... they are the kind of
instrument, the vehicle that
we'd like to step into
so that we can be bulletproof.
Siegel and Shuster, you know,
created Superman that way,
so that it could be this
metaphor for us kind of
holding up a shield against
these attacking forces.
All your core characters
are found in New York.
Metropolis is a glyph
for New York.
To Batman, Gotham City
is also a glyph for New York.
The scale, the buildings,
they were all part of
the dream of New York
that existed around the world.
By the 1960s,
the big Marvel heroes come out.
Stan Lee collaborated
with Jack Kirby and Steve Ditko
to create, you know, Spider-Man,
the Avengers,
the Fantastic Four,
Daredevil,
Doctor Strange...
Instead of having them live
in a fictional place,
like Metropolis or Gotham City,
I plunked 'em right down
in New York City...
Because I knew New York City,
I could write about New York City,
and I figured,
why not let 'em live in a real place?
Marvel Comics
made New York City
the center of this moral drama,
and they've made it
the home of the imagination
of a whole generation
of young people.
I grew up in the Bronx, originally,
and I would read comic books
all the time,
and I could imagine as a kid,
you know,
Spider-Man swinging
from building to building,
and I remember as a child
looking up, saying,
"Wow, if I could only do that."
It brought it that much more... real.
I remember the first time
that I went to New York City.
I was maybe 12 or 13,
and we went to the Statue of Liberty.
I remember thinking, "Oh, I think I
read an issue of, um, Marvel Team-Up
with Spider-Man and somebody
that took place here."
My whole orientation
to New York at the time
was absolutely via Marvel Comics.
In the late '60s, Marvel
Comics were the ones that,
it seemed like, were more tackling
the upheaval and changes
that were going on.
You've got civil strife
in New York City,
and so everything's changing,
and because everything
was changing in life,
everything was changing in art.
Comics were
becoming more socially relevant
and more interesting.
The X-Men,
a metaphor for civil rights.
These were normal people,
flawed human beings,
people who, in various ways,
had dealt with prejudices and bigotry
and intolerance of whatever kind.
Comic books
talked about the real world,
which is what Denny O'Neil and I
were very conscious of
when we did the Green Lantern,
Green Arrow series.
That comic book talked about
my neighborhood up in the Bronx
and dealing with drug problems.
It talked about overpopulation.
Comics were getting more
sophisticated, more marketed to adults.
In the '80s, you had the Punisher,
but you also had Watchmen.
Those were really,
really challenging stories.
They were stories about
changing the status quo
and necessary fascism
and all those kind of things.
We can't believe in
these super Boy Scouts anymore.
We don't know anybody in real
life who behaves like that,
and the readers don't believe in them,
so we've just tried to make them
a little bit more like
real 20th-century human beings.
And then Frank Miller
made a massive difference
with The Dark Knight,
and his Daredevil work was brilliant.
Frank brought a level of realism
that was really unprecedented.
Watchmen,
Dark Knight, Daredevil
were based out of New York.
They infused political topics,
you know, gang violence.
You could feel the city.
You could feel the grit
of the place in every panel.
By 2000 and 2001,
comics had a mature enough
base of storytellers in New York
to be able to speak to the unique
concerns of the 21st century.
We just had a plane
just crash into an upper floor
of the World Trade Center.
Then you had 9/11,
and the diet of heroism
changes worldwide
because of what happened
to those artists in New York.
Comic books are a kind of
monolith to New York City,
the same way
the Twin Towers were.
You look at them, and they're
kind of this gleaming ideal
of American ingenuity,
culture, art.
The Twin Towers
were about as iconic a...
a New York landmark as there is.
I can remember
when they were being built,
the newspapers talking about
how they were hideous,
how they shouldn't be built,
how it would "ruin the skyline."
And then,
when they were completed,
people finally realized,
"Wow, they are majestic."
Superheroes are operatic,
larger-than-life ideas.
The Twin Towers represented
this symbol of American triumphalism,
and that is reflected in the comic
books and the popular culture.
And then you had 9/11,
after which everything changes.
The unimaginable happens,
and it happens right in the beating
heart of America, New York City,
which is the heart and soul
of comic books.
It's difficult to find the words
to describe the feeling
in New York City today.
New York City is in shock,
one of its most famous
landmarks destroyed,
thousands dead,
and America is under siege.
What the hell is going on?
What happened?
It was a day like any other day.
I remember it like it was yesterday.
I was home on 27th Street.
We could see what was going on
from the point of view
of the clouds of smoke.
I feel a sense of tragedy that,
you know, men do this to other men.
Watching the TV
and seeing the plume of smoke,
and then opening the window
and seeing the plume of smoke...
It was nothing I've ever
experienced before.
My parents were visiting, and...
and my father and I had planned to
walk around and explore Wall Street,
and, uh, I ended up sleepin' in
a little later to...
to catch a slightly later train,
and when I did come downstairs,
uh... my folks were in front
of the TV, watchin' CNN,
and we watched
the whole thing unfold,
and I... I went out my backyard,
climbed up to the top of the hill,
and, uh, you know, even from
there, could see the smoke rising.
Our lives changed.
Everybody's lives changed.
So many lives were lost.
The Marvel and DC offices
were both in New York,
and so all of our friends,
the people that we cared about,
people that we were
in the industry with,
we wanted to make sure
that everybody was okay,
and everybody was not okay.
Some people dealt with
their grief really differently.
The... the dust from 9/11
is on the... the... the tables
and the platforms in those buildings
when it's time to go back in
there and make the next issue.
My mom worked
in the World Trade Center
when I... when I
was a young kid, you know.
I used to visit the Twin Towers
all the time,
and so for me, they were personal.
How do I represent
what has happened...
in a way that's not just
for entertainment?
Comics responded
to 9/11 immediately.
Marvel was probably
the first on the scene.
Joe Quesada and Bill Jemas...
Joe was the editor-in-chief,
Bill was the publisher...
were the first to go,
"We're New Yorkers.
This is our town,
this thing happened here.
We've gotta talk to our people,"
and so they created a pinup
anthology called "Heroes,"
which gathered
all of the best talent
that was able to turn in
a great piece of art in a week,
and they created
"A Moment of Silence,"
which was a comic book narrative
that spoke to the concerns of 9/11.
They immediately went
on The Today Show.
They immediately went out
into the world
and started saying,
"We've got something to say.
We've got what you want to hear."
What is the thing that
Marvel Comics is trying to do
- that is important here?
- Well, again, we...
we strive to tell stories of
the heroic ideal,
and I think what we saw after 9/11
was that the heroic ideal
was living amongst us,
and it walks amongst us every day,
and we... we always
take it for granted
until we actually
need these people.
The 20 years leading up to 9/11
was about a quest for legitimacy
in the comic book industry.
We wanted to be seen as important
as any other form
of popular culture,
but they weren't afforded that respect.
They were regarded as low value.
They were regarded
as this thing that was lesser.
This stigma really became neutral,
it really went away, after 9/11,
and it went away because comics
were the first on the scene
to respond in an intelligent way
people could relate to.
Whenever you're going through
those big changes in a civilization,
uh, people need stories.
People reach for stories.
The superhero genre gives you
a great opportunity
to process all of that.
Jan Michael Straczynski
wrote a Spider-Man comic
where Spider-Man's at 9/11,
and he expresses all those feelings,
in December of 2001.
Spider-Man down at
ground zero, it's the sense of...
I mean, even me, as an FBI agent...
Your soul is ruined.
You are internally destroyed.
"With all my great power,
with all what I have,
with all what I was given,
it still happened,"
and that is hard to accept.
It's hard to live with.
I remember, like,
one of the most striking panels
was Doctor Doom rolling a tear.
You know how many times
we've seen Doctor Doom
take on New York?
Even Doctor Doom was like, "Whoa."
It set up a lot of really interesting things,
the way that they portrayed the heroes,
because the superheroes,
they were actually drew smaller.
The heroes are often
in the background,
where you see the... the firefighters
and the other rescue workers
in the front in that particular issue.
We've done heroes for
years and years, but they were...
they were not real, compared to,
you know, the police, and firemen,
and paramedics that came in and
actually, you know, helped people.
It's something that the companies
really wanted to get across.
These fictional ideas, they
couldn't stop the atrocity from happening,
but they can help frame the way
that we cope with the atrocity.
They can help frame the way
that we deal with
the world that had changed.
These characters had sudden resonance.
I think that comics,
after 9/11, were just beginning.
I think the superhero worlds
were really just beginning.
You need these superhuman beings
to sort of fight out,
in an exaggerated way,
the challenges of the time.
After 9/11,
New York City was kind of
an incredible place to be.
Everyone was kind of coming together
in this way that I'd never
experienced, you know, before or since.
I saw just a lot of
people just together, bein' friends,
a big change in the way
people acted and talked then.
You just got a warm welcome
from everybody you saw.
We suddenly started
plastering American flags
in our apartment windows,
and adding American flags
to our comic books.
That was a time when patriotism
became much more important in America.
The first Spider-Man
movie with Tobey Maguire
had been filmed, had been
written, before 9/11 happened,
but the movie opened
with an American flag.
It closed with an American flag, which was
really, really a big thing after 9/11.
People just... I think they felt
that when they went and saw it,
and I think that's one of the reasons
why it became as popular as it did.
That patriotism, and,
specifically, New Yorkers
comin' together and,
"I love New York," uh, kind of vibe
was a very important
part of the film...
to show the bad guys that, you
know, they can't keep us down.
They can, you know, they can
maybe knock us down,
but New York is going
to get right back up.
The advertising campaign for Spider-Man
was built around the Twin Towers,
and there was a teaser trailer,
and Spider-Man, uh,
basically saves the day
by spinning a web
between the Twin Towers.
It was a great campaign, a great
way of kind of, you know, saying,
saying, "Hey, here's this hero that
you've been waiting for all these years,
going to be on the big
screen in New York City,
and what could be
more iconic for New York?"
But at the same time, those images
became these kind of triggers
for just really complicated
emotional reactions for people,
so they pulled that entire campaign.
I remember havin'
a conversation with Sam about...
He was talkin' to the marketing
people, and sayin', you know,
"Maybe we just leave it."
But the decision was made to deal
with the reality in the aftermath.
You could see something about
that movie was kind of taking hold.
With Spider-Man, he's a guy
who's kind of a metaphor for the Everyman.
It was a man personally going
out there, fighting for New York,
and taking matters in his own hands,
and you have epic evil battles.
They're superheroes,
and they're winning,
and so it's something
that all of us...
It was probably
the most gratifying thing
that could come along
at that moment.
After we had all felt so powerless,
the world was just ripe
for that kind of storytelling.
God bless you, Spider-Man.
Bless you.
In a weird way, it was
Spider-Man that reminded Americans
that after 9/11,
they needed superheroes.
We wanted a savior we could believe in.
We wanted a hero we could believe in,
that would swoop in
and save New York,
because saving New York was about
saving our idea of the United States.
When Marvel recognized that they
had the opportunity to tell stories
set in this ambiguous new
"war on terror" environment,
they took the idea of superheroes
and set the stakes in a way
that people would understand.
Captain America, especially,
was a way to inspire people
to cope with the changes that were
happening in the country at the time.
Marvel wanted Captain America
to represent something
that we really needed.
Captain America
was a symbol of America.
He was a New Yorker
fighting the Germans,
you know, during World War II,
at a time when our country
was at stake.
Joe Simon and Jack Kirby
created him a little before the war,
but as a rallying cry
to get America to fight fascism.
Captain America punched Hitler
a year before the U.S.
entered World War II.
Suddenly, Captain America is
resurrected in a much more
complicated environment.
We're in a new world.
It wasn't like, you know,
"Captain America versus the Red Skull"
type of a conflict.
It was just this... madness.
There's such anger, and we'd better
blast the hell out of somebody.
Everybody's ready to flatten someone.
The House of Representatives
has spoken clearly to the world.
The gathering threat of Iraq
must be confronted.
Suddenly, we're going to invade Iraq,
that had nothing to do with 9/11.
People started questioning their
government to the point of protest.
It was a massive rally
up and down First Avenue.
Fights broke out,
eight cops were injured,
some 50 protesters arrested.
In New York, you have Americans
choosing sides
and becoming very partisan,
and that's just going to affect
comic books immediately,
because all our offices
were in New York,
and all our editors were in New York.
Marvel has a New York office,
and so they're there in it,
and you want to say something.
Writers force Cap
to question the choices
his government was making,
because the writers
could not continue
to write this character
as a proud patriot
when New York was going through
such a violent and terrible upheaval.
Captain America is America, you know?
He's the embodi...
He's the super-soldier.
He's the leader of armies, and
then now he's opposed to the war.
I was surprised
that comic books stepped up,
because the Dixie Chicks said
something wrong about Bush,
and their album sales dropped.
Lead singer Natalie Maines said
she was ashamed
President Bush was a Texan.
Some protestors used a tractor
to smash the group's CDs...
Suddenly, things were
a lot more blurry,
and the black-and-white
ideologies of heroism
that defined superheroes before 9/11
didn't really apply.
When America becomes polarized
and America no longer has a center,
you're either on the left
or the right.
Who does Cap side with?
That question, just as it
tore apart American society,
and New York in particular, tears
apart the comic book universes.
At this hour,
American and coalition forces
are in the early stages
of military operations
to disarm Iraq, to free its people,
and to defend the world
from grave danger.
After 9/11, the United States
goes from being unfairly victimized
and therefore the object
of great affection
to itself seeming to be a threat.
The invasion of Iraq,
Guantanamo,
and the Patriot Act, which
became a big overreach in terms of
what the government gave itself
the permission to do,
and that has its reverberations
in New York,
and in the comic book world.
In 2004, Marvel started
taking all their characters
into one storyline every year and
creating a big event in New York where
they would have to face
a threat that was large enough
for the entire Marvel universe
to have to deal with together,
and Mark Millar, a phenomenal writer,
had the genius idea to say,
"Okay, what if this big threat
is really the heroes themselves?"
It was unlike anything
anybody had ever done.
I've found everything I've done
relates to whatever is happening
in the world at that time,
and Civil War was a response
to the very polarized America that
I saw when I traveled to New York.
Every two or three months,
I used to be in New York,
and I would see a country that
didn't seem very at ease with itself.
People just seemed to be having
these massive polarized
arguments, and, for me,
that ended up working its way
into a superhero story.
Mayhem in Manhattan...
Over 1,100 arrested
as anti-Bush protesters
clash with police.
Get back! Get outta here!
Comic book artists and authors
were able to use this visual medium
to debate what was being debated
in... in the political
sphere at the time.
Civil War began with
a tragedy in Stamford, Connecticut,
where the actions
of a team of inexperienced
young superheroes
resulted in the death
of several hundred people,
including about 60 schoolchildren.
It was obviously an analogue
to what happened in 9/11,
so the U.S. government passed
the Superhero Registration Act,
which required that all superpowered
beings register their identities
with the government,
become trained by the government.
In the Marvel "Civil War"
context, the government says,
"Listen, you guys
are gonna have to register
and do all these things
and follow all these rules."
Is that securing freedom,
or is that the end of freedom?
This is a question
that the Patriot Act raises.
It's a question that
the entire war on terror raises.
That question, just as it
tore apart New York City,
tears apart the Marvel universe.
It's that profound a question in
the minds of the artists and society,
that you literally have a civil war,
not between villains and heroes,
but a war among the heroes,
because the answers
are no longer obvious.
"Civil War" was a case
where there were people
who had different ideological
beliefs that led them into conflict.
They... they thought they were right,
and it was leading to all-out war.
It pitted Captain America
and Iron Man against each other.
Captain America's viewpoint was the
idea of "I fought for these freedoms.
I fought the Nazis for
this, and we're just going to
voluntarily hand them over?
No, I'm not gonna do that,"
whereas Iron Man's position was
"We should trust in the government
to best manage this."
Iron Man represented the Republicans
because Tony Stark is really a guy
who has, like,
loads and loads of money,
and he makes munitions,
and Captain America represented
the Democrats...
But Spider-Man's us.
He was Everyman, trying
to work out "What do I do?"
He was a moderate guy in the middle,
living in New York City,
trying to work out
what was happening.
I was a New Yorker at the time of 9/11,
so I was, um...
traumatized and worried.
I was behind the Iraq war,
the Patriot Act.
The same thing happens with Spider-Man
in the "Civil War" comic books.
Spider-Man stands for New York,
and he sides with Iron Man,
but when he sees that Iron Man,
in enforcing this law,
is taking superheroes and putting
them in other-dimensional prisons,
spying on them, killing them,
Spider-Man starts to really wonder
about the enforcement of this law,
and he defects.
Yes, national security is really
important, but so are civil liberties,
and that's not a little wussy thing
to be concerned about.
It's not treasonous.
Spider-Man sort of gave me
the courage to see that.
I think one of the really interesting
things about "Civil War"
is that it really doesn't
come to a conclusion
about which side was better...
And it ends with
the death of Captain America,
which was a hugely publicized event.
Today, comic book fans snapped up
and dove into the pages that
mark the end of Captain America.
It begs the question about
Captain America's death. Why now?
When Captain America was shot,
it was, to me, the iconic moment
of "Civil War."
It felt like that loss of innocence
that the nation went through on 9/11,
embodied in a character
that embodied America.
It was a statement about
how hope was beginning to fade,
that we were shooting ourselves
in the foot,
that American patriotism and ideals,
the very embodiment of
sort of September the 12th,
where people came together
in New York City,
had just been shot through the heart.
Civil War became
a huge comic storyline
because it was...
it was of its time.
It was the biggest thing that's
ever happened to superheroes.
It's no coincidence
that Marvel's Civil War
is the phenomenon that it is.
This is a story fundamentally
about this existential fear of terror.
This has to do with
these external threats,
and what we are willing to do
as citizens to cope with them.
Having the story set in New York
helped people
wrap their arms around
how they can be change agents
in their own life.
Whether it's 9/11
or the Patriot Act,
I think that's all fair game
in comic books,
and all sort of ripe material
for comic book filmmakers
like Chris Nolan to draw from.
Before 9/11, New York
was this kind of city of dreams
that people from all over
the world were going to,
but after 9/11, it was a city that
wasn't quite so wondrous anymore.
It was March 6, 2008,
and the military recruiting center
in Times Square was the target.
In Times Square today, the FBI put
up a billboard asking for tips.
Similar postings are going up
in New Jersey, Connecticut,
and Pennsylvania.
When we were working
on a story for The Dark Knight,
Chris and I talked a lot
about New York,
because everyone always
substituted Gotham for New York.
The version of New York
that was in The Dark Knight trilogy
is kind of being, if things
just kept that downward spiral,
what would New York become?
This is the week the world actually
gets to see The Dark Knight,
one of the most highly
anticipated pictures of 2008.
The film's a follow-up to
director Christopher Nolan's
Batman Begins, which I admired,
but The Dark Knight
paints a dizzying portrait
of Gotham City nearing total anarchy.
There have been many different
interpretations of Batman.
Tim Burton's Batman,
wonderful movie,
but there's a choice made
to set it in a time and place.
You had the Jack Nicholson Joker,
larger than life.
There was the campiness of Batman...
We felt that the Burton Batman,
as wonderful as they were,
they were kind of out of lockstep
with where the public psyche
was at the time,
especially in and around
New York City.
We were reading
secondary terrorist attacks
in New York City, and saying,
"Okay, how can we take
a page from reality
and bring it into
this fictionalized world?"
It's not enough to have
a super-villain rob a big bank.
If we're going to delve into this,
then the villains
need to become truly villainous,
and the way that you become villainous
is that you terrorize people.
9/11 changed the perspective
and the attitude towards the material.
When you think about that event,
and you think about
how massive that was for...
for everyone, Americans and
people around the world alike,
it's not something that you just
take out of your thinking.
In The Dark Knight,
you are presented the Joker,
who is a different Joker
than we've ever seen before.
All you care about is money.
This town deserves
a better class of criminal.
Heath Ledger's Joker,
he really embodied a terrorist
that nihilistically wanted
to destroy New York City
because he hates
what it represents,
and there's a certain feeling
that that's what happened in 9/11.
Terrorism, it's rooted in a philosophy,
a particular interpretation of religion
that seems extremely, uh...
alien to us.
Terrorists had a...
a mission, if you will,
to fulfill with organized,
if you will, mayhem
here in New York City
the same way the Joker did as well.
When we were
reconceiving of the Joker,
we talked about the kind of tactics
that the insurgents were using,
the way that they would,
you know, kidnap people
and execute them, and...
and terrorize.
How do you deal
with terrorism?
In some ways, the hero
becomes the anti-hero
who's willing to throw away
his or her own moral code,
get down to the level of the villain,
in order to prevail.
Well, that is 180 degrees
from the lesson of...
lessons of comic books for 30 years.
A strong part of, you know,
Chris's theme in those movies
was the... the blurring of the
lines between good and evil,
um, and, uh,
Batman takes this, uh, step
into a... a darker, uh,
ethical and moral world.
That was a moment in which you
had the first revelations
about the warrantless wiretapping
that they were doing,
and it was something
that I was fascinated by.
You've turned every cell phone
in Gotham into a microphone.
- I've got to find this man, Lucius.
- At what cost?
The story
of what he's willing to do
to stop something terrible
from happening,
for me, takes on
much more dimension.
It's got much more grit to it, because
he's willing to go a little too far.
One of the questions that
we were constantly trying
to subtly posit
to the audience is, you know,
are the methods he's employing
actually making things better?
We were trying to draw
those kinds of analogies
into the superhero world.
We have this duality
in our personalities,
and we have the dark side
and light side,
and sometimes we think
we need to go to the dark side
to solve the problems and the issues.
Harvey Dent has a line in
The Dark Knight, which is...
You either die a hero,
or you live long enough to see
yourself become the villain.
The longer the...
the fight goes on,
the more likely
that something in your soul
gets a little compromised,
and you find yourself
on the other side of it.
We wanted to take the film
to the nightmarish version
of what if the villain's plot,
which is always foiled
in every comic book movie,
what if it wasn't?
Right? What happens in the
fallout from that event?
Every event since the attacks
has shaped the way
that comic books work,
the way that characters
interact with each other,
the issues they're concerned about.
9/11 changed New York
City like we've never seen before.
9/11 didn't just change facts,
9/11 changed fiction.
You have this sense that
New York is the natural place
for these superhero films to play out,
because comic books
kind of grew up with the city,
and they feel inextricably
linked to one another.
As New York has matured,
superhero storytelling has
matured in an interesting way,
and that is fueling
the movies of today.
These characters aren't
just kind of bland, basic,
you know, paper-thin people.
They've become so much
more sophisticated, and that's,
you know, one of the reasons
why they're just so successful
at the box office.
The Avengers,
they absolutely crushed domestic
box office records.
Over $200 million in ticket sales.
We see in The Avengers
movie that heroes can also be
not necessarily villains, but they
can be the source of destruction,
and even as they're trying
to protect New York City,
there can be this enormous
collateral damage,
and instead of just coming back
in the next episode
having forgotten that,
or starting over,
these movies are dealing with the
complexity of that kind of reaction.
They really try to treat destruction
not as something fun to draw
and something to read,
but something that causes real pain,
and because of that,
the superheroes are more thoughtful,
they're more upset,
they fail more often...
and they're still talking about the
battle of New York in several sequels.
We're looking for realism in fiction?
Even though you're using it
as an escape from the real world,
you still kind of
want to be connected.
9/11 and... the event
and things that happened
after that in New York just
kind of made it almost impossible
to not want to connect in that way.
New York was always
synonymous with comic books,
and so it's not surprising
to me that, to this day,
New York continues to be
synonymous with Batman,
the Avengers,
Spider-Man,
and the Daredevil TV show.
...he told me you were
the man this city needs.
I think you're also
the man this city created.
When we were writing Daredevil,
we were channeling the New York
of the early '80s, late '70s,
when Frank Miller
was doing the stories.
You felt like you were doing
something new,
but that you could root
in their history.
New York City
is its own character in comics,
because it represents
the United States of America
in a very material way.
It represents so many things.
It represents hope,
and that's what comics represent.
One World Trade Center
will officially open to the public today,
bringing back a view
that has not been seen
since the attacks
on the Twin Towers years ago.
The operators say they wanted it
to be a place of hope and courage.
It's a beautiful thing, man,
and even post-September 11th,
comics found a way to address
the worst thing that ever happened,
and do it with their characters,
do it with respect,
honor New York,
mark the moment,
and allow us all to kind of
pick up and move on after that.
When you look around now
in New York City,
the superhero is everywhere...
In the same way that in Rome,
the Roman gods were everywhere,
and the Roman gods were
everywhere doing the things
that gods do
to teach lessons for people,
to teach lessons for mortals,
and, increasingly, the superhero
has been playing that role,
and they certainly did after 9/11.
It's a forum that deals
with high philosophy, virtue.
What is virtue?
What is good?
Who is good?
What is my duty?
What is right and what is wrong?
It's something that helps
bring us together
as New Yorkers,
and as Americans,
and as a bunch of people
with our inner nine-year-olds
still alive and well.
New York is this city of heroes.
It's also a city of dreamers.
That connectivity to the city,
and the place where
all of this was dreamt up
is still very, very important.
I think it'd be a shame if that...
if that ever went away.
We all are
on this little island together,
and we're in it together
and we're fighting together,
and we're coexisting together.
I really believe that this is a place
where, you know,
heroes are born.
By setting the
superhero universe in New York,
comics had enlarged the idea of
the city from what was already
a very large idea
in the human consciousness.
The city was no longer
just the place that you went
to prove yourself.
The city created all
kinds of aspiration.
The city was a city of heroes.
Really, that's the only place
a superhero can effectively belong.
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~