sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
I read a lot of comic books
when I was a kid.
There were no black superheroes.
None of 'em...
looked like me.
As a young black kid,
we would look at
the representations
that we had
and sort of be ashamed.
The comic books today, they
reflect the people who create them,
people who are in charge,
who are mostly white males.
At the time, I said, "If I want a world
where there's black superheroes,
we're going to have to create
some black superheroes.
Every black kid who's ever wanted
to do comics has had that idea.
I told him, "The only way we're
going to see it is if we do it."
Milestone Comics
was heroes for everybody.
They were very, very innovative
and ahead of their time.
It was definitely revolutionary.
The political act
was forming the company,
and having four black guys in charge.
We broke a lot of barriers,
but there's a price to be paid
for doing things differently.
So... you want the real
story of Milestone?
Okay, here we go.
_
I was raised
in Springfield Gardens, Queens,
by my grandparents.
They took all of us kids in
after my mom died.
She died when I was eight.
After my mom died,
I met this kid, Derek,
Derek Dingle.
He and I sat next to each other
from second through fifth grade.
We were...
we were pretty much inseparable.
I went to Denys's home one day
with a stack of comic books
from my brother's collection.
I did not know
what a comic book was
until Derek showed me,
and I was just done.
From that moment, you know,
I just looked at them,
and I was just...
I was just gone.
After that, I probably went to
school to look at comic books.
Well, I liked to get
the new comic books from Derek.
I had big bottle glasses,
I had a pocket protector,
I looked like Sam Jackson
in Unbreakable.
You know, with that hairstyle
that went like that?
I was that kid.
I was that kid... I was picked on.
Well, the comics were, like,
helping me cope with all that,
or maybe sometimes you get picked on
because you're reading comic books.
Comics were sort of
that little underground thing
that we all did back then.
Growing up, I read
a lot of comic books.
Most of the kids in my neighborhood
read comic books.
It doesn't grab everybody.
You just know it's for you.
I mean, you have to be born
a comic book fan, I think,
'cause once you see one, it's like...
And you open one, and the smell,
and the pages, and everything, it...
You have to be born
a comic book fan, I think.
Black kids
read comics in huge numbers.
The presumption that
black people don't read comics
comes from people
who don't know black people.
To be a kid growing up in that era,
you know, and reading
The Fantastic Four,
and reading The Hulk,
and Spider-Man, and Batman,
Superman, whatever it was
you were reading,
and to not see yourself,
you know, like, we were
completely invisible.
There were representations of
African-Americans in mainstream comics,
but they tended towards kind of
the stereotypical or the racist.
Probably the most
infamous would be Ebony White
with Will Eisner's "The Spirit."
Big lips, big eyes...
he was meant to be comic relief.
"White Wash," in 1941,
this big red-lipped,
pimp hat-wearing guy
who's all, "Oh Lord, help me!"
you know, this kind of thing.
He was always in trouble,
and it was just a superfluous,
unnecessary character.
As a young black kid, you know,
we would look at these other
characters and sort of be ashamed,
because that's all
we would see of ourselves.
That was the representations
that we had.
There was nothing to aspire to.
After a while, you're saying,
"Why isn't the hero African-American?"
I remember the day when Derek
bought me a copy of
"Fantastic Four #52," and I
remember us reading it under the desk
when we were supposed to be,
you know, doing our lessons,
and that was the first time
I had seen the Black Panther.
That was something...
that was a special moment.
When the Black Panther showed up,
dressed all in black...
still one of the coolest outfits
in the history of comic books.
He's not a sidekick,
he's not a mugger...
His introduction was him
taking on the Fantastic Four
to see if he could beat them,
and he did,
and as a kid, that blew my mind.
They'd beaten Dr. Doom.
They'd beaten Galactus,
who eats planets, but...
the Black Panther defeats them all.
So you go,
"This cat is badass."
The Black Panther is a really
important character.
Now, of course,
all of his earliest adventures
were written by, you know,
white writers
and drawn by white artists.
Well, I never thought
that it was my place
to talk about politics, but I
also felt there were some things
that perhaps
ought to be mentioned,
and one of the things I've
always been against is bigotry.
I like the pilot very much, yeah.
She's a black girl, that's good.
Stan Lee and Jack Kirby
named their black superhero
"the Black Panther"
in the middle
of the civil rights movement.
Think about that.
Stan Lee and Ja... Two white...
Two Jewish people!
And I thought, "I will make him
the king of a black nation in Africa."
He had his own
country, and his country was
the most technologically
advanced country on the planet.
The mythology
is that he sort of understood
that Americans were a little too racist
to accept, like,
a black superhero from America.
The Black Panther can be
powerful over there in Wakanda,
and so he is not
as inherently threatening
as someone that you might see
around the corner.
The first
African-American hero I saw
was Luke Cage.
I would go to my local comic book store.
They had their comic books
on a spinner rack,
and I remember
this one standing out.
It was just a single figure
of a black man
bursting out of chains,
and I thought it was
the coolest thing I'd ever seen.
I brought it to school,
and I showed it to Derek.
He was blown away.
It was one of the few times
I got to show him something,
you know, as opposed to him...
him always showing me.
In the beginning,
I embraced it,
and I bought all of the issues, but
I was finding it hard to read it.
Some of the characters struck me
as being stereotypical
and sort of making fun.
I mean, I loved Luke Cage,
and my cousins and I
would sit down,
and we would read Luke Cage,
and we would laugh,
and we would go,
"Nobody talks like this."
You know, I don't think
that Luke Cage
should be saying
"Sweet Christmas" all the time.
"Sweet Christmas!"
Really?
I knew there was a white guy
sitting back, writing
and penning this, going...
"What does a dude
from Harlem sound like?"
Black people have never been in control
of their own story in this country.
People should tell their own stories.
The one thing that comic
books always communicated to me
is two things,
heroes and possibilities,
and if you don't see yourself
as part of that,
then, you know,
who are the heroes,
and what are my possibilities?
When Derek and I
first started hanging out,
it was all about
reading comic books.
Eventually, it became about us
making our own comic books.
I don't even think we thought to copy
them or mimeograph them or anything.
We just sold the original art,
like, stapled together,
like, you know,
you can get your own comic.
The first characters we created
was a character called Black Vig,
and Jive was his partner,
and I remember thinking,
"These are
the coolest characters ever,
and one day they're gonna be famous."
I think at one point
Denys did say, you know,
"Wouldn't it be cool if we could
do this when we were older?"
That was the dream,
to somehow, someday,
make our own comic books.
We graduated.
Graduation day from P.S. 37,
my family, the day after,
moved to Norfolk.
Because he was my best
friend, it was unreal for me.
It was unreal. I didn't
think I would see him again.
Getting
on that Greyhound bus
and knowing that it's a possibility
I never would be connected
with my best friend again.
When I got into comics,
there were very few artists
who looked like me,
so I didn't have a whole lot
of examples to look up to.
The comic book industry in the
early 1970s wasn't diverse at all.
It was a bunch
of Jewish and Italian guys.
I'd say that DC was probably,
at that point, entirely white,
entirely white and male,
except for, you know, two women,
and then I upped the demographics
by being the third.
At the time, there were only a
few black artists and no writers.
I remember one black guy,
I can't remember his name,
who was in the production area,
and beyond that there was me.
Arvell was, like,
the living example
of a black person who made
his living drawing comics.
One day, this 14-year-old
kid came over to our apartment,
knocked on the door.
I opened it, and it was,
"Hey, you're Arvell Jones!
Hey, it's really great to meet you!"
and he just kind of
barges his way in,
threw down some of his artwork
and told me, "Hey, man,
I'll do whatever I could do."
Well, that kid was Denys Cowan.
He was an eager kid, and I thought,
that took a lot of guts to stick
his neck out to get what he wanted,
so he was always at the apartment
helping Arvell.
I wasn't drawing anything.
I was making coffee, running
errands, sweeping the floor.
I was a terrible assistant.
I think the only thing
I really wanted to do was draw.
Three years later, I was, like, 17.
I had a chance
to bring my portfolio
into the art director at DC
at the time.
He looks at my portfolio.
My heart's beating, I remember
that now. He says, "Good."
He handed it back, looked at me,
and he said, "These are good,
but we already have a colored
artist working for us."
At the time, I said, and strangely,
it was like, "Oh, okay,
so you're not hiring
any more black artists."
That's the only thing I thought.
I didn't realize how [bleep] up
it was until later.
After that, Jim Shooter at Marvel
hired me to draw Luke Cage...
- So Cage is trapped by the Halwan army...
- Right.
And he hired me
to do it because he thought
that I might be familiar
with the subject matter.
"You're black, so we're going to
give you this black [bleep] to do,"
so I got a chance to do Luke Cage,
which I had read
when I was a little kid.
After that, I had another opportunity
to draw the Black Panther.
Now, that was a big deal for me.
This is at the start
of my political awareness a bit.
That story was about the Black
Panther fighting apartheid,
and his South African neighbors
were being oppressed,
and what was he doing about it,
being the king of Wakanda?
Around that time,
I started to get recognized
throughout the industry.
It was a bit surreal. I even ended
up in an ad for Dewar's Scotch.
While I was at Marvel, I met
another black artist, Michael Davis.
I heard about Michael
from a mutual friend of ours.
Her name was Darlene.
Darlene said to me, "Michael,
you've got to meet Denys Cowan,"
because you're, like, only one
of three or four black people
working in the industry.
I don't understand
how it happened,
but we ended up being
very good friends.
From that point,
he became my boy,
and, quite literally,
introduced me to the industry.
It was 1983.
I came back to New York.
I got a job at Black Enterprise
as an associate editor.
One day in 1989,
I was on my way to work.
I see this 50th anniversary
Batman comic book,
and then I go to the artists.
It's Denys Cowan.
The very next day,
I called DC Comics.
"I have to find Denys Cowan."
I said, "You know what?
I'm going to go to Denys's house,"
and I rang the doorbell...
And I went to answer the
door, and there's Derek in a suit.
I guess I probably looked like,
you know, an IRS agent.
That's one of those movie moments, too.
You open the door
and your best friend, who you
haven't seen in 10 years or whatever,
is just standing there, going,
"Hey, what's up?"
New York City was insane.
The things that were going on
were crazy.
Bed-Stuy, Crown Heights...
We will not continue to pay
for people that abuse,
and murder, and maim us...
I mean, the '80s shaped what we did.
It's funny that my
start would be with a group of guys,
you know, and we're sort of
like a hip-hop X-Men, I guess.
For a lot of people,
the escape was music, whatever.
My escape was comic books.
Hip hop was emerging
in a very political way.
Public Enemy,
Tribe Called Quest...
Def Jam was rising.
Spike was creating, you know,
his production company.
"She's Gotta Have It,"
"Do the Right Thing,"
Malcolm X...
Spike Lee, for us,
was a major influence,
because Spike Lee did it himself.
In the comic book medium,
there was a absence of this voice.
99.9% of comic book
companies up to that point
had been owned and run
by white males.
My own inclination
was to create comics
that were more contemporary,
that, even though it was
a fantasy world,
we wanted it to look like
the world we lived in.
He was a brilliant person.
Not just a brilliant writer,
but a brilliant person.
Dwayne McDuffie was probably
the only black writer that I had met.
I met him because they had asked
me to do Deathlok at Marvel,
and he happened to be the writer.
I responded to his writing immediately.
My biggest issue, generally,
in writing mainstream comics is
if you write a black character,
he represents blackness,
and that's ridiculous.
That's way too much,
way too complex,
way too much weight
for any character,
any single character, to hold.
And we had both
gotten to the point where
we were frustrated at
the lack of characters
to express the things
that we wanted to express,
but that all changed in 1992.
I literally woke up one morning.
I thought, "This is it.
If I want a world where
there's black superheroes,
we're going to have to create
some black superheroes."
I got up and I called Michael Davis.
The idea was to create
a universe of characters
- that looked like us.
- "What do you think? Am I crazy?"
and he said, "You're crazy."
Every black kid who's ever wanted
to do comics has had that idea.
I told him, "The only way we're
going to see it is if we do it."
It was that time.
So the next person
we called was Dwayne McDuffie,
and Dwayne looked at both of us
and said, "You guys are crazy."
I'm like, "Nah, Dwayne,
we can do it because..."
whatever reasons I came up with,
I don't even remember,
and Dwayne said, "You're crazy, but
imma do it wit' you because you crazy,
but we'll do it, but you crazy."
Denys was committed from day one
to get Derek involved.
You know why? Because him and Derek
made up comic books
when they were kids.
How cool is that [bleep]?
Dwayne and Michael and I
knew nothing about business,
but we knew Derek wore a tie.
I always wore a suit,
even on Saturdays.
"Here's the idea," and I
pitched him the same thing.
He said, "You're crazy."
My response, of course, was,
"Denys, I have a job."
And he said, "Derek...
we have to do this.
You know,
people have marched and died
so that we can create these images."
From that point on,
the reservations, you know,
faded away.
We met constantly,
I drew a lot of pictures.
I probably designed
the whole universe.
I got a phone call
from Denys Cowan,
and I always wanted to do
something like this.
Christopher Priest
wrote some bible stuff.
Michael wrote some bible stuff.
I created most
of the background stuff,
and then I ran it all past Dwayne
McDuffie, who made it better.
Dwayne McDuffie
distilled all of it, rewrote it,
and made it fit into
this 28-page document.
On a Friday evening, I brought
that document over to DC Comics
right before Paul Levitz
had to go home,
and gave it to him in his hands.
Denys Cowan walked into my office,
we were friendly,
- and he had a nice thick bible...
- He couldn't put it down.
Every time he put it down,
he'd pick it back up.
So Monday morning,
he calls me up,
calls me on my phone and says,
"Denys, this is great.
We want to do it.
Come down and meet with us."
Boom.
It was euphoric.
It was exciting.
You know, we did pop the cork
on the Champagne,
but what was cooler than that
was when we went into our offices.
That made it real.
"Oh, my god, what does this
really all mean?"
That means that we had to deliver.
We all initially met at my
studio in Manhattan at the time.
We said, "Okay, if we're going
to create a comic book universe,
what do we need to do?"
and then we said,
"Well, we need archetypes,
like the Superman archetype."
Icon
is an African-American...
No, he's not. He actually is not.
Icon is an alien.
He crash-landed
here on Earth.
The pod being discovered,
but he wasn't discovered
by Ma and Pa Kent.
He was discovered by a slave.
It was important to us
to represent
there was no one monolithic
black point of view.
He's a Republican
because Lincoln freed the slaves,
and he's sticking with
what's working for him.
Icon had a sidekick, Rocket,
and Rocket was
the antithesis of Icon.
Rocket was a spitfire,
and young and energetic.
The book was told
through her point of view,
which was another Dwayne innovation.
You only saw the world
through her eyes.
If she didn't see it,
you didn't see it.
Genius...
just genius.
To see them having the
conversations that they were having,
to see Rocket challenge his
assumptions about class, and work ethic,
and the way in which you can pick
yourself up by your own bootstraps...
Reading that comic book became a
much more rich experience for me.
The next book
we released was "Hardware."
I loved Hardware
because he was just cool.
You know, he had that Tony Stark
kind of swagger to him.
Hardware is a technological genius
who works for a corrupt company,
Alva Industries,
and because he recognizes
the corruption in the company,
he decides to create the Hardware
armor and fight the corruption.
The first couple of pages
of the first issue,
there's this metaphor
of a caged bird...
Certainly, Dwayne
was writing about himself
and that frustration of working for
the man that doesn't appreciate you.
The next book we did
was a little different.
"What if we had a teenage kid,
and he's a black kid,
and he has nuclear powers?
No, what if he has speed powers?
Like, he's really...
No.
What if he has electric powers?"
He can control electricity,
and we'll call him "Static."
Static was interesting
because Static,
it was one of my favorite comics.
It was the most old-fashioned.
He spoke to
who the core demo was,
which was smart,
nerdy, black kids,
- or I guess the new phrase is "blerd."
- We made him a geek.
We made him a big science fiction fan,
like the four of us actually were
when we were that age.
The last thing we needed
was a superhero team,
because all great comic book
universes have a superhero team.
There's no other superhero team
like the Blood Syndicate.
All superhero teams
are basically like a gang anyway,
so why not just do a real gang?
I loved the diversity
of "Blood Syndicate."
You had gay, straight, lesbian,
African-American, Latino,
Native characters in a comic,
which you had never seen before.
There were a lot of
metaphors for police brutality,
drugs, and the ra... you know,
how drugs ravaged communities.
The Blood Syndicate
dealt with all of that.
Each of these
characters in that universe,
in the Milestone universe,
to a degree, because they
were black, had to eat crow.
They didn't turn their backs
on the greater good.
They still said, "Damn it,
this dude thinks I'm trash,
but let me go
and save this airplane."
There's never been
a good distribution chain
that was black-owned
or black-controlled,
or even particularly black-friendly.
They really wanted to be free
to do things very independently.
There's limits to how much
independence was possible
when they required both
distribution, economic support...
- It was challenging.
- We had complete editorial control.
- They could say no.
- If something offended DC's...
not principles, but sort
of DC's brand in some way,
I think we had the ability to say,
"Please don't publish that."
They had final approval of
what they were going to publish.
It was their money, their comic
book company, and everything else.
Meet the men of Milestone,
the newest division of DC Comics.
Dwayne McDuffie
is the editor in chief...
We want to give people
that shock of recognition I got
the first time I saw a black superhero,
and I went, "Wow," you know?
"I could do this.
I could be Superman."
20 years ago, there
were two titles being published
by a major publisher
that had black lead characters,
until this week,
where everything changed.
History changed this week.
The books
were as good or better
than anything else on the stands,
and I read them not out of
some sense of obligation,
but because I wanted
to read the books.
These Milestone comic books
are really dope, man.
I got, I got this, um,
Blood Syndicate, man.
They've got all kind of people in here.
What you got?
Icon, man... Oh, he looks hell.
What you got, Dre?
- I got Hardware, man, all three issues, man.
- Yeah?
It's hard to say
what numbers we expected
from the Milestone comics,
but they were really good.
We've got these jackets
with "M" on the back, right?
It's like, you walk
through a convention back then
with that "M" on your back, man,
it's like you're a Beatle,
because we did something
that no one else could even
imagine getting done.
Sometimes you didn't know
who would be coming into the office.
You know, one day
it'll be John Singleton,
another day it'd be Quincy Jones.
Clarence Thomas,
the Supreme Court judge,
- wrote Derek a fan letter.
- You know, because of Icon...
In fact, invited me to his chambers.
It was amusing to us,
and a little strange,
that Clarence Thomas would say
this was his favorite book.
Now I think about it, I'm like,
Well, yeah, he liked Icon,
who was just a conservative dude.
I moved to New York City
to work for Milestone specifically.
I knew that they were making history.
They knew me
as the white guy at Milestone.
I ended up doing some of the
most exciting work of my life.
Dwayne had
a very strong point of view
that he wanted
to get across editorially.
Dwayne had this unshakable
moral code.
It created some...
some challenges,
because in some situations,
in terms of business,
there needs to be,
you know, compromise.
When things are going well,
you know, you kind of rolling
along, and it's all good.
It's only when things are not going so well
that you start taking stock
that maybe this wasn't
what we thought it was.
There was
a political heart to Milestone.
Dwayne McDuffie
has always been political.
His books have always been political.
His stories have
always been political.
He was an activist.
Two questions
Dwayne always asked in a story.
One is, "What's the worst thing
that can happen?"
and the other is, "What if
this was really happening?
How would it play out?"
Well, in Icon and Rocket,
we had Rachel get pregnant,
at 14, so it was
a teenage pregnancy,
so we were dealing with, like,
kind of heady stuff for 1992.
It was to address a certain reality
that has never been reflected
in comics before.
We got into some kind of
controversy about that.
We published a lot of stuff that
made them very uncomfortable,
which always sort of amused me
because they weren't as uncomfortable
when they dealt with those topics.
Well, it was largely Dwayne's job
that we would butt heads with.
He thought that
they can't tell us what to do.
"They hired us
for a specific point of view,
and if they're not going to let
us do this, then why are we there?
We have to do this, and we have
to do it, we're making a point."
I felt it was unnecessary.
Denys, I think, was starting
to butt heads with Dwayne more.
They're... they're
two different people.
It wasn't that he was
more of an idealist.
It was just that I was
a little bit more practical.
I knew there was
a lot of internal tension,
and the friendship
and the partnership started to unravel.
Probably the biggest...
the biggest actual fight that we had
was an issue of Static.
The incident
that happened was
that we wanted to show safe sex
on a Static Shock cover.
It sounds like something
we'd have an argument about.
The way we were going to do that
was to show condoms
in a wrapper on the cover.
On the cover, he's
making out with his girlfriend.
There's no flesh exposed,
but they're going at it pretty good.
The idea
of a black teenage superhero
having sex with his girlfriend and
using cond... That was a lot for DC.
You can imagine. There was a lot of
Pepto-Bismol being had at DC that day.
I remember there was one...
one issue of one of the books
where we had a fairly energetic
disagreement about the cover art,
and we asked them to make changes.
They were very frustrated by that.
That was a huge, huge fight,
and I think a lot of it,
it wasn't about sexuality.
It was about black sexuality.
He didn't like it at all.
You know, when they decided to censor
that particular issue of Static Shock,
he fought back.
He fought back pretty hard.
Even though they said
that we couldn't do it,
somehow in between the stage
of where they approved it
and when we sent it to the printer
after getting it back,
somewhere between
Dwayne McDuffie
and whoever else
was working with him,
through some kind
of bait and switch,
the condom
was back on the cover,
but that's not what
the issue was ever, really.
The issue was the editorial
that accompanied the cover,
and the editorial page started talking
about the injustices
that were done to us,
and how was it racist to not
show condoms on the cover,
and this and that and the other,
and I think that people at DC,
Paul and other people,
got very upset at that,
reading about themselves
in an editorial page of Milestone
and how unfair they were,
because they had been paying
for this whole thing.
I felt it was their money.
I really did.
I felt it was unnecessary.
I felt we could have gotten
what we wanted
without going through the "Let's put
it on the cover based on principle,"
because what happened
after that was... not good.
Mysteriously, payments that
were due to Milestone kind of dried up,
and we kind of had a
little bit of trouble.
Paul's response was...
dispassionate and direct.
"If this is the way you feel
about how we treat you,
then we're going
to no longer treat you
like we were treating you before.
We will treat you in this new way,"
and that's when things became
very hard for Milestone.
Soon after that cover incident
is when I left,
and didn't discuss it with anybody,
and it was just... it was just
a very bad situation for me,
handled not very well by me.
Derek, I don't know what Derek said.
I think he was disappointed,
because I just made the move.
There was no hard,
long discussion with Derek,
because at that time,
I wasn't having any conversations
with Dwayne and Derek
about anything.
My friendship with Michael continued,
but not with Dwayne and Derek,
not at all.
I would talk to Dwayne on
the phone every once in a while.
"Hey, man, how's it going?"
and everything, and he would say,
"Oh, man, it's always a fight."
At the time,
the whole comics industry was...
not collapsing, but it was definitely
changing and imploding and shrinking.
I mean, Derek was doing the best he
could to keep everything together.
Milestone was dealing
with the challenges of the industry.
They ended up moving
to DC Comics
and working
out of DC Comics' offices,
but once you're doing that, it's over.
The Milestone line, along with a
number of other lines, were cut.
I don't know whether
we broke the news to them
or they broke the news to us.
We just weren't able to make
it work in the marketplace.
I think that they just
ran into losing sales,
and "These guys are difficult
to work with anyway."
At the time when... when
they were considering
what to do with Milestone,
that was part of it.
It pissed me off because
sometimes they don't know what...
what was missing until you
jump up and scream loud enough,
and that's what was the bummer
about Milestone stopping,
was... was there was
a voice that was silenced.
It's sad, because Milestone is the
greatest thing to ever happen...
Milestone's the greatest thing
to ever happen to comics
since the Black Panther.
I think when you see comics
fans talk about Milestone now,
they often talk about Milestone
as some sort of failed experiment.
It's always been my argument
that Milestone comics didn't fail,
but that comics failed Milestone.
Milestone is not a failure
by any stretch of the imagination.
There's a lot of folks
who not only got their career started,
but got a crash course in storytelling
and business from Milestone.
How many people
did Milestone Media hire?
How many artists got
their start at Milestone Media?
How many writers?
How many illustrators?
That's passed on
through all of these artists,
probably hundreds of artists.
Milestone was not
a failure to me
because the things that we created,
and the characters that we created
are forever.
About three years after
Milestone stopped publishing it,
a producer pal of mine pitched the
idea of doing Static to Kids' WB.
Basically, I got a phone call, and said,
"Would you mind if we did
Static as a TV show?"
and, you know,
I thought about it and said yes.
Static Shock the animated series
was an extraordinary success.
The first day
that Static was on television,
more people saw it than read
all of 45 issues combined.
The creative process
was mostly Denys and Dwayne.
At that point,
they patched things up a little bit.
I remember talking to Dwayne,
and he said, "You know what?
There are some things
I can never forgive Denys for,
but I can sure as hell work with him."
We worked together on Static
Shock, and once again we got along famously
professionally, but personally,
it was a lil... it was a little trickier.
Because I was friends
with everybody,
even when people weren't getting along,
I was talking to everybody.
After the success of Static Shock,
Dwayne and Denys, I hear,
were talking about a reboot
of the whole Milestone line.
I felt it was important
because these characters
needed to be seen again
by an entirely new generation,
by the generation that
missed them and by their kids.
That's when the germ of the idea
about bringing it back started.
I was excited to say,
"Okay, let's get together,"
again, we're scheming
on how to revive Milestone,
the whole thing,
and then it was over.
I get a call from his wife
saying that Dwayne
was in the hospital.
Dwayne had had a heart attack.
He had surgery.
He had come out of surgery...
So we all thought he was
going to be fine and that he was fine.
He sent me an email
from the hospital,
and it was picture of Static Shock,
the action figure
that was going be produced...
"Look what we created.
Look what we did,"
and then the next day,
he was dead.
It was like...
...somebody just hit me
and took all the air out of me.
I turned on the computer,
and it said Dwayne McDuffie was dead.
You know, I always
thought that Dwayne didn't realize
how much of an impact
his work had on people.
I mean, I can say
beyond a shadow of a doubt,
Dwayne McDuffie,
I owe a massive debt to.
What he has given to comics,
what he has given to animation,
can't be overstated.
So many people
coming to us and saying,
"This needs to come back.
There's still a void."
And it was
that pivotal moment
where you just go,
"Well, we just can't let it end."
We had a memorial service
shortly after Dwayne's death.
I was fine
until I saw Dwayne's mom.
When I saw his mom,
and we started talking about her son,
that's when I broke down,
and she knew what kind of
rocky relationship we had...
but none of that mattered, you know?
None of that mattered.
What mattered was what we had
done, and what we had shared,
and the devastating loss.
People were
starting to disperse,
and I called Denys and Reggie,
and I remember saying,
"We can't let this die.
This is too important."
That's when the germ of the
idea for bringing it back started.
It was time.
Reggie Hudlin said, "We should talk."
"We can't just let it end like this.
We can't let it end
at a memorial service."
Denys shook his head
as he's always shook his head, "I'm in."
I called Derek
two days after.
We kind of patched things up
and we talked about it,
and I apologized for any of my...
miscalculations on how...
how I should have behaved,
and he accepted my apology,
and I really meant it,
because Dwayne's gone...
and it won't be the same,
but to me...
it's just as imperative now to...
to... to build this again,
and he agreed.
Got some huge news at the Con.
Milestone Comics is coming back,
and Reginald Hudlin
is part of all of this, and...
After Dwayne McDuffie passed
away, I met with Reggie Hudlin,
who had been invited into
the Milestone Media Group,
so we took a number
of meetings with him and Denys,
and really just talked about the future
of Milestone and these characters,
and we saw that there was
an incredible missed opportunity
not having
these characters out there.
Everyone at DC was excited about
the idea of bringing it back to life.
This is going to be
a new Milestone Media.
It's not a matter of doing
what we did before.
It's about defining what
Milestone Media means now.
Hardware is making
another appearance,
Blood Syndicate,
we're relaunching Static Shock.
We're relaunching Icon and Rocket.
But the most exciting part
is that we have a whole bunch
of new characters
that people are not ready for
and they have not expected.
Who would have imagined that
there would be so many changes in fandom,
where you have people really
demanding diversity and inclusivity,
so the industry has changed
quite a bit,
and, frankly, it was the right
time for DC to do this right now.
There's definitely
been an evolution and progress
since I was a child.
Not only have we come such a long way
that Black Panther,
the movie is even being made.
It's going to be a tent-pole movie.
I'm so glad we're making
the Black Panther movie now,
and it's going to be just
the way I had envisioned it,
and I can't wait to see it.
I'm still not sure what I am.
To have Luke Cage on Netflix is,
that's some powerful [bleep].
When I heard they were
making the Luke Cage,
you know, I was a little
apprehensive at first.
It's you.
Yeah, it's you.
Sweet Christmas.
I've watched little black kids
dressed up as Thor
and Captain America and Batman
and Superman for years.
Last year, I saw little white kids
dressed up as the Black Panther.
That, to me, is way more progress
than anything I... I can...
I can quantify.
I don't see any way
you can look this renaissance
not paying homage
to Milestone Media.
They made it okay
to be black and dream.
United we fight!
This is a world that needs
Milestone Comics in it.
It needs that example.
Milestone was a badge of honor.
It represented a change
in the industry.
I must say, it's the most exciting
thing that I've ever done in my life,
other than growing up next to Denys
with a stack of comic books
from my brother's collection.
It's, um... it's been quite a journey.
It's been quite a journey.
Being able to work with
Derek again means more to me
than, you know, anyone
could possibly understand.
It's...
It's as it should be,
because we started this together,
so, you know, we're going
to continue this together.
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~