sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~
For half a century of comics,
there were only two shops in
town, Marvel and DC,
and if you weren't working
for one of those,
you just weren't working.
I went in on day one hoping I'd
work for Marvel for 25 years.
I just found out
that I wasn't wired that way.
At some point,
you have to just say "no."
A bunch of
Marvel artists who were, like,
"Not for nothing, but we think
we could do this on our own."
We didn't know
what we were doing exactly,
but we knew
it was time for a change.
None of us knew
how this was gonna work,
or if it was gonna work.
I said, "Remember that avalanche
we've been talking about all summer?
I think it just became an atomic bomb."
It was crazy.
It was a mini revolution.
It was like that
"I don't give a [bleep] " attitude
that kind of, I think, spoke to me.
They were balls-to-the-wall
with it.
And out of this crazy experiment
came some of the biggest titles
in the last 25 years...
but what these guys didn't realize
is that what
they were doing selfishly
would actually go on
to change the industry forever.
_
When I was 12 years old, I'm
reading comics all hours of the day.
Comics were hugely important to me.
I start noticing
these names in the books.
There are artists behind these books
and they're all super talented,
and I gotta follow these guys.
Late '80s, early '90s, man,
it was the artists' medium,
and artists ruled the roost,
and all the best artists
were collected at Marvel.
You got your Marc Silvestri,
your Erik Larsen,
Jim Valentino...
but there were three undeniable
superstars at the time,
Rob Liefeld,
Todd McFarlane,
and Jim Lee.
Those three guys
were drawing comics
unlike they'd been drawn
up until that point,
making the page-turns
so much more exciting
as you would
go through these books.
We broke the mould
of very static storytelling.
I remember the day that I heard
"Smells Like Teen Spirit"
by Nirvana,
and the strum of the guitar and
the entire sound of that song,
and how different it was,
and powerful and commanding.
That's what
we were doing on the page.
We had a very new sound
in comics.
I was a huge Marvel fan growing up,
and so that was my dream,
to work at Marvel
and to work on the X-Men.
You have to figure out
how to get people to see you,
and the way to do it is style.
Look at how Todd McFarlane
can draw Spider-Man
in this completely dynamic way
that nobody else has before,
and you're talking about
a character
that had been around for decades.
Suddenly, Todd McFarlane
was putting his knees
over his ears...
Spider-Man's, not Todd McFarlane's,
and it was dynamic.
McFarlane, Liefeld, and Lee
were really coming up strong.
Their work was being recognized,
and they were very important to the
company. They sold a lot of books.
Most days at the New York
Stock Exchange, the joint is jumping.
Marvel Comics has enjoyed some
pretty heroic sales of late,
an average of
8.7 million comics a month.
Todd had just relaunched Spider-Man,
one of the best-selling comics
of all time.
Jim Lee had just done X-Men,
which, I think,
is the best-selling comic book
of all time.
Rob had relaunched X-Force.
We'd had
the greatest financial success
and the greatest unit sales
in the history of comics.
I don't think
that will ever be broken.
If one's goal is to break into
one of the top two
comic book companies
and work on the book
that you loved as a kid,
it felt pretty good.
It felt like it was
a pretty big achievement.
I'd always wanted to work
for Marvel Comics,
since I was a kid buying their
books from the liquor store.
I never took it for granted.
Every day was exciting.
I went in on day one hoping I'd
work for Marvel for 25 years.
I just found out
that I wasn't wired that way.
I think that
everybody watching now knows
why we call this series
"A Visit with
the Comic Book Greats."
The problem with comics at the time
is that DC and Marvel kind of had
a monopoly on what creators could do.
If you didn't want
to work at Marvel anymore,
you could kind of cross the street
and go work at DC,
but if you didn't want
to work with either of them,
there weren't really
a lot of options for you.
I created characters for Marvel,
like Deadpool,
Cable, X-Force
that are still going strong today.
You know when you're in the zone.
I was in the zone,
but suddenly I was hearing
from Marvel, you know,
"Well, maybe we should
go this way or that way."
I'm like, "Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, now I'm not driving
the car anymore?"
You know, there's nobody that's...
that's indispensable.
They can't be.
The characters
are the most indispensable part.
That's what the business was built on.
So the book I'm doing
is now selling more
than any book in the country.
When I first walked
in the office, years ago,
when it wasn't in the top 20,
they're going, "Help us!"
And then I take it to the top,
I set records,
and now they're going,
"We'll take over now, Todd," and...
"Because it's too popular."
In my world, the characters
had to come first,
and, you know, Spider-Man
has to do certain things...
and he can't do certain things.
We used to tell advertisers
and merchandisers
that "Spider-Man
will never disappoint you.
He'll always do
what he's supposed to do."
So you go,
"I don't think this elevator
goes any higher here.
I've reached the top
of my opportunities here."
I had read the stories, and the
one that had the biggest impact
was that they had
taken advantage of Jack Kirby.
Jack "The King" Kirby,
that was his nickname,
ladies and gentlemen.
Jack Kirby actually
co-created 90% of the Marvel universe.
We don't want to be the ones
that create a kingdom of characters
and then feel unhappy
with the way we were treated.
I was on the phone with
both Erik, but mostly Rob Liefeld, a lot.
Todd told me once,
"Ugh, you're calling me again?
You call me
more than my mother,"
and I was like, "Uh, I don't
know how to take that,
but I'm just going to keep talking."
The germ of the idea
was as simple as Rob just
wanted to do his own stuff...
any way he saw fit.
Same with Erik,
same with myself.
I decided I was going
to publish my own comic,
and it was called The Executioners.
I had a big emphasis
on the "X" in "Executioners."
He'd taken out a one-page
ad in the Comics Buyer's Guide.
It was just a bunch of characters
that he had come up with.
I was so excited! I wrote my
check. I bought my ad.
I'm gonna get a full-page foldout
ad in the Comics Buyer's Guide,
which, The Comics Buyer's Guide
was a huge weekly
comic book newspaper.
And Marvel flipped out.
They were giving him angry phone
calls, and, at that point...
it was sort of
blood in the water, you know?
We could see, like, "Oh, these
guys are... these guys are scared,"
and that,
probably more than anything,
was the genesis of Image Comics.
The whisper mill
of the comic book community
was a very strong and powerful thing.
Rob was on the phone
all the time with Todd,
and Rob was on the phone with Erik.
Something big was going to happen,
but he couldn't talk about it
and didn't really know
what shape it was going to take.
We talked
about launching a label,
and I said, "I'm ready to go.
I'm ready to do this now."
We're going to get together,
Erik, Rob, Todd,
and we're gonna have our books.
Now, Rob says, "Hey, I've got
a buddy, Jim Valentino.
Is it okay
if he comes along for the ride?"
Sure, what the heck?
We've got four.
The more the merrier to me.
- We're now a boy band.
- Todd took over,
and I asked him, I said,
"Are you really gonna do this?"
and he said "Yeah,"
and I said, "Okay, then I'm in."
Most of us were
still working at Marvel Comics,
so we didn't talk in the open
about this.
Definitely there were
secretive conversations.
It was definitely, like, how
many guys can we draw into this,
and how big can we make this?
Now, at this point, we've involved
Jim Lee, but he won't commit.
I'd been at Marvel for about five years.
I got to work on the characters
I loved as a kid.
I did very well by them.
- Jim... was adored by Marvel.
- We were the bad boys.
Mwah!
He was the golden boy.
Nice kid, best art,
best-selling book for Marvel.
They expected us to do something
stupid, but not Jim, you know?
Nobody expected Jim to do it.
Todd McFarlane had suggested
we bring Marc Silvestri onboard,
and I'm gonna tell you,
Marc is the premier illustrator
of our generation.
So Todd and I are in New York City,
and in the hotel lobby
where we were staying,
Marc Silvestri's right there.
"Do you have half an hour?"
He goes, "Yeah, yeah, yeah."
It's about 11:30 at night,
and I give him the best
sales pitch I've ever given.
The way that Todd sells things,
and he's a great salesman,
is that you just
don't want to be left behind.
"Look at these Marvel
and DC guys," you know?
"Look what they did
to Jack Kirby," you know?
It was like,
"He gets nothing," you know?
"He gets nothing!
We get nothing!
This time, we've got something."
You know?
It was genius.
I was like, "I'm onboard."
Rob Liefeld, myself, and Todd,
and we were all
in New York City
because we had
some artwork of ours
that was being
auctioned off at Sotheby's.
And I run into Jim Lee,
and Jim goes, "Todd!"
He goes,
"What are you doing?"
I sort of told him
what we were doing,
and he goes,
"Wow. Let me think about that."
I appear to be
a fairly nondescript person,
but there, in my heart,
I really like doing
things that other people
wouldn't try to do.
A few hours later, he phones
me up, and he goes, "Todd...
You mind if... You mind if I join?"
and I go,
"What? We've got the Golden Boy?...
Yeah, you can come."
Once Jim made that move, the
train was off and running.
- Hey.
- How are you doing?
- How's it going, bud?
- Hey, what's up?
Jim wanted Whilce to join,
so everybody just went,
"Yeah, sure."
I get a call from Jim Lee,
and he says, "Hey, look,
there's something happening,
and we'd like you to be part of it,
but, uh,
I can't tell you about it,
but, you know, if you can,
think about it."
Four, five, six, seven...
We just grabbed three X-Men guys.
That was... That was the
best-selling books at that point. Wow.
Basically,
all of the Spider-Man office
and all of the X-Men office
is now combining
into one new publishing label.
That... was exciting.
That was very exciting.
Todd had decided
that he wanted
to formally inform Marvel
that we were leaving,
which I didn't understand,
but if he was gonna do it,
I'm going too.
I'm gonna be part of that ride.
So Jim and I went along.
Marvel was closed for the day.
I just remember walking
through the dark bullpen,
and there was Terry's dark room.
That might've been the first
time I ever went to his office,
maybe the second.
It was supposed
just to be us and Terry.
By coincidence,
the Editor-in-Chief happened
to be going to get a coffee.
"Oh! What are you guys
doing here?"
I did stumble in, in that I wasn't
intentionally going to a meeting.
You know, I just showed up,
knocked on the door,
and was invited in.
They weren't happy.
They really wanted control
and a very large
percentage of the profits,
and basically I said,
"That's not gonna happen."
I'm sure we all have our warped sense
of what happened in that meeting.
My memory goes something like this.
"We're here to say we are
leaving Marvel Comic Books.
We're just telling you why we're
leaving, and if you don't do something,
you may have
another seven tomorrow."
Terry's trying to come up with
solutions to what he perceived
as our discontent, and
Todd was having none of it.
Todd told him
about how his dad,
when he worked at the factory,
they gave him a watch.
"They gave my father a watch
for his work."
Like, "We don't even get a watch,
not even a watch from Marvel Comics,"
and I was like, "A watch?
What the hell?"
I think Jim... It was the first time
Jim Lee had heard about the watch.
I don't think I said much,
other than "That's interesting."
Was I surprised?
Yeah, I was a little shocked.
I had shareholders
that would ask me,
"What are you gonna do now that
you lost your top three artists?"
We left the meeting.
Just like a movie, as the
elevator doors are closing,
Tom DeFalco's on the outside,
and his last words to us were,
"Hey, if it doesn't work out,
you've always got a home!"
And I remember I looked at Jim,
and I just went,
"Wow...
They think we can't do this."
Marvel Entertainment
fell three and a quarter today.
Eight artists are jumping ship
for a competitor.
Some investors did the same.
The industry trades
were writing Image's obituary
from the moment they got the
press release announcing its birth.
Marvel and DC, at the time,
essentially had a monopoly.
They controlled distribution,
they controlled printing,
they controlled the retailers
to a certain extent,
so the idea that another company
could be formed that could
actually compete with them was
absolutely unheard of at the time.
We represented
a generational shift.
What united us for several years
was the industry rising up against us.
You know, I'll confess. I didn't
think Image Comics was gonna last.
We actually had professionals
dissing us publicly.
"Ah, these guys, bunch of losers,
bunch of idiots, a bunch of..."
"So unappreciative."
None of us knew how this was gonna
work, or if it was gonna work.
I had put every dime I had
into a down payment on a house.
There was no precedence
to speak of.
There was nothing that
we could turn to and say,
"Well, these guys made it huge."
It had been quite the opposite.
What I told my wife at the time
was I either made
the worst mistake
I've ever made in my entire life,
or I made the best call
and we're just going to have
to wait to see which one it was.
February 1st, 1992,
our very first meeting.
We were supposed to say,
"Here's the book we're gonna do."
We had to get practical.
Were we confident, cocky, or smug?
I would say all the above,
if you mixed us all together.
The thing that people
should be aware of
is there was no group-think
going into this.
We only had two rules...
and the first rule
that was that Image Comics
Incorporated would own nothing, ever.
The other rule was that we would
never get in one another's way,
- as far as business went.
- Everybody had a different agenda.
Todd was out to make
an anti-Marvel statement,
but I just wanted the freedom
to do whatever I wanted.
None of us considered this might
be a problem down the road.
The book that I launched Image
with was called Youngblood.
Youngblood is a
celebrity-focused superhero team.
My first book at Image was called
WildC.A.T.s,
Covert Action Teams,
a group of espionage agents that
were after superpower villains.
I created Spawn,
the character that today, I still do.
Spawn is a man who's died.
He's back, but it's five years later.
Savage Dragon was this
super-powered police officer.
He was just a guy who kicked ass.
That's all I wanted.
My book for Image
was Cyber Force,
mutants with
cybernetic enhancements.
It...
You know, it was my X-Men.
I did a book called Shadowhawk.
I've never bought into the
"superheroes don't kill" idea.
Well, he didn't kill.
He... he maimed.
The first Image comic book
to be published was Youngblood,
and as I sent it off to the printer,
there was a lot of buzz building,
and we had no idea
where it was gonna end up.
This may look like
any other Hollywood premiere,
but this one is unusual
even by Hollywood standards.
It's for the hippest
new comic book, Youngblood.
Observers say it could be the
next Superman or Spider-Man comic.
Youngblood definitely
changed everything.
We knew it was gonna work.
We didn't know
it was gonna "really work."
Then Spawn comes out...
Bam! Even more sales.
Then Dragon comes out,
does tremendous.
Then WildC.A.T.s comes out,
almost as much as Spawn.
I mean, it was just
hit after hit after hit.
I remember when Spawn came out,
and that was just...
That was a jawbreaker for me.
It felt like, you know,
Wu Tang Clan
came out at that time, too,
and they came out
with that gnarly-ass video
where they didn't
have pupils in their eyes.
It was just a vibe, you know?
They really were able to capture,
I think, the '90s really well,
for me, as a teenager,
'cause I was kind of dark.
Everything
that was coming out of Image
that first, I'll say, six
months or a year, phenomenal!
For 13-year-olds like me,
the news that all those guys
were jumping ship at Marvel
and forming their own company
and creating new characters
was super exciting.
- But you've read comics?
- I loved comics when I was young.
- Oh, cool, okay.
- But this one is so different.
I'm seeing cats get
out of bed with women?
- That never happens.
- Hey... Yeah, well...
The seismic impact that it had...
It affected everyone.
It was impossible not to see
how suddenly, how overnight,
there was this major player,
and it was like the inmates
had taken over the asylum
for a little bit.
One of our focuses was on production.
We were going
to make the books look
as good as
we could possibly make them.
Jim's manager at the time said,
"I'm gonna bring in
some Mac computers."
- "Cool!"
- "And we're gonna do this PhotoShop thing.
- Whilce, can you learn it?"
- "Yeah!"
So if you look around this store,
you'll see that all these comics
are colored digitally.
That had never been done
prior to Image Comics.
We printed
our comics on better paper,
so the actual comic books themselves
looked better, felt better.
Some of that
was just creative ego, frankly.
They wanted their books
to be the best.
In August of 1992,
Image Comics became
the number-two comic company.
We became the number-two
comic company with seven comics.
DC, with their 60 comics that month,
was number three.
We were in Wall Street
Journal, we were in magazines.
We had our own tent
at Chicago Comic-Con.
That's when we all kind of went,
"Really? This is kind of crazy.
Kind of cool, but kind of crazy."
The fun
we were having was ridiculous.
We had three of the biggest
creators in comics, ever,
and the fans could start at
ground zero, which was a big thing.
Within Image Comics, we each
created our own separate studios.
My studio was Extreme Studios.
Jim's was WildStorm,
and then later on,
Marc would create Top Cow.
We went after some of the most
talented guys in the business,
and I'd say, "So,
what are you getting a page?
You getting $30 a page?
I'll pay you $300."
It... ended the discussion.
This becomes the moment, too, where
"be careful what you wish for."
It's great making the
toys that you want...
so great,
I made some for myself!
Spawn, from Todd Toys.
With the success
that we were experiencing,
I was able to do
some creative things...
For instance, go off and get one of
the top special effects prosthetics
designers in the business to
create a seven-foot Badrock costume.
And then, like, "Well,
what are you gonna do next?"
"Make a spaceship."
We decided, okay, well,
Todd's got the Spawnmobile,
he's got Spawn Alley, well,
we're gonna do the
Youngblood Battle Cruiser.
Fans would be able
to go in, sit in it,
they could pose
and have pictures taken in it.
It was awesome,
but they never factored in
how much it would cost
to actually break it down
and ship it
to the next convention.
You had to store the thing,
you had to set the thing up,
you had to cart the thing around...
it did nothing but cost money.
I sold it for virtually
pennies on the dollar
to a paintball park
here in Southern California,
but I was just happy
to get rid of it.
That's when
you have too much money.
We were just
these renegade punk kids
who were going off
and doing their own stuff,
and there was criticism of it
because not everything
that came about was...
completely awesome
right out of the gate.
There were books
that seemed to be empty and flashy,
there were books that had a
lot of possibility to them...
The one thing that they had
that clearly was an appeal
was the artwork.
Whether the stories
were good or not
didn't seem to be
a make-or-break factor.
We were novices as writers,
and we come out of the gate
with badly written books.
Okay, I'll concede it.
And we crushed it sales-wise.
Why? Because they liked our art,
and you know who that
bugged the most? The writers!
Image was playing to the era
and its strengths.
The men looked like they could
kill you with a pinkie,
and the women looked like
they suffered chronic back pain.
The breasts on some of them
were of terrifying dimension.
I mean, the joke is "pouches."
Everybody had 90 different
thigh straps full of...
I don't know
what they carried in there,
- like, lip balm, maybe?
- Yes, the work was juvenile,
and, yes, the work was aimed
at 14-year-old boys,
but I was a 14-year-old boy,
and 95% of the audience,
if not more at that point,
was 14-year-old boys.
I was a girl,
and I still loved Image Comics.
It was like that
"I don't give a [bleep] " attitude
that kind of, I think, spoke to me.
I never really cared
what people thought.
I was just happy
that Image Comics existed,
because it had a voice
that I resonated with.
People at this convention
in San Diego, California
know something many of us don't.
Over the past 10 years, some
of the most popular comics
have become hot investments.
I don't buy expensive books.
I buy ones
I think will become expensive.
By the time I retire, I'll liquidate
everything and retire comfortably.
A lot of Image Comics
and a lot of comics in general
back then
was fueled by the speculator
market... and we knew that.
I remember having
this conversation with Jim Lee
about "how long do you think
this is gonna last?"
Speculators
were buying comics in droves,
just people were filling up
basements with boxes of comics
that they thought were gonna
put their kids through college.
You could sell
a million copies of a comic book
just by showing people a cool-ass cover
and saying it had "number one" on it.
You know how many alternate
Spider-Man "number one" covers
I got, man? It's crazy.
I've got the platinum one,
the holographic-type paper one...
I've got the one with the card in it.
I've got the one with
the certificate in the back.
These are two separate
posters, the same book,
- but different editions of the same book.
- Right.
Image...
Image was part of it.
As an entire industry,
we took advantage of our consumer.
You never, ever want to do that.
Why? They will...
they will just leave you.
By the mid '90s, sales
were down across the board,
including at Image,
but they were still a major
presence in the industry,
but readers had no idea what
was going on behind the scenes.
Image Comics
was born of rivalries.
Rivalries are great.
They drive people.
I would say that the six of us
were closer to being brothers.
You're always in competition
with your brother.
If we were guilty of anything back in
the early days of Image, it was hubris.
Marvel and DC
weren't really our concern,
because people were gonna
buy Marvel books
and they were gonna
buy DC books.
So who was gonna
be our competition?
- My partner is my competition.
- It was like frat houses...
Fighting each other
over ideas, over people.
Who gets the new hot kid
that now walks into the studio?
And if I do have a hot kid
that I nurture,
and you then give him more
money than I'm giving him,
should we be
doing that to each other?
Giving people that freedom,
I think, was part of Image.
It's, like, that's what we wanted.
The autonomy that we had set up
was also beginning
to be the source
of all of our tensions.
In 1996,
Jim Lee and myself
were contacted by Marvel Comics
to come back and bolster some
of their classic characters
who had fallen on hard sales times.
They said, "Look,
these characters are suffering.
We want your help in sort of restoring
some shine to the characters."
I thought it was a big win
and a cool opportunity.
These were characters I hadn't really
worked on while I was at Marvel.
You know, that was when...
as opposed to the early days
of Image, people needed money.
Marvel came and basically
cash-whipped Jim Lee and Rob...
And it's just, like,
now it's just about the cash!
Like, oh, my gosh, now we're
administering even more,
because now it's like I can be bought.
When the news of Heroes Reborn
reached the other partners,
they were very upset.
It was the first time things
were getting openly ugly,
and you're like, "Oh, we're not
being polite to each other anymore.
This is...
These guys are pissed."
I sat next to Todd on a panel
when all the questions
for Jim and I that summer
were about our deal with Marvel.
He lost his cool.
He yelled at the fans.
"This is for Image!
There will be a panel later
where you can talk to them
about Marvel!"
This was getting to the point where
it just... it wasn't fun at all.
Under the Image Comics deal, I
owned all the books that I created,
so I began to publish them
under another company I created
called Maximum Press.
The other owners
were not happy about that,
because they actually saw that
as competition to Image.
Todd sent me a letter that said,
"If you do not bring these books
back from Maximum Press,
we are going to take
legal action against you,"
and I responded with, "I don't care.
I'm not bringing them back."
Our pages are actually 10 by 15,
which is about the size of Rob's ego.
There did
get to be certain arguments
that had taken place
with Rob Liefeld.
There ended up
being enough points of friction
that Marc Silvestri was like,
"Look, if this guy's gonna be here,
I got to go."
Extreme Studios went after one of
Marc's top guys, and Marc had had it.
You know, at that point,
it was, like,
"What are we doing here?
This is insanity."
I just couldn't live
in that environment anymore.
I got a letter
pushed under my door
by the publisher of Image Comics
that Marc has resigned.
Now, I'm not stupid.
I knew that that was ramping
up hostilities, and...
but I-I got to tell you, I didn't care.
Todd called me, and we talked...
and I said, "I can't deal
with the B.S. anymore."
And I go, "What if you're not
the one that goes?"
We were gonna meet
in a suite at the Marriott.
I wanted to do a little espionage.
I bought the room next to the suite,
and Matt and I stayed in that suite
and literally, we are
laying on the floor,
looking through the light in
the door, but I hear everything.
"I guess Rob's not coming."
They all kept waiting
for me to come into the room,
but I thought this would be
an honest assessment, you know,
and I hear Todd and Marc and Jim
and Erik and Jim Lee discuss me.
Valentino is reluctant,
Erik Larsen's pissed off at me,
Todd's like, "We've got to do
what we've got to do,"
Jim Lee is quiet,
and I was like, "Yeah, we're done."
Right before
we were going to vote him out,
Rob faxed in his resignation.
When the news broke
that Rob was leaving Image Comics,
it was like the Beatles breaking up.
You really got a sense that they
were all the best of friends,
and, you know, this was
kind of the first indication
that that wasn't true.
It was kind of heartbreaking.
I don't think
any of those decisions
were made lightly by any of us,
and, actually, he and Todd
were super close as friends,
and I'm sure that impacted
their friendship for a bit,
and it impacted
my relationship with Rob.
I didn't talk to him
for years after that.
I'm not proud
of that moment in our history.
We had success hard and fast.
The money came, you know...
It was just...
It was overwhelming.
The sales slump which
threatens to engulf the comic world
could be the one enemy
its superheroes cannot defeat.
Since peaking in the early 1990s,
over half of America's comic shops
have gone out of business.
About 1995, the speculator
boom crashed, as they do.
When the guys
who were planning to cash in
went into their local comic
book store and tried to cash in,
found out their store was gonna
give them 10 cents on the dollar,
then the bottom fell out.
Every year, the numbers were falling.
Every month,
the numbers were falling.
Every week, sometimes,
numbers were falling,
and nobody could really stop it.
The business was seemingly
kind of falling apart around us,
and also, I was just burned out.
That kind of got me thinking
about what it would be like
if I took WildStorm and
partnered with a bigger company.
Jim Lee took his company, WildStorm,
to DC Comics and sold it,
and eventually
became an executive there.
That was a shock.
When Jim sold to DC, that was a shock.
Rob's leaving, I think,
just leaves a bitter taste,
but Jim Lee was a bigger punch.
You know, Jim was Jim.
WildStorm was a massive studio.
They were our largest
market share within Image.
It was a big blow to us.
We were worried for a minute,
you know, would we survive?
and I think a lot of us
got kind of scared.
I think Image floundered for a bit
at the end of the '90s
and into the early 2000s.
Jim Lee leaving
sort of forced us to take on books
that we normally wouldn't.
We had lost some of the business
dealings with our distributor,
so we needed to get
our market share back up.
At first, we were taking on stuff
that we weren't overly proud of...
I volunteered to take over.
My idea was to get rid
of all the books, the ones
that I just thought
brought the company down,
and I told the guys,
"We can do better than this."
We started thinking in terms
of "we need to diversify."
You know, there's a market that's
not being catered to out there.
It's the "indie market."
Image started to take
a lot of chances artistically.
It wasn't always superheroes.
They were starting to find
new genres and new ways to go.
One of the guys
that walked in the door
- was a guy named Robert Kirkman.
- At that point in my career,
I had never done anything at all
that was successful,
and I wanted to do a zombie comic,
because I had been watching
tons of George Romero movies
and I'd fallen in love with
that genre, and I was like,
"Ah, there's so much more
you can do with this genre
that hasn't really been explored."
He pitched what he called
"Planet of the Zombies" to me,
and I was like,
"Oh, Robert, that's just horrible."
You know, and I said,
"Look, zombie books have never,
ever sold in this business.
I know their movies do okay, and I know
they're a niche thing and all that..."
Jim was basically
turning down the book,
and he said, "Unless you can
tell me how this is different
from every zombie book
that's ever been done,
there's no reason to do it."
There just was nothing
that would've given you the idea
that, like,
"Oh, we should do this book
because it's going
to be a huge success,"
especially from somebody
who had, you know, not...
a great track record up to that point.
And so, in the moment, I just go,
"Well, you know, there's, it's, I...
I didn't put it in the pitch,
'cause, you know, I wanted
to surprise you guys,
but the whole thing,
it's an alien invasion.
There's spaceships,
and they've created the zombies,
and they're trying to weaken
the world's infrastructure
so that they can take over,"
and I would later find out
that that is apparently the plot
from Plan 9 from Outer Space.
I didn't know that at the time,
and they didn't know that
at the time,
but they're like, "Yeah, no,
that's cool, that's... yeah!
Hey, that's the hook we're looking for.
Yeah, it's a good-looking book."
Done. Accepted.
The book's doing great,
and I'm loving it.
I'm reading every issue and,
at some point, I say,
"Robert," you know,
"You said you were salting
in all of this stuff
about the alien invasion.
Like, can you, like, point
out any of those things?"
So I just said, "Eric, I lied to you.
There's no aliens in this book,"
and he goes, "Oh, okay...
Meh. Probably better for it."
Walking Dead
has been a runaway success.
I mean, that comic book
started off with low numbers
and just kept building and building
and building ever since then.
There was really no...
no stopping it.
Spawn was always
the number-one book,
and then Walking Dead
kind of was getting there,
and I was like, "Oh, my god,
is this gonna happen?
Like, I don't know
what's gonna happen,"
and then, all of a sudden,
there was one month
where it was like, boop...
boop... boop. You know?
And it kinda like...
and then it... and it kept going,
and I was like, "I can't believe it.
I can't believe that
Walking Dead is outselling Spawn now.
This is crazy."
It became Image's best-selling
book in probably a decade.
I don't think you can overstate
the importance of the Walking Dead.
I think that it revitalized us, and
it's not just the book on its own,
but I think what it said about Image.
So then Robert Kirkman
becomes a partner
of Image Comic Books.
We needed to show that we were willing
to add to our ranks of partnership,
if you were loyal to us,
and you didn't
have to be an artist.
Becoming a partner
at Image Comics is probably...
you know, aside from my
children being born and meeting
my wife, like, the best thing
that ever happened to me.
The Walking Dead show is nice,
and it does very well,
and I'm very proud of it,
but I had dreams as a child of
being at an Image Comics meeting,
and then I became an Image partner,
you know, as an adult,
which is the stupidest
thing in the world.
I have to tell everyone
in the audience right now,
I love the gentlemen on this couch.
They were...
the most arrogant,
reckless maniacs,
who decided that they were gonna
start their own company,
and they were gonna build it
all around themselves,
and they were gonna do
whatever they wanted,
and for whatever reason, they were like,
"You know what?
Let's build a company
for all creators.
Let's make the deal
that we create for ourselves
that is the absolute
best deal in comics
and let's make it available
to everyone."
My kids now have the opportunity
to grow up
and be completely pampered,
and that is because of you guys.
Everything was going great,
I couldn't be more excited,
but there was one thing that
just wasn't sitting right with me
that I felt needed to be fixed.
Comics aren't a genre.
Comics are a medium.
One of the things
that Image has done, I think,
spectacularly well
in the last half-dozen years
is demonstrate
the strength of the medium.
I think for me, their legacy was... balls.
In American culture,
"to have balls" means
that you don't care what people think
and that you are willing
to express in all honesty
whatever it is that's on your mind,
and I think if there's
any legacy for Image,
it'll be that, that they were
balls-to-the-wall with it.
What they did
for the business for comics,
how they disrupted the way
things had always been
and who got to make the rules was
nothing short of revolutionary.
One of the things that Image brings
is a creator ownership deal
that is, in my opinion,
right and fair and proper.
They keep
the other publishers honest.
Everyone's page rates went up,
and then exclusive
contracts happened,
so now freelancers had security
and stability in their income.
The success of Walking
Dead took everyone by surprise,
myself included, and it
made people think, like,
if a weird black-and-white
zombie book can find success,
the sky is the limit.
There are a number of titles
that have come through Image
that could not possibly
have existed anywhere else.
Image Comics publishes Saga,
which is a romance story
set in a sci-fi universe
that is completely adult and
has people with TVs for heads,
but, you know, rivals
Walking Dead in popularity.
It's a massively successful book.
Pretty Deadly
is a mythological western.
It is not an obvious commercial success,
and they let us do it anyway,
which is... not capitalism.
I did a book called Sex Criminals
which literally could not exist
anywhere else but Image Comics.
This is the part of the show
where, like,
you can show different stuff
that I've done
and just the pages
will be completely pixelated
and pixelated and pixelated.
Literally, they said
I could do all that.
It's ironic that a
company that was founded
on bulging veins and pouches
and ammunition and women as props
is now publishing easily
the most progressive
and politically provocative
books on the scenes.
I met Robert Kirkman
at the 2003 Chicago Comic-Con.
You know, we start talking, next
thing I know, he's like,
"I gotta come to my room.
You want to come to my room?
I got to get something real quick,"
and we're chatting in his room,
and he's like, "I got to go
to the bathroom,"
and he goes to the bathroom and
leaves the bathroom door open,
and so I'm, you know,
a childhood fan of Rob Liefeld,
having known Rob Liefeld
for an hour.
I'm like, "I can't believe Rob Liefeld
is peeing four feet away from me,
and then he's like, "Oh,
you want to go to the movies?"
I'm like, "Yeah, I want to go to the
movies with Rob Liefeld." Let's do that.
And then we became
happy friends for 48 hours.
I think we did dinner.
We did breakfast.
We had another breakfast,
another dinner.
We were inseparable.
Rob had just rebooted
Youngblood with another publisher.
Youngblood is the first Image comic.
It's the first thing
that had the Image "I,"
and there's a connection
between Youngblood and Image
that, as a fan, you know,
it just irks me a little when
there's a Youngblood comic
that doesn't have an Image "I" on it.
Robert and I kind of had
to sell the other partners on,
"Hey, we want Rob to come back again."
We all kind of go, "You know what?
We all did this together.
Whatever the water was
that went under that bridge,
it is under the bridge,
and we did something special
together 25 years ago."
Did it take time to heal?
Yeah, sure it did.
Was I hoping that that healing
process would eventually come?
Sure, 'cause Rob is a good dude.
At his core, he just makes you laugh.
And it was like,
"Sure, with open arms.
Come back in.
Publish your books through us."
You know? It's like a version
of the old days, you know?
- And it's been great.
- And I'm like, "I can't believe
I'm gonna be doing this
with Image again.
This is fun,"
and I remember I called Robert.
- I go, "Is everyone okay?"
- "Everyone's okay."
So here we are, 25 years later,
and I am so proud
of all that Image Comics has
accomplished, and I love these guys.
We've been through a
lot, all of us, all the partners.
I don't believe any of us
would trade anything,
even with headaches,
even with disappointments.
That's what we signed up for
25 years ago.
I'm now...
got gray hair
and I'm a little bit older.
I went from being the cool brother
to, like, that fun uncle,
to, like, now I'm just, like,
that dad,
and pretty soon I'll be,
like, "Grandpa."
"Oh, yeah, that's right, he's
the guy that sorta started it."
I could get hit by a bus tomorrow,
and it won't really matter.
Image... is here.
If it all went away
tomorrow, to be able to say,
"Oh, I only got to do
everything I ever wanted to do
for 25 years, and that was it..."
It's, like, that's still
a hell of a run, you know?
It was an exhilarating time
in my life.
We were doing what we wanted
and having tremendous success
at changing the industry.
I wouldn't trade it for the world.
I know that
there's a version somewhere
of a guy that did all this
and he's bitter.
That's just not me.
There are bands,
and you hear the story
of how a song came to be,
and all that matters in the end
isn't how great
your guitar riff was
and isn't how great your lyrics were.
It's how they work together
to create immortality,
and that's what Image Comics is.
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ Addic7ed.com ~