You're moving in with Tuo?
Yes.
His dad decided to sell the
house and move to Kaohsiung.
But Tuo wanted to stay.
His dad told him he was on his own.
I see.
The company I'm interning at now...
is too far from home.
Commuting to school and my internship...
takes up so much time.
We're not sleeping well.
We're always dozing off in class.
So I was thinking...
Tuo and I could live together.
Find a place that's
convenient for both of us.
An internship is only temporary.
Just tough it out for
a bit, and it'll be over.
Honey.
It's a three-hour round trip
every day. Could you stand that?
It takes that long?
Yeah, Dad.
You're always saying...
how Tuo is more
independent and mature.
If I move in with him,
I can learn from him.
Yushu left.
And now even Junxi wants to move out.
Yushu ran away from
home because you two fought.
Junxi is discussing this with you.
They're completely different things, okay?
Alright, alright. I agree.
Thanks, Dad.
(Episode 8: His Lie, His Panic)
"Secret Lover"
Daddy.
Little bro.
Bro.
You...
Tuo.
Yushu.
Long time no see.
Are you really moving back in?
Well...
I had a run of bad luck..
Because of the pandemic, my
braised-food shop went under.
I couldn't find a job after that.
I was three months behind on rent.
Now...
my landlord kicked me out.
What about my sister-in-law?
We're divorced.
A month ago.
I'm counting on you, bro.
Help me look after Xiao Zhou.
Look.
Clothes, snacks...
toys, utensils, everything.
Just watch him for one day.
Let me go back and have
a proper talk with Dad.
With Xiao Zhou there...
Dad might be easier to talk to.
We just moved in ourselves.
And we haven't even unpacked yet.
You know what Dad's temper is like.
What if he tries to hit me?
Is your big brother's
pride more important...
or is unpacking more important?
I knew you were the best.
Then you need to talk to Dad properly.
Don't get into a fight.
This is the signature
braised food from my shop.
Help yourselves.
It's gross.
Don't eat it.
Son.
Okay, that's all for
today. Class dismissed.
Now that Yushu is back...
his dad must be giving
him a real hard time.
That's what he's afraid of.
That's why he asked Junxi
to help watch Xiao Zhou.
Xiao Yang, are you ready?
Hey, busy bee. Want to grab a bite?
I have to go help Junxi look after a kid.
ORGAN
A kid?
Who'd Junxi have a kid with?
His nephew.
Just kidding.
Tuo.
Junxi's been having a tough time lately.
You should help him
out more with Xiao Zhou.
What do you mean?
Xiao Zhou.
That's Uncle Tuo's ruler. It's not a toy.
I don't care!
Walk slowly.
You'll fall.
Stop jumping around.
It's dangerous.
Okay.
Uncle's gonna get you!
Gotcha!
Pay your rent, or get out!
Just who are you?
Landlord-Man.
Who's the landlord?
You're back.
Time for dinner.
Let's go wash our hands and eat.
Okay.
Can you eat by yourself?
I can. I'm five.
Here you go.
Junxi.
During our liberal arts
class today, Xiao Yang said...
Uncle.
Let's go to the park after we eat.
My dad always takes me to the park.
Okay.
We'll go after you're done eating.
Take your time.
Xiao Zhou, catch!
Here.
Here it comes!
Great job!
Go get it.
Go on, get it!
Hurry!
Again!
Look, look.
The airplane's taking off!
To your left.
Look over there.
You little rascal.
That's mine!
Come on, come on!
Come on!
Try and get me! Try and get me!
Retreat!
Wow, you're pretty good.
Backup!
You're it!
Again!
Uncle, a kiss.
No kissing.
He's mine.
Mine. Uncle is mine.
(Watch on www.kisskh.ovh to support Admin)
Mine.
He's mine!
Uncle is mine, right?
What are you saying in front of a child?
Come on, let's go take a bath.
He's finally asleep.
An angel when he's asleep,
a little devil when he's awake.
I don't know how my brother
raises him all on his own.
I want some too.
Xiao Yang mentioned you're having
some issues with your internship.
You haven't...
looked at me all day.
This isn't right.
If we keep it down, no one will find out.
I have to pee.
Uncle.
Uncle, I have to pee.
Uncle, hurry! I'm going to burst!
I have to pee.
Hello?
Bro, are you coming to get Xiao Zhou?
Okay.
See you in a bit.
Let's go.
Dad really hit you?
Yeah.
He grabbed a stick and
was going to beat me with it.
Luckily, I was good reflexes.
He only got me once.
And that's what happened.
You ungrateful son!
How dare you come back!
J...
Honey, stop.
Come on.
We're going to stay at
Grandpa and Grandma's.
Say thank you to your uncles.
They worked really hard
taking care of you yesterday.
That's not true! I was very good and brave.
I slept all by myself at night.
Not lik
like the uncles, who
cuddle when you sleep.
I had Xiao Zhou sleep
in my room last night.
You could have just slept with Xiao Zhou.
Why'd you need Tuo?
You two..
Are you, like, a thing?
You're overthinking it.
We're just regular friends.
Is that so?
Well, we're heading out.
Bye, uncle. Bye, Uncle Tuo.
Bye.
See you.
Okay, let's go.
We're going to see Grandpa and Grandma.
Off we go.
Bye.
My brother didn't notice, did he?
Of course not.
You've been living
together for almost a month,
and you're just now inviting us over?
Everyone's been busy.
And you two are hard to pin down.
It's fine. Celebrating your one-month
"cohabit-aversary" isn't bad either.
Junxi, how'd you get your
parents to agree to this?
Well...
Don't tell me you told your family...
you're just roommates, learning
to be independent or something.
Seriously? I guessed it?
That excuse-is used by
nine out of ten couples
who move in together.
He Youmei.
- So old-school.
Such a classic move.
Have some fried chicken.
I'll go get some beer.
Don't mind He Youmei.
That's just how she talks.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
You tell me to share everything with you,
but what about you?
You never tell me when something's wrong.
What could possibly be wrong?
Aren't you getting
bullied at your internship?
Xiao Yang told you.
Was that a message from
your company just now?
I'm so hungry.
We left before I could even get full.
That's because you couldn't
keep your mouth shut.
You ruined a perfectly good party.
What did I say?
They're the ones with a guilty
conscience. How is it my fault?
The way they're dating in secret,
they're basically planning an
exit strategy for their relationship.
It's not like they're trying
to hide it on purpose.
Who knows?
A relationship like that is
bound to have problems.
Take it from someone who's been there.
If you don't believe me,
just you wait and see.
A love that can't be spoken
aloud can't withstand any real tests.
It's like ice cream.
You take it out into the
sun, and it melts in an instant.
And then there's nothing left.
He Youmei.
Did something happen to you in the past?
Surprised you, huh?
I just read all that stuff in a comic book.
I'm starving. Let's go get some ramen.
I don't like it when you lie.
If it hurts, it hurts. If
you want to cry, cry.
Smiling and saying you're fine
doesn't actually make you fine.
If I say it hurts,
will you kiss it and make it better?
Make it better?
Like this.
What's there to make better?
If you don't face your wounds,
they won't disappear, and they won't heal.
No matter how many
times you kiss it, it'll still hurt.
If you keep this up, I might fall for you.
Idiot.
So, which ramen place do you want to go to?
The one at the internet cafe.
Are you crying?
No, I'm not.
He Youmei, you're a crybaby.
I'm not!
Your nose is running.
No, it's not!
Yes, it is.
See for yourself.
I want to eat...
Spicy.
Let's get spicy ramen.
You're blushing.
I told my brother
that I fell asleep in your
room playing video games.
I told him not to overthink it.
Or should I say...
I'm used to sleeping with a stuffed toy,
and that's why I was holding you?
And tell him not to get the wrong idea?
Or maybe...
I shouldn't have forced this on you.
Tuo.
Are you only with me...
to humor me?
Out of pity?
Don't be ridiculous.
Hello?
Mom.
What?
Junxi.
Over here.
You can't even drink water.
But I want some ice cream.
This is no time for ice cream.
Mom.
Didn't Dad pass out?
He was awake by the
time he got to the hospital.
The doctor says it's gallstones.
He's scheduled for minimally
invasive surgery tomorrow.
Big Bro.
I brought Dad's things.
See if I missed anything.
Mom.
I'll stay with Dad tonight.
You should go home and rest.
Just come back tomorrow morning.
That's right. That's right.
It's nothing serious.
You go home and get some rest.
But...
There are no buts.
Just go home and rest. It's fine.
All right, I know.
Then you two have to get along, okay?
No fighting.
I'll come by tomorrow after class.
Dad.
You don't drink enough water.
I'm so busy every day.
Who has time to drink water?
I've got no one to help me.
Mom, I'll go get some water.
Okay.
Get water for what?
Your mom just said I can't drink any.
Don't be mad.
Just talk nicely.
I'm getting it for Mom to drink.
Get along.
All right, stop nagging. Just stop.
Looks like my brother hasn't
said anything to our parents yet.
What a relief.
What is wrong with me?
My dad is sick in the hospital,
and all I'm worried about is myself.
My head is just full of thoughts about us,
about whether we've been found out.
I...
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Let's break up.
FOX
///*
/ +19 AD/
Jiamei Hotel Taipei/
(Next episode preview)
Sacrificing yourself for the one you love.
So noble of you, you coward.
Lashing out because you're embarrassed?
Why does love have to be so hard?
What if our parents can't accept it?
Could you still fight to be with Tuo?
Mom.