Junxi.
[Episode 10: Love is a Secret
You Can't Hide]
This atmosphere...
What am I supposed to do later?
[Secret Lover]
If you dare make fun of Tuo
for not having a mom again,
I'll kick your butts!
Let's see if you dare do it again!
Tuo!
Finally found you.
I chased them all away.
From now on, just play with me.
Ignore them.
Maybe from that moment on,
I wanted to stay by his side...
to protect him.
Running away isn't protecting.
One lie leads to a hundred more.
And it hurts the one I want to cherish,
making him anxious and me uneasy.
Are you really in such a hurry?
What am I supposed to do later?
Junxi.
Dad, Mom...
We...
We've known for a long time.
Finally, you decided to tell us.
But I haven't said anything yet.
He hasn't?
Honey, didn't you hear him?
I was just following your lead.
Didn't we agree that
when Junxi came clean
about dating Tuo,
I was supposed to follow your lead?
Follow you.
So you've known all along?
And you also know
that Tuo and I are living together
not to save on rent,
but because we're dating?
Of course.
I know
you're both very mature for your age.
And you never give us any reason to worry.
Why are you crying?
You must have been worried
we'd disapprove,
and it's been weighing on you
for a long time, right?
I'm sorry.
I've been lying to you all this time.
I didn't know how to tell you
about my relationship with Tuo.
I was afraid it would upset you
and that you'd
be disappointed in us.
It's not his fault.
I asked Junxi to lie
to hide the fact that we're dating.
You didn't lie.
You just didn't tell us.
That's different from lying.
Besides,
you two didn't need to tell us.
We already knew.
Yeah, yeah.
Even without saying anything,
when you two are together,
it's obvious
that you only have eyes for each other.
Real feelings can't be hidden.
So all this time,
I was the only one in the family
who didn't know you two were dating?
To think I've been worried for nothing!
Mom, look.
I'm getting a bald spot!
Serves you right
for running away from home!
You deserve it!
Serves you right!
Alright, alright, alright.
It's best if you go completely bald!
Go bald.
You deserve it.
You're serious about my brother,
aren't you?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I can put on a sour face too.
Let's do it together then.
From the moment I realized I liked him,
all I wanted
was to be with him forever.
So you want to marry him?
Wherever he is,
that's my home.
This place too?
Then why are you making that face at me
when I'm your family?
And you've been giving me that sour face
since you were little.
Because when we were little,
Junxi liked you more.
Of course.
He's my little brother.
Jealous much?
Does Junxi know about that?
Whatever happens,
I've got your back.
Kiddo!
Stay home for dinner tonight.
By the way,
when did you and Dad
find out that Tuo and I were together?
Around your freshman spring semester.
Right, honey?
I think so.
It was around the time when you dragged me
to join some parenting class,
saying it'd help us
understand our children better.
But...
Tuo and I didn't get together
until sophomore year.
So we've been wrong all this time.
Well, son,
that means
you already liked each other very much
before you started dating.
Otherwise,
how could we have misunderstood?
Auntie said that?
I only realized
after my mom pointed it out
that I'd already liked you so much
even back then.
Why is it so messy here?
Let's tidy up together.
How about we do it tomorrow?
I've missed you so much.
You just said you liked me.
Where is it?
How did it disappear?
What are you looking for?
Did I wake you?
Time to wake up anyway.
I have class this morning.
What are you looking for?
The ring you gave me.
I clearly put it here.
I put it away.
Ever since we moved here,
you haven't been wearing it.
I thought you didn't really like it.
That was one of the reasons
that made you feel insecure, right?
Put it on me.
You don't have to force yourself
for my sake.
I didn't wear it
because I was afraid of losing it.
And also because
if we wore matching rings,
it'd attract too much attention.
And if one day
you realized
we weren't right for each other
and wanted to break up,
it'd just be awkward.
We'll never break up.
Last time...
Let me finish.
I thought that way at first.
But when you said
we should break up last time,
I realized
that I could never break up with you.
I've loved you so much for so long
that I can't imagine life without you.
Let's not talk about this anymore.
And I'll never bring it up again.
You still have class this morning.
I'll skip it.
Didn't we go at it enough last night?
Not enough.
Rock-paper-scissors.
If I win,
you'll go to school.
Scissors,
rock,
paper.
What are you doing?
After we get married,
I'll replace it with a wedding ring—
and only then can you take it off.
And
no more leaving the ring at home.
Let go.
No.
How can I hug you
if you don't let go of my hand?
We'll save up together
to buy our wedding rings, deal?
Go.
Go where?
Go to school.
Or go to bed?
I thought you'd become a workaholic.
Turns out you were just fighting with Tuo
and using work as a distraction.
I didn't tell you
because I didn't want you to worry.
At least it turned out well.
Uncle and Auntie are so supportive of you.
That's really wonderful.
Tuo and I promised them
we would work hard to become better people
and not make them worry.
And having so many people
support you both,
that must feel wonderful.
Xiaoyang!
Is that my lunch?
I brought you two packs of spicy radish.
You really do know me best.
Han Tuo?
Hold this for me.
Let me borrow it.
Thank you.
The professor asked me to tell you
that he hopes you'll return to school
as a guest lecturer.
I knew it.
When he asked me to return to school
for a second lecture,
I knew he was up to something.
Are you really
going to reject me?
Han Tuo!
Let's have a relationship
that feels light and easy.
You like me?
I do.
Why?
At first, I just thought
you were talented.
I don't know when it started,
but it hurts me inside to see you sad.
You don't need to answer right away.
I'll wait for your answer.
I only like Junxi.
Then I'll just have to wait
until you two fight again
and swoop in.
I still won't choose you.
You deserve someone
who genuinely likes you.
What should I do?
I think...
I'm growing more and more fond of you.
Tuo!
Be careful.
You borrowed it from He Youmei?
We meet again.
Hello.
Remember,
the design draft's due tomorrow.
Okay.
Bye.
Jealous?
Maybe you should just lock me up at home.
I'll think about it.
We forgot the hoverboard.
He Youmei can go get it herself.
She almost made you fall.
Why such a huge change all of a sudden?
Did he get so much of Han Tuo's saliva
from kissing
that he turned into a jealousy monster?
Then why haven't you become
more and more like me?
What did you say?
Nothing.
Xiaoyang, are you blushing right now?
-Say that again.
-I didn't say anything.
Why are you here?
[Field Café]
Here's your coffee.
Thank you.
I said we should move to Kaohsiung,
and you just moved out—
even got a part-time job
to cover your living expenses.
You think you're all grown up now, huh?
Why are you so stubborn?
You suddenly came to see me
just to ask about this?
Where are you going?
Is arguing all that's left
between us as father and son?
When I was young,
all I did was work.
When you were little, you cried a lot.
I really didn't know what to do.
So I just let your mom
take care of everything.
She already had postpartum depression.
But I still kept working.
That also worsened
her mental health problems later.
In the end, we divorced.
I know I was wrong.
But I still chose to keep running away.
I always thought
that providing you with
good material conditions
would make up for everything.
But I was wrong again.
I'm your father
and your only family.
I should have been by your side.
I know.
Dad.
I've already transferred
the living expenses to you.
Um...
how have you been lately?
You're up so early?
I know I've been busy with work,
and I've neglected you.
It won't happen again.
Let's
move to Kaohsiung
and spend more time together.
I believe your father cares about you
and loves you.
He said that for your own good.
Dad.
I'll come visit you in Kaohsiung
next time.
[Field Café]
Junxi.
[Stellaris]
Jeff is looking for you.
Come in!
[Planning Department]
You did pretty well
on the "Dream Home" project.
HR asked me to check with you
if you want to continue the internship
and become a full-time employee
after graduation.
Here are the system access logs
from the day of the setting error,
along with the data
before and after the changes.
Cross-reference them, and you'll find out
who really caused 50,000 players
to get free characters.
Lu Junxi!
I wasn't the one mainly responsible.
Talking to Jeff like this
will definitely offend him.
You don't want to stay at Stellaris
after graduation?
Jobs aren't easy to find these days.
I know.
If it had been the old me,
I might have chosen to stay.
But now,
I don't want to work at a company
that makes rookies take the blame.
Stellaris might be the best company
in the industry.
But
I want to find the one that suits me best.
Just like dating.
So, has the best one already come to you?
That's not the point.
I'm jealous.
Here, eat this.
Time to feel sour, not salty.
You are the best.
[Juicy Joy Fruit Shop; Cash Register]
Boss,
your staff are so handsome!
They're not staff here.
They're my sons.
Both your sons are very handsome.
Yeah,
both are real charmers.
Awesome.
Our dragon fruit is also very good.
Sis, come take a look.
Dad just said
you're his son.
After our internships are over,
let's go on a trip together.
Sure.
I think...
that's when
I started to like you.
When was that?
Xiaoyang went to get ice cream,
but she's taking so long.
Why are you crying again?
Dad lied to me,
and Mom lied to me too.
Mom really doesn't want me anymore.
There, there.
If your mom doesn't want you,
then you don't want her either.
I'll share my mom with you,
and my dad too.
And Yushu...
I'll share him with you a tiny bit.
What about you?
I'll give you all of me.
Forever?
Forever!
I gave myself to you when I was so young?
I'll never let you go.
You're mine.
All mine.
Alright.
Yours.
I'm all yours.
Forever?
Forever.
What do you want to do next?
I don't want to.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors instead.
The winner can order the loser to do one thing.
Okay.
Let's play.
Scissors,
rock,
paper.
I won.
Han Tuo, you're toast!
Tuo!
[Secret Lover]
[The End]