[The Promise of the Soul]
[Episode 11]
[If the Red Thread Snaps, A Bond Ends]
Why are you here?
If you won't go back soon,
I will...
What will you do?
Why do people think
someone like you is suitable
to be a dorm supervisor at school?
I portray myself
as a hard-working postgraduate student
with talent.
Besides,
I'm so good at acting.
Then when will you come back?
Soon.
Wait a little longer.
Just a little longer.
You abandoned me
just for a mission.
Listen.
I'll give you another month.
During the month, if you...
What if it exceeds one month?
Then I'll change the lock on the door
and won't let you in.
Alright.
Go.
Go, go.
Just go.
Go back.
Okay.
Go ask my brother
to find someone to replace me,
so that I can go back early
to accompany you.
Bye.
Go.
Be careful.
Who is he?
Who?
No one is here.
Stop lying.
Boyfriend?
Don't think that everyone
is in a relationship
just because you're in love, alright?
I heard,
if you love someone,
your feelings
will leak out from your eyes.
You can't fool me.
Leak out?
You sound so fancy when you talk.
Why?
Are you in relationship trouble?
Did you look in the mirror
and see your eyes?
Between Ye Haiyuan and Guan Riqing,
who are you going to choose?
Haiyuan.
I didn't see you.
I thought you went to the toilet,
but I couldn't find you.
Then I checked the social room.
You weren't there either.
I just went to buy breakfast.
How would I know you would get up early?
I even knocked on Room 102.
Guan Riqing has trouble using his hands.
His mother took him back
to take care of him.
How do you know?
I heard about it.
Don't worry.
Are you going to
become a grumpy man,
a stalker,
or a control freak
just because you're in a relationship?
I'll be afraid if so.
Be good.
Have breakfast.
What's wrong?
Say something.
What happened?
You used to be uninhibited before.
Did something happen at home?
Or do you have a fever?
Chen Qiansui,
do you not care about me at all?
Yesterday,
I dreamed that you were with someone else.
You even introduced him to me happily.
Why were you with someone else?
Jiang Bailing,
what were you dreaming about?
Tell me
who I was with
and who I introduced to you.
I don't remember.
It's just a dream.
Don't take it seriously.
Why can we only be friends?
If you can be with someone else,
why couldn't that be me?
That's because
a fortune teller told me
I'm doomed to bring bad luck
to my wife and children.
I probably won't be able to date.
I don't want to hurt the person I like.
So you won't date me
because you like me,
right?
I caught you!
Then why didn't you find someone else?
Because I like you.
Since when?
I don't follow you around
like anyone else.
And I'm not good to you.
I just want to be good to you—that's all.
I don't know when I started liking you.
But you have to promise me,
if you want to date someone,
I want to be the only candidate.
I'm not gonna be your wife.
I can't have a baby with you.
You can clear up that doubt
you got from the fortune teller.
I didn't expect you to think like that.
You guys from the sports department
really are a bit straightforward.
It doesn't matter
even if I'm very straightforward.
Having you around is all that matters.
Were you bitten by a mosquito?
No.
Where's the bracelet?
Don't you have another one?
How do you know I have it with me?
Let's give it a try.
But I'm unlucky.
You can't blame me for that.
Look.
I told you they are together.
What about Guan Riqing?
He's been quiet lately.
Maybe he's accepted the fact.
I didn't expect Xia Zefang
could take down Ye Haiyuan.
They are looking at me.
Stop talking.
Haiyuan.
Is the professor looking for you?
Do you want to go first?
Fine,
I'll go first.
Wow.
Ye Haiyuan can't live without you now.
You surely know
how to get along with your partner.
This is much better than Xia Zefang.
Bailing has the same bracelet
too.
Are you really...
Hi.
This must mean the same thing, right?
A token of love.
Are you with Ye Haiyuan now?
What about Guan Riqing?
Or has he given up?
Where is Zefang's soul?
Will he come back?
Stop holding my hands.
Guan Riqing and Ye Haiyuan will be jealous
if they see this.
Let me ask you.
If the red thread is missing,
what does that mean?
When a bond ends,
it snaps.
What if the red thread
is connected to someone else?
When a bond begins, it connects.
Do you believe in destiny?
If you do,
you will be guided by it.
But if you don't,
everything is an illusion.
It's like...
Say, we usually go to the temple
for Poe divination.
If the two pieces fall differently,
we would be happy.
But if they
have their curved sides facing up,
we would think
if we should ask again
or ask in another way.
Because the result is not what we want.
If
the red thread is connected to Ye Haiyuan,
does it mean
you have a romantic bond with him?
What if it's connected to Guan Riqing?
Does it mean
you have an ill-fated bond with him?
Or
does it mean
Zefang has a romantic bond with him?
H-How did you know
the red thread
is connected to Guan Riqing?
Did I call it or what?
What should you do?
Are you going to be with Guan Riqing?
You said
the red thread represents marital fate.
I found the red thread
connected me to Haiyuan before,
so I thought
he was the reincarnation of my wife.
But now,
the red thread
is connected to Guan Riqing.
But I really think
you and Ye Haiyuan are a good match.
So does the red thread
belong to me or Zefang?
Who on earth is it connected to?
Ask your heart.
You, Xia Cha, are staying in the body now.
Xia Cha, which one
do you prefer?
Oh no.
The professor will call the roll
in five minutes.
Hold on.
[It's rude to leave me on read.]
[I just told the professor
that you had diarrhea.]
[Hurry back.]
So you're with me
just because of the red thread?
Ye Haiyuan,
you left me on read.
Why all the mystery?
Don't you know I'm worried?
Are you sick?
Now,
do you think Guan Riqing
is the reincarnation of your wife?
Why is he connected to the red thread?
How...
How did you know?
You thought it'd be better
if I didn't know?
I don't know yet.
I'll figure it out.
You won't figure it out
by getting close to Guan Riqing, will you?
Didn't you say you'd stay away from him?
Or
you'll get close to
whoever is connected to the red thread?
Do you really see me that way?
I have no opinion of you whatsoever.
Yes.
I overthink it.
I'm the one who's afraid,
not you
who always lead an aboveboard life!
That's unfair.
No one here is more afraid of losing you
than me.
Zefang!
Zefang, come out and talk to me!
Is the red thread
mine or yours?
Why are you here alone?
Where is your Zefang?
He is not Xia Zefang.
Okay, okay.
Where's your Cha?
You had a fight?
Someone said,
time's for loving each other.
You
should go upstairs when you're ready.
He might think I'm annoying.
He's so smart.
If he thinks you're annoying,
he can find whatever excuses to avoid you,
instead of staying by your side.
The braised food stall by the back door
seems to be open today.
You can buy his favorite food
and lay it out all over the table
to make him happy.
Then he'll...
Where are you?
God,
just give me a quick end.
How can I return my body
to Xia Zefang?
Or...
Or do I have to live like this?
Can you give me some hints?
Are you okay?
No.
I regret not treating Zefang well
and not telling Zefang my true thoughts.
Would he think
I was with him
only because of Ye Haiyuan?
If I die,
does it mean I can meet Zefang?
Don't jinx it!
Young people
shouldn't talk about "death" so lightly.
If Zefang were here,
he wouldn't want to see you like this.
Wait for me.
Just a moment.
This is Zefang's footprint
recorded after his birth.
As I recall,
he weighed only 2,400 grams.
This is a photo of him
taken on his one-month birthday.
Isn't he adorable?
Let me tell you.
He was really hard to take care of.
He cried nonstop every night
and didn't even like drinking milk.
What is this?
Well, this...
I made this for his grandma.
Before she passed away,
she told me to keep this with me
and said she would come back to me.
Don't they say people have an obsession?
Sometimes I think,
that might be the reason
why I've been brought back to life,
so that there's a chance to meet her again
in this lifetime.
If she were to reincarnate immediately
after death,
she would be the same age as you.
So,
we don't know
what will happen next.
But I believe,
if Zefang comes back,
you can do better.
I really miss Zefang.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Go away!
Cha!
Ye Haiyuan.
Can you stop being so childish?
If you don't understand me,
at least learn to respect me.
I don't respect you?
So,
I should've sent you there myself
and closed the door for you?
I just felt sorry for him.
Could you
stop being so overly compassionate?
Because he didn't believe
I wasn't Xia Zefang.
So now he believes,
and you hugged him.
I didn't.
He's injured.
How could I ignore him?
Besides,
the red thread is connected to him now.
It means he might be Yu Chan.
How can I ignore him?
If he's Yu Chan,
what about me?
When you die, you die. That's it.
There is no reincarnation.
You've been living in your world.
Why don't you look forward?
What do you know?
What I have in this life
is this limited.
Everything I have has been put in.
I want to follow them
and leave this world.
Do you think it's good to be left alone?
When I miss someone,
I can only hold this iron box,
with no one to talk to.
Yes.
I didn't do enough good deeds
in my past life.
So I can only think about the past
all alone in this life.
I'm sorry.
Cha, I didn't know about these things.
Ye Haiyuan.
Do you know
what this iron box means to me?
You don't understand.
These are all promises I failed to keep.
Young Master died for me.
Yu Chan waited for me.
It doesn't matter now.
Now that the box is broken like this,
it's time to wake up.
Leave me alone.
Cha!
Zefang.
Why are you staying in my body?
Am I not supposed to live?
What are you talking about?
Give me back my body.
It was yours to begin with.
Aren't you reluctant?
Everyone likes you and doesn't like me.
I'm wondering
if this trip
can really help me understand my grandson,
so that I won't have so many regrets.
Zefang,
don't be unhappy.
The more people feel miserable,
the more unhappy they are.
You have to confirm
that you can come back
after I give back your body.
Grandpa.
I haven't heard you call me Grandpa
for a long time.
I still remember
the first time you called me Grandpa.
After you moved here later,
you pulled me and told me
you didn't want to go to school.
I hit your butt.
You cried.
I cried too.
Later,
you went to school in Taipei.
I seldom saw you.
I'm sorry, Grandpa.
I didn't spend time with you.
I forgot to accompany you.
I didn't want you to accompany me.
I was just afraid
I didn't know what you needed
and what you wanted.
I didn't take good care of you.
But I have to thank you.
I've had a lot of fun
for the past six months.
I even
dated Haiyuan
by staying in your body.
I have no regrets now.
Things you think don't matter
are just what I never tried to do.
Remember,
even if it's just a few days,
as long as you live life to the fullest,
it's worth it.
You should cherish it.
Don't complain anymore.
Be good.
Grandpa!
[If you want it,
I'll give it back to you.]