[The Promise of the Soul]
[Episode 5: Live a Student Life Again]
Your call will be forwarded to voicemail.
The bill will be charged after the beep.
Why hasn't Ye Haiyuan come back yet?
I'm so hungry.
But if I go out,
I'll run into Guan Riqing.
This is for you.
It's food.
Thank you, Qiansui.
Don't thank me.
Ye Haiyuan asked me to bring it.
Qiansui.
I'm playing games.
Little brother.
Are you free after work tonight?
Stop teasing him.
Here.
Margaret.
Hana.
The part-timer at your store
is really handsome.
He works hard.
But he has a bad temper.
Ye Haiyuan.
A guest at the counter bought it for you.
People treat you to drinks every day.
And there are tips too.
I thought I was running a host bar.
Thank you, Haru.
Tell me.
How much would it take
to spend a night with you?
Don't teach bad things to kids.
Just kidding.
He's young and cold all day.
I saw him last time with a friend.
He's pretty cute.
Who is it?
Bring him to the store next time.
No.
Haiyuan has a new friend?
What kind of person is he?
You seem to care about Ye Haiyuan a lot.
I don't.
You do.
So cute.
One more kiss.
Ye Haiyuan sleeps during class and
works after class.
Hurry up and come back to chat with me.
Good boy, you sleep here.
Do you fall asleep or not?
I told you to come back early.
It's not safe outside.
You worry about me?
I don't have anyone to chat with.
You can ignore Zefang,
but you can't ignore me.
Why?
Because I'm Xia Cha.
I went to help the professor
with organizing his thesis.
Qiansui went to study at the library.
Remember to go to class later.
Your handwriting is quite nice.
Midterm exam?
Isn't it the important exam
that Zefang mentioned?
If I don't do well, I'll fail.
I might even get expelled.
Will I ruin Zefang's future?
Haiyuan!
Ye Haiyuan!
Here.
Thank you for your notes.
But the handwriting
doesn’t seem like yours.
You especially borrowed them
for me, didn’t you?
I was afraid you would keep pestering me.
I read the notes,
but I didn’t understand them.
Would you like to teach me?
No.
I won’t let you help me for free.
I’ll take care of your food and drinks.
How about that?
I need to work. I’m busy.
I don't care.
If you don't agree,
I’ll just keep hugging you
and pestering you.
How’s that?
Are you scared of
being pestered by Zefang like this?
I don't mind.
Why are you getting so close to me?
You came close to me.
Aren’t you the one
who wanted to get close to me?
You little kid...
If it weren't for you,
Zefang and I wouldn’t be like this today.
You have to take responsibility.
How?
Anyway,
you have to take me seriously.
From the bottom of your heart.
How did I suddenly fall asleep?
Why didn't you wake me up when you left?
Boy, studying is hard.
Would you like some tea?
Come on.
Have some tea.
Studying is hard.
Weird, why did everyone leave?
What are you going to do?
I raised you so well before.
Change your clothes.
Here, the latest one.
What do you mean?
I'm fine.
Now you don’t even look like you.
What do you like about Zefang?
Why was he with you?
Wasn’t it good between us before?
I'll buy you whatever you want.
If you don't like anyone,
I'll beat him up.
As long as you ask.
You and Zefang have problems.
Stop it. Come back with me.
What are you doing? Let go of me!
Let's go. Stop it.
Help!
Help me!
Stop it, Xia Zefang.
What are you doing?
Thank you.
For what?
A student reported an issue with 103
using unauthorized electrical appliances.
I'm here to confiscate it.
But my tea is expensive.
It costs 3,000 yuan per catty.
When will you give it back to me?
I'm very angry.
How could Zefang be with Guan Riqing
because of those reasons?
You and Guan Riqing.
One is self-abased
and the other is arrogant.
It’s a perfect match for mutual benefit.
Isn’t Zefang in love with Haiyuan?
Did you really forget
or did you forget it on purpose?
Many people chased after you,
but you refused them.
You were only interested in Ye Haiyuan.
But then, for some reason,
you ended up with Guan Riqing.
But he’s a pretty good guy.
If you were not happy with someone,
he’d beat them up.
If you wanted something, he’d buy it.
How could Zefang do this?
I'm not afraid you'll get mad.
Using moral kidnapping or
emotional blackmail
at this school won't work.
But now you’re doing much better.
If it were in the past,
I wouldn’t even want to talk to you.
Did I do something wrong
that made you like this?
Why did you say that?
Zefang lost his parents when he was young.
I spoiled him.
I only found out recently
that everyone didn’t like him.
You are not Xia Zefang.
Who are you?
Smart.
If I told you,
I was afraid you wouldn't believe me.
I'm not Xia Zefang.
I’m his grandpa, Xia Cha.
We had an accident after we got back.
We both fell to our deaths.
I’m alive.
Anyway, my body was burned,
but my soul moved into Zefang’s body.
No wonder I felt like
your smell was different this time.
But I heard Ye Haiyuan call you Cha.
So he knew about this?
Yes.
He was there when I woke up.
But he told me not to tell others.
He didn't want to trouble Zefang.
That's right.
After all, the soul exchange thing
is a bit magical.
I'm psychic.
Let me check.
Can it be connected like this?
Could you ask
where Zefang’s soul went?
Haiyuan.
Why did he turn and leave?
How would I know?
Haiyuan.
Ye Haiyuan!
Where is he?
Why is he angry for no reason?
Is it because Qiansui and I were too close?
Or
he saw the clothes Guan Riqing
bought for me?
People get angry because they care.
When someone cares about you,
you have to cherish him.
I heard that the new dorm supervisor
has magical powers.
He knows everything.
Help yourself.
Eat.
I want to ask
is there a way to cut off
bad luck with love relationships?
Cut off bad luck with love relationships?
About who?
Guan Riqing and Zefang.
Zefang?
Guan Riqing and me,
me.
No need to do fortune-telling.
First,
you have to cut ties with Ye Haiyuan
before doing that.
No.
It seems
you chose Ye Haiyuan
instead of Guan Riqing.
Why?
I...
Recently, rumor has it that
Ye Haiyuan went into the business
of being a host for money.
Is he better than Guan Riqing?
Nonsense!
Haiyuan is not that kind of person.
He comes back every night with
the smell of cigarettes and alcohol.
He even climbed the wall
when the door was locked.
It's dangerous.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
Take this.
Take it.
Money is very important.
You can do many things.
This is your commission for performance.
Take it.
Prepare for the midterm exams.
You don't have to come here recently.
No.
Hana will be too busy.
I’ll feel bad.
Ignore her.
I'll take care of it.
Bye. See you tomorrow.
Your performance is so good.
I'll be worried if you leave like this.
What are you doing?
Smell of cigarettes, alcohol
and perfume.
A customer treated me to drinks.
Could it be that the rumors
in the dorm are true?
Is Haiyuan really doing this for money?
This is not what a student should do!
Do you know that?
Why are you getting so close to me?
You came close to me.
He was angry because
Guan Riqing wanted to rape him.
It can also explain it.
He doesn't want it at all.
But when I saw Qiansui
getting close to Cha,
I was jealous.
Why?
Why are you still here?
What are you doing here?
I'm going to take a shower too.
Let's go together.
There's no hot water after 12 o'clock.
You should wash earlier next time.
I want to wait for you.
Hello, Hana.
You mean the key to my warehouse?
Okay, I'll look for it.
I’ll wait for you to wash together.
Wash up.
Wash up. It's so nice.
The power is out.
Who?
Haiyuan.
Ye Haiyuan.
Open the door!
Haiyuan.
Let me out!
Stop playing!
Open the door!
Open the door.
Cha.
Cha, what's wrong?
What happened to you?
The light suddenly turned off
and the door couldn't be opened.
Who did this?
How would I know?
I thought you were joking.
Then why did you fall down?
It's strange.
I was suddenly panicked.
My heart tightened.
I couldn't breathe.
I felt dizzy and wanted to throw up.
You have claustrophobia.
What is that?
It’s like,
being afraid of darkness
and narrow spaces.
I'm not.
That’s not manly.
Maybe Xia Zefang has it?
Why does Zefang have so many problems?
So even if we exchange souls,
the body will remember what happened.
Does that mean
once I get over the psychological barrier,
I can swim?
I can help Zefang make more records.
You almost couldn’t breathe just now.
Could you think about yourself more?
You're the one living in this body now.
Are you worried about me?
I’m afraid you might accidentally die
in the bathroom.
Then you’d better watch me closely.
[Why should I watch you closely?
Because I’m afraid you’ll run away.
I see now, the feeling of
wanting someone by your side is like this]
You're drunk.
One more.
Just one more.
Then let's celebrate after drinking it.
Your performance is so good.
Qiansui found out that I'm not Zefang.
I didn't expect
Qiansui to be psychic.
So he tested the spiritual power.
The clothes on the ground
were given to Zefang by Guan Riqing.
But I refused.
But he ran away after he threw it here.
Give it back for me when you come back.
Help!
[Next Episode Preview]
Do you believe in past lives
or soul reincarnation?
Like a dream.
The inexplicable fear.
The trust in strangers.
It proves that
there might be a reincarnation.
So you were the person
who troubled Haiyuan
the other day.
Why are you so sure
that I did all the bad things?
Cha.
When Zefang comes back,
you have to give him a chance.