[The Promise of the Soul]
[Episode 9: Filming Our Happy Daily Life]
Saying things that hurt me so much.
Stepping right where it hurts.
Sir, are you done picking?
Don't squeeze the fruit.
Sorry.
Haru.
You're wearing it already?
Didn't expect Ye Haiyuan
to be this romantic.
It's something
they were selling at the temple.
What romance?
Temple.
He's just too shy to tell you.
What do you mean?
This is a bracelet made by Haiyuan.
Hana was learning.
He was beside her making one too.
So clumsy.
When he finished one yesterday,
he immediately took it
to the temple to pray.
Saying it's to keep you safe.
I think it stands for
romantic relationship.
I'll get going.
Miss, that man didn't pay.
Are you going to pay for him?
Don't act all pitiful.
I'm the one who got scolded
and misunderstood, right?
You and Guan Riqing don't get along.
Don't get me involved.
If you're a man, show your heart.
Don't force it.
I'm sorry.
Cha.
I like you,
not Xia Zefang.
It's you.
Yet I'm afraid that
I'm just a kid in your eyes.
Don't say that.
I'm just an old man.
One good deed a day.
I don't know what you like to eat.
Tell me later.
[Male's Dorm]
Are you still angry?
No.
Then,
why don't you sleep on the bed?
It's uncomfortable to sleep on the floor.
It's too crowded with two people up there.
You can come up anytime.
Ye Haiyuan,
I think you've gone too far
these days.
I'm a hot-blooded young man now.
If something happens by accident,
I might not be able to
handle it right away.
So,
we need to keep some distance.
I've lived most of my life.
But maybe
I don't have enough experience
in that aspect.
In that era...
Anyway,
if you want that,
you might
have to give me some time
to mentally prepare again.
Just let me hug you.
The more I say no,
the closer you come.
Don't move.
[Do not drop]
Get some more sleep.
So early.
Morning.
What can I do for you?
Your delivery.
Thank you.
Yesterday I told Haiyuan to remember
to pick it up.
He forgot.
It's because you guys
were too focused on dating.
Who said we're dating?
You're not?
You two even sleep hugging each other.
Back then,
we were the ones
catching those girls staying over.
Now you're sharing a bed,
totally justified.
Just because we're holding each other
doesn't mean...
Mean what?
Anyway, we didn't do anything bad.
Don't lie to me.
Tell me.
How far have you gone?
So Ye Haiyuan is your past life?
How do you know that?
Don't leave your post for too long.
Thanks for the delivery.
Why are you so nosy?
[Do not drop]
[Love is love]
[International
Affirmative Action Film Competition]
Alright, classmates.
Now,
our school is now promoting
international affirmative action.
So we're calling for
short film submissions.
Our theme is
that love is love.
Anyone want to make one?
Anyone?
Anyone...
I heard that
participants
can get extra credits.
If you win,
you can even earn other rewards.
Me.
Who are you filming with?
Can't I do it myself?
What's the point of filming alone?
It's about love.
Love.
We all have love.
Let's film together.
Do you even know
what affirmative action means?
I can.
You can't.
Your partner
can only be me.
First step,
heat oil in the pan.
Go over there.
Whisk the eggs evenly,
and then we can fry them.
Amazing.
Try it.
It's delicious.
How is it?
It's really good.
I'm glad you like it.
One.
Two.
-Wait.
-One.
Two.
Are you marching?
At least hold hands.
Stop.
Like this.
I've been curious.
How come
there are cicadas now?
Maybe it's because of you.
Why?
Before I met you,
I never heard cicadas here.
Maybe
you brought your world with you.
Turns out
people really change
when they fall in love.
Actually, we can give it a try.
OK. Can you two look at each other?
Be a bit sweeter today, okay?
So you're filming a couple's weekend date?
Yes.
Hold this first.
And get down like this.
Get down.
Raise your hands like this.
Lower.
Like this.
Yes.
Then push your elbows out.
Like this.
This way?
Let me teach him.
Hold it.
Put your fingertips and palms on the table
and then stand your palms upright.
I'll teach my own partner.
Trying to show off
in front of my Haiyuan?
Haiyuan is mine.
Wanna bet?
Two people in a group.
The loser does whatever the winner says.
Deal.
Who's scared?
What?
Have a little more faith in me.
You can compete,
but no betting.
Just look at me.
Why look at the loser?
Let's beat them up together.
Come on!
Please.
OK.
I'll leave it to you.
Hurry up.
You need to hit this one.
You need to hit here.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll get the scores for you later.
Don't say we're bullying kids.
You knew they were great.
I told you we can compete,
but no betting.
A bet is a bet.
What do you want us to do?
Baby.
No need to do more.
Just one.
Is that okay?
It's just a student's film.
Just pretending is enough.
I'm not pretending.
That's not what I meant.
Then what do you mean?
Kissing
in front of everyone like this,
I'll get shy.
This is what makes you shy.
But we can cut it out.
Boys.
Great job.
In such a short time,
you managed to finish a film like this.
Very efficient.
Especially Zefang.
You're working so hard for the credits.
And Haiyuan.
Putting aside old grudges for him.
Is this how you become his boyfriend?
Great!
Let's give them a round of applause.
Get up.
Thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
There's love.
Love.
Love is love.
Looks real, doesn't it?
It's too fast, huh?
Didn't you say it's a film?
Does this look like acting?
If Riqing finds out, he'll freak.
So,
we can't let him see it.
If you don't want to,
you don't have to submit the film.
No way.
It's my ticket to staying here.
What should I do?
I think…
I like you too much.
I'm not romantic at all.
I don't know any romantic tricks.
My only dating experience
was ordinary.
But somehow,
I have a different feeling
for you.
When
you get too close,
my heart just goes
thump,
thump.
That kind of feeling.
Cha.
Thank you for coming into my life.
In broad daylight,
can you be a little more serious?
Then we can do it at night?
You're still growing.
Don't think about that all the time.
What kind of thing?
Even with my wife,
I'd only do that kind of thing
with the lights off and my eyes closed.
Unlike you,
you're not ashamed at all.
You only care about your wife.
Ye Haiyuan,
you're getting better
at throwing tantrums.
You used to be cold and distant,
but now you're jealous and clingy.
You're not so manly.
Ye Haiyuan.
Actually,
you and she have a lot in common.
Maybe that's why
I fell for you.
So,
you should thank her
and that red string.
Otherwise,
I might not have fallen for you so easily.
You have to take responsibility for me.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be led around like this.
Alright.
Isn't H&H booked out today?
No.
I'll take a day off.
Hey.
I asked you to take a leave,
but you said no.
What's the excuse today?
Sex.
What are you talking about?
It's just a bike ride.
[Male's Dorm 1]
No speeding.
No fighting.
No drinking.
Also,
don't let people
take advantage of you.
Be good.
I haven't finished my report yet.
I'll keep you company tomorrow.
You're going to see Bailing, aren't you?
After meeting you,
Haiyuan really changed a lot.
Before, even though he was handsome,
he had a bad temper.
If I weren't his distant cousin
and the dorm supervisor hadn't asked me,
I wouldn't have wanted to room with him.
You are his cousin?
Before you came,
I took care of him.
But now,
someone can finally take over.
By the way,
why do you go to Bailing's place
every night?
Because you and Haiyuan
blind me with your PDA every day.
We didn't do anything.
It'll be too late if you do something.
I was lying on the floor.
Unlike you,
lying right on someone's bed.
We're just friends.
You want to be more than friends.
I'm leaving.
Hey.
Feeling guilty?
With my years of experience,
you two have something going on.
Takes two to tango.
How do I remind him
that I can see Xia Zefang's soul?
Hey.
Are you mad?
Why are you ignoring me?
Take care.
Lend me your bed.
No.
Young Master.
Don't go, Young Master.
Let's go catch the cicada.
No, you're not feeling well.
Last time you almost died out there.
If you won't go, I'll go by myself.
Young master!
Young Master!
Young Master, don't go!
Young Master.
You wanted to settle a score
after so many years?
[No matter the danger ahead,
love is love]
Food's here.
This is yours.
Okay, thank you.
LGBT Q.
So complicated.
It's just five letters.
How can it mean so many things?
It's really open now.
Back in my day,
if a man loved a man
or a woman loved a woman,
their legs would be broken.
There is nothing wrong
with liking someone.
In the crowd of people,
because it's him,
it's him.
Meals we've shared.
Roads we've walked together.
Scenery we've seen together.
Lives we've experienced together.
Because of love,
these everyday moments
become happier.
Enough.
I think
for this short film project,
we can film your dates with Ye.
It sounds easy.
Why don't you film with Bailing?
You two are close.
I'm different from you.
I have enough credits.
I'd rather play games when I have time.
Are you okay?
It's decided then.
Cha.
Show all your life experiences.
Just film your dates with Ye.
Leave it to me.
Didn't you say you have little experience?
I've never seen a pig,
but I've eaten pork.
I've got lots of hidden skills.
At that time,
I'll make you fall for me.
[Next Episode Preview]
Have you seen Cha?
Where is he?
You seem anxious.
I can't get in touch with him.
Of course I'm worried.
He looks down on you.
I treat you so well.
What more do you want from me?
You keep saying you love Xia Zefang,
but don't you know he's claustrophobic?
Do you want to kill him yourself?
You're fighting Haiyuan for Zefang
just to prove...
I've given you everything.
Let go of me!
Enough!
This time,
he won't come to save you.
Don't hurt Ye Haiyuan.