♫Don't give up so easily♫
♫I'll accompany you♫
♫The darker the world is♫
♫The more I see the light♫
♫The sun shines brightly somewhere♫
♫During your passionate youth♫
♫It's inevitable to get hurt♫
♫The darker the world is♫
♫The more I see the light♫
♫The sun shines brightly somewhere♫
♫During your passionate youth♫
♫It's inevitable to get hurt♫
♫Remember how it used to look♫
Do you like the song just now?
[There are echos in this live stream. Hello... Hello...]
[Are you a new live streamer? The number of viewers is so low!]
[Handsome, come sing at my place!]
Thank you, Iron Man, for always supporting me.
Wang Zhan is the best. I want to listen to your live performance.
My live performance?
Have you been to one before?
Or are you busy saving the world?
I think Park No. 10 has finished its maintenance recently.
Yes.
That's my favorite place to perform at.
The first time I saw your performance was there too.
Really?
Meet you at Park No. 10
at 2 p.m. tomorrow.
Did everyone hear that?
Who are you?
Yingxiu asked me to take you back.
Tell my brother not look for me again.
My guitar!
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Let me go!
Let me out!
Thank you!
[Exclusive Love]
[Episode 1: I don't want to take over]
Let go of me!
Wang Zhan.
Brother?
Brother.
Can't you meet me
in a more normal way?
You ran away
and became a street performer.
You refuse to support me.
Am I wrong to rely on myself?
I'll give you three months.
Inherit the business in three months' time.
You know I don't want to do that
but it's because I'm afraid of all the complications that come with it.
You are the legitimate son.
Before Dad left, he told me
to manage the company until you graduate from university.
And what happened?
You studied for six years.
I have no interest in studying funeral etiquette.
If there's nothing else,
I'm leaving.
Who are you?
He is the best funeral director in Hongze Funeral Directors,
Tang Duzhi
In the past three months,
you will be in his hands.
Don't let Dad
and me down.
Why did my brother suddenly change?
Hey.
Do you know what happened to my brother?
He didn't ask me to take over so intently in the past.
There are two floors in the villa.
This is your room.
Everything you need
is in the suitcase.
I have to live here?
Yes.
We will stop renting your place,
and your card and account will be frozen.
You don't have the right to do that.
Don't you want
"Dong Dong" anymore?
Where did you hide it?
Give it back to me.
From now on,
you need to be mentally prepared.
It's so late.
What's there to prepare.
It's okay.
It's all fake.
Wang Zhan.
Wait!
Pause!
Wang Zhan!
Du, he hit me.
Move.
Stop acting.
I'll be scolded.
Du.
Why am I here?
Yesterday...
What time is it?
What...
What was that yesterday?
This is the training plan for these three months.
Last night was just the first step.
In psychology,
this is called emotional flooding.
It's for you to overcome your fear
for blood and funerals
in a short time.
You call that a training?
That ghost was part of it too?
Me?
Wait!
Ji Huiyu?
Junior?
Why are you here?
You kept postponing your graduation.
I've graduated long ago.
You should call me senior.
So you're ganging up on me?
I'm here to decorate the venue.
As a big horror fan,
everything you saw was my collection.
Did I ask you to scare him as a ghost?
I just wanted to help.
It's noon.
Go for your class
after lunch.
Noon?
I saw your first performance there too.
Really?
Meet you at Park No. 10
at 2 p.m. tomorrow.
No, I have to go out.
No.
You have to stay here.
I something to do.
I don't like repeating myself.
Hello?
I'll be right there.
I'll leave Wang Zhan to you.
I'll be right back.
No problem.
Leave it to me.
Come on.
Okay.
How's this new venue?
It's very good.
Thank you Mr. Zhang for helping test this venue.
Don't you think I'll be a good wedding planner?
Just be the boss of your construction company.
Don't steal my customers.
Are you hungry?
That's all you're giving me?
Hello? Wang Zhan?
What?
Okay.
Who is it?
Who are you?
We're here to see Wang Zhan.
He's busy.
Junior?
Senior?
-Long time no see.
Why are you here?
You were Wang Zhan's dorm mates right?
Yes.
He's busy.
Qing!
Help me.
Who is it?
What are you doing?
Tie his hands up.
Tie up his hands.
Wang Zhan.
Wang Zhan, what are you doing?
Let go of me!
Junior.
Now you know how I feel.
Wang Zhan!
My guitar.
Let me out!
Your brother is so cruel.
How can he do this to you?
Yes.
Where did he find that cold-blooded instructor?
Forget it.
Take me to Park No. 10.
Qing. Are you a turtle?
Open the trunk!
Qing, wait.
Who are you calling a turtle?
That's such an old joke.
Aren't you tired of it?
I'll keep telling it.
Okay, I'm sorry. It's my fault.
Happy now?
Open the trunk for me.
Okay, open it for him.
Since you don't have any fans,
I'll help you.
It's Park No. 10.
Okay.
Du.
He's still not answering his phone?
I still can't reach him.
Give me his laptop.
I'll check where he might go.
Okay.
Thanks, bro.
I love you so much.
Okay, hurry up.
How disgusting.
I'll go first.
I'm hungry.
Let's go eat.
I don't want to hear him sing.
Let's buy some food and drinks over
to support him.
Fine.
I'm still late.
Wang Zhan.
You are...
I'm Iron Man.
You're Iron Man?
I don't look like Iron Man, do I?
That's not true.
You're my big fan.
Thank you for listening to my songs.
Of course.
♫The darker the world is♫
♫The more I see the light♫
♫The sun shines brightly somewhere♫
♫During your passionate youth♫
♫It's inevitable to get hurt♫
You want to trap me?
Wang Zhan!
Help! Wang Zhan!
Wang Zhan.
What the hell!
Wang Zhan, you bastard!
I'm doomed.
♫The sun shines brightly somewhere♫
♫During your passionate youth♫
♫It's inevitable to get hurt♫
Shut up!
Go play elsewhere!
You can perform here.
Hey.
You're quite feisty.
Don't go too far!
Wang Zhan.
Are you okay?
How feisty can you get?
Don't touch him!
What?
Are you okay?
Help him up.
Don't you know your condition?
Brother, I'm sorry.
You are brothers?
Brother.
Ask Wang Zhan play the guitar on live streams more.
Bye bye!
Bye bye.
Sorry.
I didn't know his condition.
Don't you think
you should explain about running away first?
I have to keep my promise
to my fans.
Who is he?
The cold-blooded instructor you mentioned.
Are they your friends?
They helped you escape?
Why can't he come out?
Wang Zhan can be considered your boss too.
Who are you to restrict his freedom?
My boss is Wang Yingxiu,
not him.
No matter what,
you shouldn't force someone
to take over like this.
Whether you like it or not,
this is your responsibility.
Why does my brother
want me to take over so badly?
What happened at home?
I'm only responsible for training you.
If you want an answer,
look for it yourself.
Fine.
I'll go back.
Are you serious?
But I'll tell my brother
whether I want to take over or not myself.
Also,
I have another request.
This is coming with me.
Take off your shirt.
It's just a minor injury.
I don't like repeating myself.
Even if you ask three times, the answer is the same.
I'll say no, thanks.
Do you want me to take it off
or do it yourself?
I'll do it myself.
It hurts.
Why that force?
Clean up the area
and get ready for dinner.
Who told you to hide my guitar?
The way to overcome blood sickness
is to replenish iron elements and vitamins.
I have no appetite.
Eat it yourself.
Besides, my hand is injured.
It's not convenient to eat.
Eat with your left hand.
I'm right-handed.
I don't know how.
If you don't eat,
I can feed you.
[Exclusive Love Epilogue]