[Exclusive Love]
[Episode 2: Annoying and Terrifying Special Training]
The dietary method to overcome blood phobia
is to supplement iron and vitamins.
I have no appetite.
Eat it yourself.
Besides, my hand is injured.
It's inconvenient for me to eat.
Eat with your left hand.
My left hand is not my dominant hand.
I don't know how to eat with it.
If you don't eat it yourself,
I can feed you.
I have many ways to make you eat it.
Or do you want to repeat...
What happened last night?
If you spit it out,
the penalty will be tripled.
Continue.
Hello?
You're also still working overtime at this hour?
Are you saying you haven't received the project payment?
Okay.
I'll ask the accountant to confirm it tomorrow.
Sorry about that.
Mom.
I'm working overtime.
Why are you still up so late?
Another blind date?
Okay.
Alright.
I have to get back to work.
Luckily, I've still got you.
Hungry, huh?
Trying to blow me off with this?
Is this all we can be?
Stop it.
Don't think about sleeping in.
Get up and exercise.
Can't you let me sleep a bit longer?
It's only 5 a.m.
Why did you bring me here so early?
As the successor of the company, you must be on call 24/7.
So you need to improve your physical strength.
So?
You need to jog every morning as exercise.
Training?
Also,
you must memorize all the proper terms
of the funeral industry.
You want me to memorize them while I jog?
Do you understand?
Yes.
Yes!
Start.
Faster.
-Why should I jog?
-Again.
Repeat after me loudly.
All the arrangements during a funeral...
Including setting up the memorial tablet, encoffining...
Burial, date picking...
Obituary printing, content design and writing...
Mourning hall decoration,
farewell hall reservation and decoration...
Mourning hall decoration and farewell ceremony decoration...
I've sent you the location of my blind date.
I'm going in.
That's weird.
Is he really not coming?
Don't go in there.
Come with me.
It's finally over.
Your reward is too exaggerated, don't you think?
Pick up all the confetti.
Are you kidding me?
Do I look like I'm kidding?
You ran back too slowly.
This is a punishment,
and it can help train your concentration.
This is just a prank.
Take it as concentration training.
Is there any problem?
No.
Start.
This is a prank.
Is there anyone inside?
Whatever.
What are you doing in my room?
My bathroom needs fixing,
so I thought I'd use yours.
I'll ask someone to fix it.
Which way are you going exactly?
Hey!
Sorry! I didn't see anything.
I mean, I didn't see anything.
I'm not saying you've got nothing there.
What the hell am I talking about...
Give me back my towel.
How should I?
Let go,
and give me the towel.
I'll go take a shower.
Transfer student!
Do you live nearby?
I heard from our teacher that you live alone.
Isn't it boring living alone?
My family won't be coming home tonight.
I'm really hungry.
Can I...
Can I go to your place for dinner?
Sir, your food is ready.
I'm starving.
You dragged me here
before I could eat anything.
Promise me one thing first.
Let me have a bite first.
Don't go on blind dates with people you don't like again.
So, if I can never meet someone I like,
will you stay with me?
I think so.
Will you stay with me...
Forever?
Well, we're meant to be friends forever.
Don't worry, Yingxiu.
Everything is under control.
Take a look at this.
Don't let Wang Zhan
about this.
The best late night snack is instant noodles with beer.
Why do I seem to see Tang Duzhi?
It's really you.
Are you sleepwalking?
Who
allowed you to eat these?
Go away!
Clean it up and go back to your room.
You know what?
I know I have my responsibilities.
Although I'm a rich successor,
my soul is empty.
I have two friends who also
took over their family businesses like this.
But I really love singing.
Singing can bring warmth to people.
So,
even if there's only one person,
I will sing for him.
Don't you know how late it is?
What the hell's your problem?
Just let me finish this song.
I'll take over right after that.
Okay?
♫Find the answer that belongs to you♫
What are you doing?
Put me down!
Tang Duzhi!
Let me finish this song!
Put me down.
Tang Duzhi.
Let go of me...
Tang Duzhi!
It's concert time.
Let go.
I can't be the only one at the concert.
I'll be scared
if I'm the only one.
Let go.
Do you know why I'm scared?
Let me tell you a secret.
You can't tell others about it.
Because my brother
would take me to scary places when I was little.
That's why I'm scared.
He only took you to the hospitals and farewell ceremonies
to train you
so that you could get used to it.
All that training was to prepare you
for the succession.
Why do you know me so well?
Have you been watching me in secret?
No way.
That's not possible.
The reason why you know me so well
is that this is your job.
Let me ask you.
Don't you feel scared when you touch
those dead bodies?
Who wouldn't be scared
seeing a dead body,
especially one that is decayed and damaged?
Some funeral directors who are new to the profession
will have nightmares,
and some will have nausea.
So what should I do to not feel scared?
When funeral directors feel scared,
they need to stay calm themselves
so that the deceased
can go to another world in peace.
As a funeral director, when you feel scared,
take a deep breath
and show respect for the deceased.
What you said...
Is it like this?
Thank you all.
I love you.
It's you again.
Sorry, I didn't mean it.
I was dreaming.
I was catching a ghost.
Enough.
Stop it.
I'm leaving.
Yesterday...
Yesterday?
Yesterday, you said you'd study hard.
Don't forget what you said.
How is that possible?
Don't try to lie to me just because I blacked out last night.
[I'll be the successor. I'll become a pig if I break my promise.
Wang Zhan!]
You have to
keep your promise.
Just let me finish this song.
I'll take over right after that.
Okay?
How do you prove it?
I'll sign.
[Wang Zhan]
I was drunk last night.
You're so scheming.
As long as it can solve the problem,
it's a good method.
No one will like you if you behave like this.
I don't need others to like me.
You made a mistake yesterday.
Your training today will be doubled.
Any problem?
Start.
[Postscript of the Successor]
Buddy, your earphone.
Thank you.
What song are you listening to?
It's a song I wrote myself.
Do you want to listen to it?
May I?