[Exclusive Love]
[Episode 3: The feeling of a fluttering heart]
He's really not interested in me.
Like he said,
we are just friends for life.
Then tell him what you think.
What if...
he refuses?
We can't even be friends then.
Maybe Qing is like you,
thinking that he's friendzoned too.
If you hug...
and kiss him,
you'll be together.
Hug and kiss him?
Like what you did last night?
What?
You're blushing.
You're shy from just a kiss.
How weak.
It's not like I want to blush.
It's a hormone problem.
A hormone problem?
More like Stockholm Syndrome.
Think about it.
He trained you
and abused you.
Yet, just because
of a kiss from him,
you're blushing.
If this isn't Stockholm Syndrom, then what is it?
The more he tortures you, the more you love him.
I don't believe
you don't feel anything
when you talk and eat with him.
Don't worry.
I won't feel anything.
You'd better.
That's enough about me.
Think of your situation with Qing.
Bye bye.
Zhang Yiqing.
I've decided.
I give up.
Let's just be friends forever.
[Qing]
Who are you?
I'm Zhou Youning.
Let's go out for a walk?
Why?
I'm your blind date.
Let's go.
Wait.
Concert hall?
What concert are we going for?
Are you sure this isn't your twin sister?
You have a completely different image.
Come and listen to my concert.
You'll know me better.
[Zhou Youning's Western concert flute concert]
Tang Duzhi?
Are you there?
His room is quite clean.
I didn't notice it last time.
What are you doing in my room?
To see what your room looks like.
Don't lie.
There's still a long time to go for our training.
I thought
we could get to know each other more.
So you hid by my bed?
I got nervous.
You always pull a long face.
Are those your parents?
And Iron Man.
Don't ask him out again.
Jing'an...
He had a serious accident.
He has a heart injury. He can't go out.
Sorry.
I didn't know his condition.
Seeing your family photo,
I envy you.
The only family photo I remember
was taken when I was very young.
But since my dad got sick,
we never got a chance to take another one.
So...
You playing music
has something to do with your parents leaving?
After my dad passed on,
my mom remarried after a few years,
leaving me all alone.
I would listen to music when I'm on the bus,
doing homework, or sleeping.
So all along,
it's music that has been keeping me company.
Go back to your room.
We have training tomorrow.
Okay.
Good morning.
Here comes the chance to test.
The lighting here is better.
I'll drive out after dinner.
I'll introduce you to our business partners.
Drive?
Can I drive later?
I have a driver's license. It's been a while since I last drove.
I want to practice.
In movies, when the protagonist drives,
it's very romantic.
If I don't feel it this time,
then I don't have Stockholm Syndrome, right?
What are you waiting for?
Drive.
Stop!
What's wrong?
The rear mirror.
Remember this.
Drive.
Basically, this area
is for the first stage of a funeral.
You need to get familiar with the environment.
Ask any questions you may have.
Get it?
Hi, Du.
Got it.
Wen.
Du? Why are you here?
Are you new here?
Hello, I'm Wen.
Hello, Wen.
What's wrong?
Let me have a look.
We need to discuss about
Grandpa You’s funeral venue with his family.
His family wants to hold
a special farewell ceremony for grandpa.
When he was young,
he really liked playing basketball.
We can hold a farewell ceremony
related to basketball for this 80 year-old grandpa.
Basketball?
Do you know basketball?
Of course. I used to be an athelete.
I even know how to hurdle.
I was in the school team.
I can dunk with one hand.
Can you?
Sporty style?
That's pretty good.
Let's plan going in that direction.
I also think it’s a good idea.
The rookie is excellent.
MVP.
We have to do our best
to fulfil what the family wants.
That's the duty and meaning of a funeral director.
Yes.
This newbie...
Nice.
My mom wants me to go on another blind date.
I quite like
her.
That's great.
Finally, I don't have to act as a bride snatcher.
Yes.
Maybe I'll get married in a flash.
If you need me to help you plan your wedding,
I'll give you a 50% discount.
Will you stay with me...
forever?
Well, we're friends forever.
What are you doing?
He stole your parking space.
Of course you should honk him.
Forget it.
I was parking too slowly.
You're just too steady and slow.
You never ran the yellow lights when driving,
never sped, and never got a ticket.
It's fine to be robbed of parking space.
Back in school, you also never
handed in any assignments late, skipped any classes,
and was always top three for every exam.
Don't you think your life is boring?
Zhang Yiqing!
Be brave.
Make things exciting.
Is it hard
to make a mistake?
I think I'm doing fine now.
Whatever then.
I'm not taking your car anymore.
Tu Jinghe.
Tu Jinghe!
Relax. Keep the distance.
S-Slow down.
Keep left!
It's so hot.
Why did you turn on the double signal?
Turn it off.
How?
Sorry, I'm not familiar with this car.
Brake!
Breaking news.
-The police issued an emergency report today.
-What are you looking at?
I told you to drive properly.
There is a thrill kill suspect which
witnesses described to be wearing a white knit top,
khaki pants,
and was last seen in New Taipei City.
The police reminds everyone to stay alert
and avoid going out alone at night.
If you have any information,
please contact the police immediately.
It was the radio
that got me nervous.
Can you buy me a drink?
I want to calm down.
Being in the same space with you
makes me so nervous.
Wang Zhan!
Be brave.
Make things exciting.
Is it hard
to make a mistake?
Are you busy?
Come to my house tomorrow.
My treat.
Stop looking.
This is me.
-Attention, all units.
-Police.
-Please show me your ID.
-The thrill killing suspect has been confirmed to be a man in his 20s.
Please open the trunk.
He's wearing a white knit vest
and khaki pants.
Please keep a lookout for him.
What's in the trunk?
-Sir, this isn't mine...
-Get off!
Get out!
-It’s not mine.
-Get off.
Trust me. It's really not mine.
Turn around.
The thrill killing suspect has been confirmed
to be a man in his 20s.
He's wearing a white knit vest
and khaki pants.
Please pay attention.
Stop!
What are you doing?
I was mistaken as a fugitive.
It's him!
Him!
Wait for me here.
Crazy!
I'll beat you up.
Go away!
Don't come near me!
Are you okay?
I told you to wait for me.
I'll take care of it.
How could I ask you
to take care of a trouble I caused?
Then why did you trick me to get off?
I just wanted to practice my driving.
It's so obvious you're lying.
Fine.
I just feel...
Chest tightness?
No.
You have a fever?
No, I just...
You are thirsty?
No.
What is it then?
What are you trying to say?
Can you make it clear in one go?
Last time,
when we kissed...
You were dreaming
and you grabbed me by accident.
That's what happened.
But...
I had a familiar figure in my dream.
He made me feel warm.
I think it's you but also not you.
And every time I get close to you,
I'd feel...
I just wanted to test.
No matter how you feel about me,
it's nothing more for me.
Everything I'm doing for you now
is to let you take over.
I have no other intentions.
I got it.
That's good.
Tang Duzhi!
After the accident, my parents passed away.
My brother was in a coma
and had a heart failure.
I thought that was the end for me too.
Wang Yingxiu, I'm only 16.
You just want me to take over?
I'm going back today for your sake.
I won't go back again.
I'm going to sing this song called "Day Break."
♫Find the place where the answer is you♫
♫Which direction is it?♫
But that day,
I felt like at least someone caught me.