[Exclusive Love]
I'll put this here for now.
[Episode 5: Am I Being Jealous?]
You got something on your face.
Let me wipe it for you.
Du's clothes...
This should do.
It smells good.
Wang Zhan?
Could Jinghe be serious this time?
What do you want?
I want to know everything about Jinghe.
Can you be my consultant?
Zhang Yiqing.
What color does Jinghe like?
Green.
He played a tree in high school drama club.
I hate green the most,
yet they asked me to play a tree.
Is it pretty?
Yes.
This one it is then.
Are you thirsty?
Would you like something to drink?
Tu Jinghe's favorite is sugar-free green tea.
It's healthier.
I happened to buy sugar-free green tea.
Drinks are meant to be sweet,
or they won't taste good.
How much is this?
You don't have to care about the price.
Check out its material.
It's actually worth it.
Look at its buttons.
Tu Jinghe, what are you doing?
I'm just checking the price.
We're almost done shopping here.
I'll go check out.
Youning.
I want to talk to Yiqing alone.
This blind date is just an act.
Is it necessary to act so real?
I'm not acting.
I've decided to propose.
Do you like it?
Are you serious?
Qing, I've found someone I really want to marry.
Wish me luck.
You... Are going to propose to me?
You saw it.
Why were you so careless?
Now there's no surprise.
Haven't we been dating on the premise of marriage?
So straightforward.
I like it.
Were you guys fighting?
I don't know why.
He treats me as a friend,
but he didn't bless me.
Why is he mad at me?
Is it because I didn't tell him first?
Maybe...
It's because he likes you.
Go home.
I'll see you off.
Du.
The way you look at Wang Zhan
is a bit different, isn't it?
Just take care of your own business.
Don't worry about anything else.
What about the last time he fainted?
You were very nervous too, right?
Wang Zhan!
Du, he hit me!
Move!
You were never like this before.
You've always been calm.
This is the first time I've seen you
care so much about someone.
This has nothing to do with work.
I don't have to answer your question.
Do you want me to tell Wang Zhan that
you've been listening to his music secretly?
Sorry.
I accidentally saw your computer.
To me,
he's a very special person.
Why?
Have you known each other before?
When I listen to his music,
I'll calm down.
Those memories
seem to
appear in front of my eyes.
Those memories
accompanied me through the worst times
of my life.
But
I can only keep my distance from him
as a working relationship.
That's also the best distance it could be.
I hope you can keep it a secret for me.
Don't tell him.
Thank you for sharing so much with me.
No matter what you think,
I will support you.
But
I still hope to see
you be happy.
If you like him, pursue him.
Don't leave any regrets.
I'll go home then.
Qing?
What are you doing?
I'm in a bad mood.
Have a drink with me.
Keep your voice down.
Are you going to drink with me or not?
But there's no wine.
Jinghe's marriage is arranged by his family.
Who are you to be mad about it?
I know I'm in no position.
But for some reason, I'm very angry,
and I'm really worried about him.
What will happen when I'm no longer by his side?
When he works overtime and wants to eat chocolate,
no one will buy it for him.
When he wants to have a feast after work,
no one will cook for him.
He doesn't like driving,
and there's no one who can give him a ride.
He can order takeout.
Is there love in takeout food?
Is there any sincerity in it?
I can't beat Zhou Youning.
Now I can't even beat a delivery guy.
Calm down.
If you care so much about him,
why don't you tell him?
Because back in high school,
he told others himself
that we were just friends.
[Tu Jinghe]
Qing asked me to come here.
I wonder what it's for.
I feel like you've been very close lately.
Is he...
Don't talk nonsense.
We're just...
We're just friends, okay?
Just friends?
Yeah.
Stop asking.
I'll call him.
He's late, and he's not answering his phone.
Maybe something came up.
Let's go.
Something came up.
I can't make it.
Let's go have smoothies.
You misunderstood him.
Do high school students
simply admit that they like someone?
So you mean...
I really don't want to get between you two,
but I can't help but want to scold you.
Jinghe has been dropping hints,
but you never responded.
So he thought you only treated him as a friend
and decided to give up on you.
That's why he agreed to the marriage his parents arranged for him.
It's not that I didn't respond.
It was because I thought he only treated me as a friend,
so I dared not respond.
No matter what you say, it's too late now.
He's already proposed.
No.
If he really likes me,
I can't let him get married like this.
He already gave up on you.
What else do you want?
Then I'll get him to fall in love with me again.
I'm going to be someone
Jinghe doesn't want to give up.
Do you have my back or not?
Sure I do.
[Thank you for signing up for the Wonder Garden Music Fest. Sorry that we can't invite you to perform this time.]
[Dear Mr. Wang Zhan, greetings!]
Try harder next time.
I really want to skate by like this forever.
I can't even perform at a music festival.
What else can I do?
I'll go home then.
There's no point in talking about it.
Come on.
Cheers.
At least you know yourself.
I really don't know what I'm doing.
Qing.
Get up.
What's going on?
Why is your friend here?
You reek of alcohol.
A month has passed.
I thought you've improved.
Look what you're doing.
What makes you qualified to take over?
You have no self-awareness at all!
Yes.
I have no self-consciousness.
I still don't understand
why my brother asked me to take over in three months
and why no one's listening to my music.
I don't know what I'm thinking.
I don't know the direction,
let alone where I should go!
Wang Zhan!
What exactly happened to you?
Pull yourself together.
Are you trying to force me again?
All you think about is letting me take over
so that you can complete the task my brother gave you.
You only care about yourself.
Don't go too far.
Du has always been...
Wang Zhan.
What exactly happened last night?
[Wonder Garden]
[Ms. Jiang]
I know I'm mad at myself.
Why would I say something like that?
It seems...
Someone just texted you.
[Thank you for signing up for the Wonder Garden Music Fest. We are pleased to inform you that you have been waitlisted.]
[Dear Mr. Wang Zhan, greetings!]
They said someone canceled their performance.
I've been waitlisted.
No way.
So unconfident?
How can you be the successor like this?
The training...
I want you to go.
Go prove yourself to me on the stage.
You can't do it?
Of course I can.
I'll show you.
Wang Zhan.
I believe in him too.
No matter what happens in the future,
he has the ability to handle it.
My brother said that?
I hope you can
keep those words in mind.
I also believe you can do it.
Du.
Isn't it beautiful here?
I wonder how it's been going between you and Wang Zhan.
This way, please.
Wang Zhan?
Ji Huiyu.
Why are you here?
I'm here to perform.
Perform?
How could Du have let you come?
You must have sneaked out.
He agreed. Go ask Tang Duzhi yourself if you don't believe me.
Mr. Wang, right?
Please come with me for dressing and makeup.
This way, please.
Okay.
You're really here to perform?
Yes.
I'll help you take care of your guitar then.
Go get your makeup done. I'll return it to you later.
I mean it.
Trust me.
Take good care of it for me.
Okay.
I'm done.
Where's my guitar?
Guitar?
When I went out for a walk,
I was carrying your precious guitar with me,
but I accidentally slipped.
So I threw your guitar
in the bushes.
I will treat you
the way you treat Du.
This manor is so big.
Take your time looking for it.
Ji Huiyu, you...
My guitar.
Where did Ji Huiyu throw my guitar?
Ji Huiyu, that bastard.
Wait.
Why do I feel like I've just been here?
Don't be nervous. It's okay.
Hello?
Tang Duzhi.
Sorry, I...
Hello?
Wang Zhan!
Du, I was just joking about
throwing his guitar on the hill.
I think that idiot really went there to look for it.
There's hardly any people there.
[Exclusive Love Epilogue]
[Tu Jinghe]