[Exclusive Love]
[Episode 6: Make a wish to me!]
Du, I was just joking about
throwing his guitar on the hill.
I think that idiot really went there to look for it.
There's hardly any people there.
Don't come near me!
No one can get hurt again.
Wang Zhan!
[I'm finally going to perform on the stage. Bros, you gotta cheer me on.]
Here's NT$300.
Thank you.
Maybe...
It's because he likes you.
Sir, did you forget your stuff?
No.
I'm sorry, sir.
I think I should go back.
Aren't you going to see Wang Zhan's performance?
Where are you going?
I'm going to see Wang Zhan.
What?
You want to avoid me?
You seemed angry last time.
Were you angry because I didn't tell you
I was getting married?
It's okay.
I'm not angry.
I just thought it through.
What do you mean?
We're going to be late.
Let's go watch Wang Zhan's performance first.
Junior?
Senior?
It's you again.
I'm not a junior.
I'm your senior.
Wang Dan–
No, something happened to Wang Zhan!
Wang Zhan!
Why is the signal so unstable?
What's going on?
Wang Zhan!
Tang Duzhi?
Tang Duzhi!
Wang Zhan!
Wang Zhan.
Tang Duzhi!
Tang Duzhi.
Are you okay?
How's your foot?
I don't know why
but I wanted to call you right away.
Do you remember what I told you?
No matter what happens in the future,
I'll be there.
You...
You're injured.
You look pale too.
It's just a minor injury.
Wait.
Done.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Wait.
I haven't found Dong Dong yet.
Ji Huiyu lied to you.
It's already at the performance venue.
He lied to me?
He's gone too far...
Let's get out of here.
The show is almost over.
You got hurt because of me.
I'm useless. I shouldn't perform.
Be confident.
You promised me that.
Go prove yourself to me on the stage.
Is it too late?
How do you know if you don't try?
Let's go together.
Be careful.
I'll walk in front.
Okay.
Yes.
It was too late after all.
When I auditioned or performed,
no matter what,
it would always end badly.
Those who participated in the auditions
would even call this
Wang Zhan's curse.
It's okay.
I'm used to it.
No one gets used to things like this.
You're right.
But I couldn't do
what I promised you.
Trust yourself.
Take the guitar.
Put on your shoes.
What for?
The performance is not over yet.
There are still an audience waiting for you.
[Wonder Garden]
You won't lie to me again, right?
Absolutely not.
Come on, bro.
Although everything you do end badly,
all roads lead to Rome.
Maybe you're suitable to take the treacherous path.
Wang Zhan.
I've never
listened to your performance.
But this time, I won't run away.
Hey, you two are terrible.
Come on, Wang Zhan!
Your biggest fan is right here.
Go on stage.
Sing the song you want to sing.
♫As if I'm trapped in a noisy world♫
♫Should I wish for a better tomorrow♫
♫I can't say I love you♫
♫The grey sky♫
♫It's as if it's laughing at me♫
♫Expectations always bring more disappointment♫
♫But in love, who doesn't get hurt?♫
♫The sky is so vast♫
♫There will be someone who will always be the light of each other♫
♫Hold my hand♫
♫Love has to go to the end♫
♫No more excuses♫
♫I'll tell you everything♫
♫We don't want to be just friends♫
♫Only I know your tenderness♫
♫The unstoppable heartbeat♫
♫Hold your hand♫
♫Love has to go to the end♫
♫Let's take each other as the exit of life♫
♫Announce to the world I just want to stay for you♫
♫I want this forever♫
♫Okay?♫
Did you see the look in
Wang Zhan's eyes when he was looking at Tang Duzhi?
-It was so loving.
So damn annoying.
I need to go calm down.
This junior must like Tang Duzhi.
It's like a love triangle.
Which side are you on?
Of course, on our bro's.
Are you alright?
It's late.
Stay for a night.
Or are you afraid that Ms. Zhou will be angry?
No way.
She knows we're friends.
Let's go then.
Yiqing and Jinghe
are so disloyal.
They left before I finished the song.
My brother too.
He went offline.
I don't even know where Huiyu went.
Huiyu...
Why isn't he with you?
Don't you need to find him?
Why
should he be with me?
I overheard you last time.
There's nothing between us.
You misunderstood.
He probably
didn't want to be our third wheel then.
Mr. Tang, I'm sorry
I didn't get to say hello just now.
Hi, Ms. Jiang.
Are you the newcomer at Hongze Funeral Directors?
Yes.
Ms. Jiang is the owner of this manor.
Someone just texted you.
[Thank you for signing up for the Wonder Garden Music Fest. We are pleased to inform you that you have been waitlisted.]
What a coincidence.
Since you're here,
have a drink with me.
Let's have a good chat.
No problem.
Ms. Jiang.
You are drunk.
Excuse me.
Ma'am.
I’ll take you back.
Here, Ms. Jiang.
Be careful.
Here, your bag.
Ms. Jiang, go to bed early.
Be careful.
Bye bye, Ms. Jiang.
Thank you.
Let me ask you.
Is this performance
arranged by...
I asked Ms. Jiang to arrange for it.
Really?
I just did what I should do.
Don't think too much.
Why can't I think too much?
Why did you help me?
Why did you save me
when I'm in trouble?
Are these
really related to the successor training?
Do you really
not feel anything for me?
Don't you like testing?
Now it's my turn to test my feelings for you.
Let's see if you want to hug me again
or go further.
As long as you want,
I can cooperate.
Mr. Tang.
Mr. Tang, the room is ready for you.
Please come and get the room card with me.
The room looks nice.
I'm going to take a shower.
Today was too thrilling.
I need to calm down.
Calm down!
The most important thing now
is that he helped me so much.
How should I thank him?
Tell me honestly.
Why are you suddenly getting married with Zhou Youning?
I know your family is pressuring you.
But you refused all the blind dates before.
Why not this time?
I think she's great.
She has convictions and is classy.
She comes from a good family too.
I'd be blessed if
I could marry her.
You don't love Zhou Youning at all.
You don't want to marry her at all.
Do you really like her?
Yes.
I like Zhou Youning.
Doesn't that prove
you like me?
I admit that I had feelings for you.
But it's all in the past.
So you still want to marry Zhou Youning?
Yes.
I want to marry her.
Okay.
Zhang Yiqing, what are you doing?
Texting your fiancee.
Tu Jinghe,
I'll prepare your wedding.
Let's take the bath together.
It saves time.
I just wanted to get some water.
Do you want some?
It's okay.
Tang Duzhi.
What's your hobby?
Is there anything you like?
Places you want to go?
Things you want to eat?
You'd better just focus on the company's business
Don't you have anything you like?
Your life can't just be about work.
What do you want to ask?
Be straightforward.
Okay, I'll be straightforward.
You helped me so much.
I want to repay you.
No need.
Just tell me.
I will help you achieve it.
Just like how you helped me.
Tang Duzhi...
smiled?
What was he smiling at?
But he looks quite handsome...
when he smiles.
Hey, what am I thinking?
Zhang Yiqing, turn off the TV.
I want to talk to you.
Zhang Yiqing!
We'll have plenty of time to talk in the future.
There's no rush.
I'd rather you give me bombs and poison
than you helping me with my wedding.
You should be happy that someone who knows you so well
is helping you with your wedding.
No.
I won't let you
hold this wedding for me.
I've talked to your parents.
They are happy that I will be planning it for you.
And they want me to be your best man.
Tang Duzhi...
Make a wish
to me...