[Exclusive Love]
It took me a long time to give up on you.
[Episode 7: Mix It or Not? Love is Complicated]
I can't afford to waver anymore.
Where are you going?
Why am I in bed with you?
I remember being outside yesterday.
Not bad.
You didn't black out from the hangover.
Where are my clothes?
Why did you take off my clothes?
Why don't you ask yourself?
Did you completely forget
what happened last night?
Last night?
Could it be that
something happened
between us last night?
What do you think?
Tu Jinghe.
Tu Jinghe!
I can't even handle my own problems,
and you keep bothering me.
I'm in a nuclear-level situation here.
What the hell did he mean by kissing me?
Isn't it obvious?
He likes you, too.
You two are in a situation where you like each other
but haven't admitted it yet.
But he clearly said before that
he had no feelings for me.
So he lied to you.
Before, his kindness towards you
could barely be explained as him taking care of you.
But now, he's already kissed you.
What else is there to say?
So now, I should...
Go ask him directly
what that kiss means.
Are you saying I should go head-to-head with him?
That's not appropriate, is it?
In my opinion,
you two are already like a couple.
You just haven't admitted it yet.
So we are kind of...
A future couple?
Yes.
You guys just need a moment
to get it off your chest.
You must seize the chance.
Otherwise, if you two end up like me and Jinghe,
it would be troublesome.
I can never do something like
kissing someone else's fiancé
and insisting on helping them organize their wedding.
I just want to give it one last try.
Maybe
he'll break off their engagement.
What if he didn't?
If not,
I'll give him my best wishes.
I didn't see you when I woke up today.
Where have you been?
I couldn't sleep last night,
because...
Your room was too hot,
so he came to me.
Yes.
Maybe I was too excited.
But haven't you always been sleeping well?
Well...
I need to take this call.
The room card and my ID are both in my wallet.
Go check out first.
Hello?
Yes.
This is the best chance for you to talk.
What?
[Birthday: November 8, 1999]
His birthday is next month.
So on his birthday,
you just...
Wang Zhan!
There's a change to our schedule today.
But
your outfit isn't quite suitable
for the occasion we're going to.
You didn't suddenly get some case
and need to take me to meet the family, did you?
Take it.
Go try these on.
Tell me, okay?
So I can be prepared.
We're having a meeting with an important partner of
Hongze Funeral Directors.
We have a lot of opportunities
to work with him in the future.
An important partner?
As the successor, you need to take care of your appearance.
It's a sign of respect for the clients,
and also for yourself.
I don't like wearing suits.
My first suit
was a disaster.
When I was a little boy, my brother forced me to wear a suit
to attend a relatives' wedding.
At that time, my suit felt tight,
and I accidentally spilled a drink
on the bride.
My first suit was given to me by my dad as a gift.
He said a suit represents a man's maturity
and also his responsibility.
He hopes I can take good care of myself,
and more importantly, understand the importance of giving to others.
I've always
remembered that.
This seems to be the first time.
The first time?
The first time you're telling me about your family.
You look good in a suit.
What are you doing?
Very few drivers are willing to
drive this far to pick up a passenger.
So?
Get in my car.
I'll tip a bit extra.
Someone will come.
If you listen to me,
there's a chance
I'll tell you
what happened last night.
Where are we going?
You'll see.
Isn't this near our high school?
Yes.
Why did you bring me here?
Let me find a parking space first.
I've already come with you.
Are you going to tell me or not?
About what?
About...
About whether we
did it or not yesterday.
What do you mean by
"did it"?
So annoying.
Zhang Yiqing, tell me already.
I'll get off if you don't tell me.
You fell asleep outside,
and I carried you inside.
I couldn't have left you out there and let you scare people, could I?
And you spilled wine on yourself,
so I had to help you change.
Or else you'd have to dirty the hotel bed.
So all we did was...
Changing my clothes?
Do you expect us to have done something else?
There's a parking space ahead.
What era is this?
Why are there still people physically reserving a parking space?
He took my parking space.
Of course I should honk at him.
What are you doing?
He took your parking space.
Of course we should honk at him.
Forget it.
I parked too slowly myself.
You're just too steady and slow.
You never ran a yellow light,
never sped, and never got a ticket.
You never handed in any assignments late, skipped any classes,
and you were always top three for every exam.
Don't you think your life is too boring,
Zhang Yiqing?
Are you upset about
me scolding you in the car last time?
All I care about is whether
you like me better the way I am now.
Do you know the difference
between a big tree and a small tree?
I don't.
They're both planted in the ground.
True.
You're boring.
Wait a moment.
I need to take this.
♫I want to grow closer to you day by day♫
♫I want to write a diary together with you♫
♫We defied gravity♫
♫To come here and exchange rings♫
♫Revealing♫
♫The secret which belongs to us♫
♫We defied gravity♫
♫To come here and exchange rings♫
♫Because of you♫
♫I can be myself again♫
Thank you.
Ian?
You must have waited long.
I'm back.
Why didn't you tell me in advance
that you were coming back from abroad?
I asked Tang Duzhi to keep it a secret.
I wanted to give you a surprise.
Ian's company has always been working closely
with Hongze Funeral Directors.
Back in high school,
we got assigned to the same group for assignments a lot, didn't we?
We have great chemistry.
I told your brother that
if you're willing to take over,
I'll definitely have your back.
It's just...
Do you really want to take over?
When you were watching the performance just now,
you were so focused.
What about your music dream?
I...
I'm not sure yet.
It's okay.
No matter what decision you make,
I'll support you all the way.
Ian just got his MBA degree from the US.
So he'll share his knowledge and information
on corporate management with you.
So he'll participate in the upcoming training sessions
together with us.
Together?
So,
you'll be living with us?
Yes, this is the second surprise.
I just made a reservation at a restaurant.
Let's talk over dinner.
Okay, let me see.
I think this restaurant
is a bit too formal.
I suddenly thought of a restaurant I've been dying to eat at.
For nostalgic reasons.
Can we go to that restaurant instead?
I'm sorry.
I didn't look into your preferences in advance.
It's up to you.
It's okay.
Let's go. I'll take you to eat.
Don't you think he's a bit too serious?
He just looks that way.
You'll see later.
This brings back memories.
It's really been a long time.
Look, the wall has been renovated.
When you climbed up that wall,
I always felt it would collapse.
At that time, I wasn't afraid of anything
but being caught by that instructor.
You were afraid of the math teacher too, okay?
Every time you forgot to do your homework,
you asked me to help you.
Not every time, okay?
By the way, you were too slow.
It was because of you that I almost got caught by the instructor.
I was too slow?
Yeah.
Let's have a race now if you dare.
Why did you start early?
Is this the restaurant you want to eat at?
Yes, I haven't been here for a long time.
I missed it.
Let's eat.
Wang Zhan, listen.
You should mix the braised pork rice like this,
so that the braising sauce evenly coats each grain of rice.
Only then can you truly taste how delicious it is.
Let me mix it for you.
Here, try it.
Thank you.
How is it?
Not bad.
Right?
Try mixing too.
It's really delicious.
Just enjoy your meal.
Don't mind me.
So you're the type who doesn't mix it?
The truly delicious way to eat braised pork rice
is definitely not to mix it.
Is this going to be a food war?
Only by not mixing can the texture of the braised meat be preserved
and the rice grains be distinct,
so that they taste crisp.
I'm telling you, braised pork rice needs to be mixed
to truly savor its ultimate deliciousness.
If you mix it all together,
wouldn't the soul of the food be lost?
Just trust me this once.
You won't be disappointed.
Just mix it once.
That's what I insist on.
It's the same with everything.
Boss.
I want another bowl of braised pork rice.
Okay. Right away.
I'll try both.
Is it good?
Yes.
Sir, two more bowls of curry rice, please.
Okay, right away.
Curry rice?
Are you serious?
Yes.
Boss, another bowl.
Gifted student.
Why are you sitting here alone?
You have good grades, so what?
I'm talking to you.
I'm going to teach you a lesson today.
What are you doing?
It's none of your business.
I'll teach you a million lessons.
What?
-Stop it!
-What?
It's none of your business!
Don't touch me!
Who are you?
Let's talk calmly. Who are you?
Who gave you the courage to hit me?
What? It's none of your business!
You don't have to fight, do you?
Talk calmly, okay?
Why did you act so tough back then?
To support you.
We used to like this place a lot.
But after that incident,
we seldom came here.
Come to think of it,
we might have missed 102 times.
No.
It should be 101 times.
We can count it as one less today.
You're really boring.
What did you want
to tell me at that time?
I wanted to tell you...
That I liked you.
It's just I didn't expect
you to tell your classmate
that we were just friends.
I feel like you've been very close lately.
Is he...
Don't talk nonsense.
We're just...
We're just friends, okay?
From then on,
I believed we were just friends.
If I had said something,
perhaps
I wouldn't have to work so hard
for your wedding now.
But I won't give up.
It was a misunderstanding back then.
But now I believe more in
seizing opportunities.
This place is nice.
Your room is upstairs,
next to Wang Zhan's room.
Wang Zhan, you live next door?
Yes.
If you want to know anything,
you can come to me anytime.
You're afraid of those things, right?
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
After more than a month of training
and diet,
Wang Zhan's fear of blood
and those things
has improved a lot.
Since I'm here,
I want to help Wang Zhan more.
Although Yingxiu agreed to let you join,
I'm still the one responsible for
everything about Wang Zhan here.
No problem. You make the call.
But I want to remind you that
if you put too much pressure on people,
it can backfire.
Yingxiu, I'm sorry.
Our personalities are really incompatible.
We might have conflicts in future training sessions.
It's okay.
As long as it helps Wang Zhan mature,
it's a good thing.
It's just
you seem to have a problem with Ian.
I'll adjust myself.
You don't have many friends.
I hope you can become good friends
through this opportunity.
It's the best timing for you to talk.
What?
[Birthday: November 8, 1999]
The best timing to talk...
How should I talk to him?
I don't even know
what gift
I should give to Tang Duzhi.
It's you then.
What do you think of
Zhicun's venue we visited today?
Not bad.
It's environmentally friendly.
Have you been sleeping late lately?
No.
Funeral director companies have great business potential.
Like Hongze,
there are many investors who are eager to try.
Look. This boss is
Mr. Zhuang.
He's very interested in Hongze.
Wang Zhan, you know, corporate management
is like a master telling a cat to catch a mouse.
The mouse runs for its life,
so why do I run?
The signing of pre-need contracts, as well as the sale
and pre-sale of cemeteries and columbaria.
Not bad.
Next, you can get ready to take over
and take the exam for your license.
Let's continue.
Give bonuses to employees,
so that they'll work hard for you.
That's right.
Well done.
You're awake.
I fell asleep?
You're not waiting for me to wake up myself,
are you?
We just arrived.
I was just about to wake you up when you woke up on your own.
Thanks.
I'm going out next Saturday afternoon.
Family affairs.
I'll be back at night.
Next Saturday?
[Tang Duzhi's birthday]
His birthday?
Is he going out to celebrate his birthday?
[Exclusive Love Epilogue]
It was a misunderstanding back then.
But now I believe more in
seizing opportunities.