[Exclusive Love]
Five, six, seven, eight.
[Episode 8: Birthday greeting that was not accepted]
Push up position.
Together.
If you can catch up with us.
Okay.
I can't do it anymore.
Wang Zhan.
Get us some water.
Okay.
Ian.
Come on.
I need more practice.
Why give in to me?
I didn't.
You're really strong.
Don't lie to me.
Why did you give in on purpose?
Because of Wang Zhan.
I can see that
he cares about you.
So?
I don't really like you.
But I care about Wang Zhan.
His business is my business.
I'm willing to do anything for him.
Including
putting up with you for the time being.
That's your business.
It has nothing to do with me.
Just don't affect Wang Zhan.
Water.
Thank you.
You've really become bolder
like Tang Duzhi said.
You dare to come out alone at this hour?
You've been disappearing suddenly at night.
So you came here to feed the cat.
I remember in high school,
a dog ran under the podium in the classroom
and got stuck there.
I was so scared.
It was you who risked your life to save it.
You know
my parents didn't have time to accompany me since I was young.
They were the only ones who kept me company.
Until...
Until you showed up.
My parents even forgot my birthday.
Only you remember.
When I went to the US to study after I graduated from high school,
I was bullied because of the language barrier.
Only you remember
to send me gifts every year.
I know how terrible
it feels to be alone
in the world.
So trust me.
No matter where you are,
I will wish you happy birthday.
So,
does Tang Duzhi get them too?
Why mention him?
You care about him, don't you?
I can't hide anything from you.
Next week is Tang Duzhi's birthday.
I'm going to surprise him.
What are you going to do?
I don't know what he likes.
Strictly speaking, I don't know him at all.
But I want to wish him happy birthday
in my own way.
Ian, will you help me?
He looks unhappy, serious,
and thinks he's an unfeeling instructor;
what about him makes you want to do all this?
Never mind.
Since you asked,
let me help you.
Thank you.
Dad, Mom.
We're here to see you.
Jing'an is getting better recently.
I'll take good care of him.
Don't worry.
My body is a time bomb.
I know it myself.
I just told our parents I'll take good care of you.
I won't let things like this happen.
You have to be confident.
Understand?
I will live on strong.
This way
I can watch Wang Zhan's performance.
Right.
Why did you close the live stream that day?
Dad, Mom.
Brother now has someone by his side
and is doing well.
Hey.
[Boungiorno J Ristorante]
Wang Zhan.
I think it's almost time.
I'll leave first.
I believe Tang Duzhi
will like it very much.
If he doesn't like it,
I'll beat him up for you.
All right.
Send him a text.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Bye bye.
Rest early.
Where are you?
I'm already at the door.
It's okay. You don't have to rush.
It's really okay.
I can celebrate my birthday every year anyway.
Where?
Don't come!
[Wang Zhan]
Sir, I'm sorry.
We're closing.
Do you need anything else?
Okay.
I'll clear your table.
You're finally here.
I thought you wouldn't come.
You didn't come on purpose?
Your family photo was taken in this restaurant.
I thought this place
was special to you.
I don't know what you like,
but this is the only way
I can wish you happy birthday.
You don't have to do this.
I want to!
I made a bracelet with
the guitar strings you used to encouraged me
to perform that day.
I also made one for Jing'an.
These are the feelings I want to express.
Take back your gift.
I don't celebrate my birthday.
Wait.
I did all this
because I have something important to tell you.
You want to tell me that you like me?
You want to confess to me
on my birthday?
What's with your attitude?
Why do you push me away every time I feel
like I'm closer to you–
I told you.
Our relationship is strictly professional.
Th-Then why did you kiss me that day?
I admit.
That was my problem.
I did cross the line I shouldn't have.
I apologize, okay?
Why are you apologizing to me?
Why don't you just say that you like me?
Why can't you just open up your heart
and celebrate your birthday with me happily–
Today is my parents' death anniversary.
It's on my birthday.
You're saying...
Today...
My parents passed away in a car accident
rushing to this restaurant to celebrate my birthday.
I caused their death.
Jing'an was badly injured too.
I can only repeat the same words
in front of my parents' tombstone–
telling them
I'll take good care of Jing'an.
But in fact, I can't do anything.
I can only watch Jing'an's health
get worse.
Like a time bomb that hasn't exploded.
I'm afraid one day it will
suddenly explode.
This is the life I have to bear.
It's all my fault.
If it weren't for my birthday,
none of this would have happened.
That's the me you want to know about.
Is that enough?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
Now you know.
[Jinghe & Youning's wedding]
[Wedding photo shoot at 7 AM
Jinghe and Youning]
Wang Zhan?
Zhang Yiqing.
It's all your fault!
You came up with a terrible idea!
What do you mean?
Tang Duzhi!
If you're not interested in Wang Zhan,
why give him hope?
It's none of your business!
I told you.
I'll do anything for him.
I've put up with you for a long time.
I just can't stand people like you.
If you don't know how to care for someone
who cares about you,
I'll do it.
I'll take care of Wang Zhan.
I agree with you.
What are you talking about?
I'm not like you.
As long as it's good for Wang Zhan,
I won't have any objections.
You still want to be the good person?
What you should do now
is to stay away from him.
This is the best for him.
In the future,
I'll take care of Wang Zhan
in my own way.
Clean this up yourself.
To your failed confession.
Cheers.
It's a pity that you're a wedding planner.
You really know how to eat.
You know what food
can heal me now.
But why do I just not know Tang Duzhi?
His problem can only
be solved over time.
Just like making instant noodles:
it's only delicious when you cook it for the perfect amount of time.
So I should give up
and keep things professional between the two of us?
I want you to spend it with him,
not to give up.
Jinghe's getting married now
but I didn't give up either.
So promise me,
you can't give up either.
Wang Zhan.
You must be hungry.
Let's go eat something.
What happened to your faces?
We bumped into each other
when we came back just now.
Then...
You...
fought?
It's fine.
After we bumped into each other,
we had a chance to talk some things out.
He asked me to take good care of you.
Tang Duzhi.
Right?
Is that true?
Get some rest today.
Wait.
I want to talk to you about what happened tonight.
[Exclusive Love Epilogue]
So you were the one
who has been feeding the cat.
How can a cold-blooded person like you feed cats?
I wish you were as nice to Wang Zhan.
Hua.
Come and eat.
What Hua?
It's Ponyo.
I always call it Hua.
It doesn't like this name at all.
How do you know?
Come on, I'm a pet communicator.
I just know.
Please communicate with Hua.
Tell it dinner is ready.
Ponyo. Come here.