[Exclusive Love]
Tang Duzhi.
[Episode 9: A Kiss to Say Goodbye to the Past]
Is that true?
Get some rest today.
Wait.
I want to talk to you about what happened tonight.
I have explained
what happened tonight.
Let's not
talk about it again.
You're still not giving up
despite what he said?
I don't want to give up so soon.
If I had said something,
perhaps
I wouldn't have to work so hard
for your wedding now.
I decided to go on a blind date
to give up on you.
But you're making me more and more reluctant to get married.
Zhou Youning called me
saying that she had a cold suddenly and couldn't come.
Why didn't she tell me?
Let's cancel it today.
She can't take it,
but I can.
In front of the photographer,
staged photos
are very unnatural.
Look.
Isn't what I took better?
No way.
Look at this one.
I wasn't ready
when you took it.
No, I think it's good.
You look so serious in this one.
How is it different from a photographer's?
It's not that bad.
Okay, let's take a photo.
Do a derp face.
Why a derp face?
Hurry up.
Look.
You're so ugly.
You have pimples here.
You had more pimples in high school.
Who had more pimples in high school?
You're the one who had more pimples.
See for yourself if you don't believe me.
You...
Why do you have these?
Zhang Yiqing, give them to me.
These are my treasure.
Come on.
You're done for.
What are you doing?
Come here!
No!
[Hongze Funeral Directors
Succession Training Plan]
This is the training plan for these three months.
Last night was just the first step.
In psychology,
this is called emotional flooding.
It's for you to overcome your fear
for blood and funerals
in a short time.
It's been three months.
[Hongze Funeral Directors' owner, Wang Yingxiu, has terminal stage liver cancer]
This is...
Wang Zhan, are you okay?
What's wrong?
Tang Duzhi.
Is this true?
Who sent this?
I don't know.
But is my brother really sick?
I'll go ask him myself.
It's true.
That's why he arranged for you
to take over in three months.
So you knew it?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why hide such an important thing
from me?
Wang Zhan.
Think about
how you were three months ago.
Tang Duzhi, enough!
I'm talking to Wang Zhan now!
Wang Zhan.
If you are mature enough,
you should think from Yingxiu's perspective.
He knew you'd be mad,
so why did he keep it from you?
I need to be alone.
Wang...
Wang Zhan!
You're not ready to go see your brother yet?
It's okay.
I'll stay with you.
You can stay for
as long as you want.
Why?
Why didn't I notice it?
Vent everything you want
at me.
Why am I so terrible?
My brother is so sick.
Yet I ran away from home and delayed my graduation.
I even made him worry about the successor.
Tang Duzhi said my brother trusts me,
yet I'm being like this!
It's not your fault.
You're already trying your best.
If my brother leaves me like this,
just like this...
Yingxiu will make it.
He won't fall so easily.
Who sent the message?
Is someone trying to take advantage of the chaos
while Wang Zhan takes over?
If they want to affect the company's succession,
why didn't they make it public
but only sent it to Wang Zhan?
No matter what,
Wang Zhan's mood will be affected.
He's more mature these days.
I believe he will calm down.
Help me investigate
who leaked the news.
Yingxiu said
this can't be hidden anymore.
If someone is trying to manipulate this situation,
he will make an official statement.
Okay.
But...
Wang Zhan will misunderstand you again.
Just do your job.
But...
Get out.
Du.
I don't like repeating myself.
Got it.
Yingxiu.
Are you ready?
I'll wait for you outside.
Sorry.
I kept it from you for so long.
You're very angry?
Very angry.
But I understand.
You can blame me.
Don't blame Duzhi.
I told him to do that.
Why are you still worried about him?
Worry about yourself first.
What did the doctor say?
The doctor said...
there's not much time left.
But don't worry.
I found a new treatment method in Japan.
Maybe there's still a chance.
Really?
Then you can't lie to me anymore.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
I'll do my treatment.
This is the amulet you gave me when you were young.
I've been wearing it.
Now it's time to protect you.
I don't need it anymore.
Wang Zhan!
Wang Zhan. I really want to beat you up.
So you wake up.
Why do you misunderstand Duzhi again?
Do you remember the first time you fainted?
The way he acted
was not something I've seen him done before.
Duzhi has known you for a long time.
He has been listening to your songs.
He has even watched
your performances before.
To me,
he's a very special person.
When I listen to his music,
I'll calm down.
He accompanied me through the worst times
of my life.
I don't know why
he doesn't want to show his feelings for you.
But he really cares about you.
He is the one
who truly cares about you.
You
need to learn to listen to others' feelings.
What's important
can't be heard with your ears.
You need to put your heart into it.
Okay.
Yingxiu.
I got it.
Tang Duzhi.
Are you treating me like a fool?
Wang Zhan?
How many more things are you hiding from me?
You kept my brother's situation from me.
You kept the fact that we've met before
from me.
Are you keeping the fact that you like me from me too?
I only found out that
you've watched my performances,
listened to my music
and helped me secretly
because Ji Huiyu told me about it.
Why didn't you tell me?
Do you think it's fun to treat me like a fool?
How many more things do I not know?
Why are you so nice to me when you
keep talking about keeping things professional?
Please.
Can you just be honest for once?
I think it's okay for me to
cheer him up like this.
Your encouragement,
I got it.
Tang Duzhi!
Don't keep your sadness to yourself!
Toss away your sadness!
Thank you.
I first met you
at your performance.
Then I met you at the bus station.
You were listening to music.
When something happened to my family,
when I wanted to give up on myself the most,
I heard your voice by the lake in the park.
I entered Hongze unconsciously
and became a funeral director,
becoming the person you see now.
I've always wanted to tell you
I want to be close to you.
I want to get close to you.
But my past...
My damn past...
keep telling me,
"You are a person who brings misfortune.
You have no right to live such a happy life."
Don't think like that.
Your parents and Jing'an
all want you to live happily.
Give me some time.
I'll give you an answer
about our relationship.
Are you asleep?
You're right next door,
but I still want to text you.
Why are you typing out so much nonsense?
Delete it.
Thank you for sharing everything with me.
Don't feel pressured.
I'll wait for your answer.
Something feels missing.
I miss you.
This seems too direct.
No.
Get some rest.
Let me help you.
Here.
Your arm.
Let me teach you.
Like this.
Yes, be careful here.
Yes.
Okay.
The other side.
Wang Zhan.
Where did you go yesterday?
Did something happen?
I...
We've talked it out.
From now on,
I won't hide anything from him anymore.
Who would believe you?
Let's talk outside.
Today,
Wang Zhan has to follow me.
Where are we going today?
There's a change in today's training schedule.
I need your help.
Help?
Because you're not the one being trained today,
but me.
One, two.
Mr. Tu, hold on.
Here, it's
one, two, three, four.
Okay?
One more time.
Youning, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Tu Jinghe,
we are completely out of sync.
You need emotions when dancing.
Only like this can the guests
feel the happiness between us
during the wedding.
Understand?
Yes.
Let me demonstrate with Vivi.
I've been learning dance from her for a long time.
Let me show you what being in sync is like.
Let me practice with you.
That's right, Mr. Tu.
That's the expression.
We need to talk.
Let me ask you.
Do you not want to get married anymore?
Yes.
I have someone I want to marry more.
Zhang Yiqing, right?
I think he's quite interested in you.
There was a misunderstanding between us,
but now it's resolved.
So... I'm half a matchmaker?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
We don't owe each other anything.
No, I broke off the engagement.
I should be responsible.
If you want to take responsibility, then take it till the end.
Even if it's just an act,
finish it up.
What are you talking about?
I just want to tell you
I can't continue acting.
If you break off the engagement now,
I'll tell my dad.
My dad listens to me.
If I complain to him
your company will be over.
Zhou Youning, are you crazy?
I already told you
my relationship with Qing.
Why do I have to go all the way in this act?
You can keep acting, right?
Why are we here again?
Since that accident,
I haven't eaten here again.
I even avoided the area
near this restaurant.
Don't force yourself.
I'm being trained today.
I hope you can help me
celebrate my birthday this year.