[Exclusive Love]
[Episode 10: I'm Your Funeral Director]
Why did you bring me back here?
Since that accident,
I haven't eaten at this place again.
I've even been deliberately avoiding
the vicinity of this restaurant.
Don't force yourself.
I'm the one who's being trained today.
Although my birthday this year has passed, I hope you can
help me celebrate it today.
Be careful. Here's your cake.
Thank you.
How can you miss the birthday cake for a birthday meal?
I just asked someone
to prepare this secretly.
Do you like it?
Seeing your family photo,
actually, I quite envy you.
Why can't you just open up your heart
and celebrate your birthday with me happily...
Today is my parents' death anniversary,
right on my birthday.
I'm sorry. I might have gone too far.
This is okay, right?
Stand a bit closer.
Happy smile.
Three, two, one.
One more.
Look.
You look much better this way.
The long face doesn't suit you.
Thanks,
for coming here with me.
Don't mention it.
Well then,
I also want to thank you.
For everything you've done for me.
I dared not get closer to you
because I care about you a lot.
And because I care,
I'm really afraid of losing you.
Make a wish to me.
Why do you seem to like wishes?
I forgot to ask you to make a wish when eating the cake just now.
Make a wish to me.
Just make the wish that
I'll always be by your side.
I already made one.
Really?
What did you wish for?
My wish has come true.
Is it...
Tang Duzhi.
Make a wish to me.
I'll go get some water.
Be right back.
Hope we can come here together on my birthday next year!
Is something wrong?
I wish you could go back to how you were before.
I don't like how you're just working every day now,
living an unhappy life.
Wang Zhan.
You are...
I'm Iron Man.
Dad.
Mom.
Now, Brother has someone by his side
and is doing really well.
You...
Oh, you.
How about we take a break
and have some dinner?
I'm not hungry.
I want to finish packing his stuff first.
I'll help you.
You go back first.
I want to keep you company.
Go back first.
Okay.
Take care.
During this period,
I hope you can help me with one thing.
Go ahead.
I hope you can send Jing'an off.
Good afternoon, family and friends.
Today, we gather here
to bid farewell to a young man who loved music,
Tang Jing'an.
Although Jing'an only lived for 24 years,
he composed a beautiful piece of music
with his short life.
The bracelet I made?
How come?
Jing'an would definitely love
the gift you gave him.
♫The darker the world is♫
♫The more I see the light♫
♫The sun shines brightly somewhere♫
♫During your passionate youth♫
♫It's inevitable to get hurt♫
♫The darker the world is♫
♫The more I see the light♫
♫The sun shines brightly somewhere♫
Tang Duzhi.
I've decided.
I will take over.
I like music
because music can bring warmth to people.
This job does that as well.
I hope I can bring some warmth
to the families who have lost their loved ones,
just like you do.
You're already qualified to take over.
I should thank you.
You taught me all these.
The successor training is over.
Next,
I'll be away for a while.
Be away?
Where are you going?
Jing'an has passed away.
It was all my fault.
It was an accident.
Please, don't think like that, okay?
I don't want to, either.
I also hate this side of myself.
I'll keep you company.
No matter what happens,
and no matter how long it takes.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to harm you.
And I can't be so selfish.
I can't accept myself like this
and go on with you.
Tang Duzhi.
Tang Duzhi!
Tang Duzhi, are you home?
You haven't been answering my calls
or replying to my messages.
I don't even know where you are,
so I had to come to your place.
Tang Duzhi.
Can you hear me?
I have an important thing
that only you can help me with.
Didn't you promise me
that you would help me
no matter what happens?
No matter what happens in the future,
I'll be there.
Tang Duzhi.
What do you want me to help you with?
If I didn't need your help,
you wouldn't see me?
Go back if there's nothing.
What are you doing?
Mr. Tang Duzhi.
As a funeral director, I'm going to purify your body now.
Please relax.
After a person passes away,
the tension of their muscles is very different from when they were alive.
So during purification,
we need to pay extra attention to the pressure.
All these details are meant
to ensure that family members can
say a proper goodbye to their loved ones.
They've entrusted us with
their dearest family,
and it is our responsibility
to ensure they have a proper final farewell.
I'm your funeral director.
I remember everything you said.
But seeing you like this,
I cannot help but think I failed my responsibility
by not letting you bid farewell to Jing'an properly.
Only you can help me with this.
Tang Duzhi.
I'll wait for you to come back.
As the successor, you need to take care of your appearance.
It's a sign of respect for the clients,
and also for yourself.
Are you ready?
It's time to enter the company.
I'm ready.
You know what?
He's Yingxiu's younger brother.
He's here to take over today.
Regarding Yingxiu's matter,
I think everyone knows about it now.
But since he's in the hospital and can't be here today,
I think,
your first day at work won't be easy.
I know.
I'll take it as it comes.
Be confident.
You promised me that.
The elevator is here.
[Hope we can come here together on my birthday next year!]
All these details are meant
to ensure that family members can
say a proper goodbye to their loved ones.
Tang Duzhi.
I'll wait for you to come back.
Tang Duzhi is the most important partner
of Hongze Funeral Directors.
Mr. Zhuang.
If you can't
respect our company's colleague,
then I'm sorry to tell you that
we're not on the same page.
As for the investment,
I don't think we need to give it any more thought.
Compared to those things you're afraid of,
human nature is much scarier, isn't it?
Mr. Zhuang just wants to
take advantage of my brother's sickness
to steal Hongze's business.
That's right.
But is it necessary for you to offend him
for Tang Duzhi's sake?
You just joined the company.
What if he plays some tricks
behind your back?
He can say whatever he wants about me,
but I won't accept it
if he speaks ill of Tang Duzhi.
So you still care about Tang Duzhi.
He won't help you,
neither is he willing to.
Stop lying to yourself.
If he was willing,
he'd be here today
since it's your first day at the company.
I don't know what's gotten into me,
but I feel like he's right beside me,
encouraging me
and cheering for me.
Wang Zhan.
Can't you see
who truly cares for you,
who's always been by your side,
and who truly likes you?
What are you trying to say?
Actually,
the person who really likes you
is not Tang Duzhi,
but me.