[Exclusive Love]
[Episode 11: It's danger, but also a turning point to love you]
Cheers.
How did you come today?
I took the subway.
The subway?
I came by car.
How could you drive when you're going to be drinking?
Are you sure it's not your girlfriend who sent you here?
No, no.
I'm single today, nope.
No girlfriend.
I'm single today.
What girlfriend?
It's Tu Jinghe's bachelor's party.
Why are you pulling a long face?
Tang Duzhi is ignoring me
and my close friend Ian suddenly confessed to me.
My brother's sick too.
After taking over, I met a bunch of troublemakers.
How can I be happy?
You're not happy either, right?
Jinghe is getting married today.
What are you going to do?
This time, helping Jinghe prepare the wedding
is a farewell for me.
I bid farewell to the misunderstanding I had with Jinghe
and expressed my feelings.
Can you really let it go?
I told you.
Even if he really didn't choose me
for his family
and his responsibilities,
I will still give him my best wishes
and say goodbye to him.
A proper farewell.
Have you ever thought of becoming a funeral director instead?
Just kidding.
Let's go.
Let's go find Jinghe.
Thank you for coming.
Of course.
Let's hang out again next time.
Sure. I'll go look for you later.
Okay, come to us later.
My friends.
Thank you.
It's been a long time since the three of us
got together to drink.
Let's put the wedding and our work aside
for now.
Here.
It's my bachelor party.
Why are you making it seem like a farewell event?
He's under a lot of pressure lately.
Cheers.
What shall we play next?
Wang Zhan.
Don't go too far.
I have a snack here.
You have to eat it together later.
But there is a rule.
There should be less than 3 cm left to it at the end.
If it breaks when you're eating it,
your punishment is
to drink all of this.
Hurry up.
Drink more! Finish it!
Finish it all!
Quick!
I feel much more relaxed now.
Thank you for today.
You ruined this bachelor party.
When it's your turn,
we'll definitely mess with you.
I've always been stuck between you
hearing your complaints.
But I dared not pass the message for you.
But since I met you,
seeing what you've been through together,
I really think
you have no reason not to be together.
Think about it yourselves.
I'm leaving.
I won't drink the tea.
Are you really going to get married?
My relationship with Youning
is actually...
Let's say goodbye to everything today.
I want to tell you all the mistakes I've made
and end all the misunderstandings
between us tonight.
Tonight.
Just tonight.
Don't care about what others think.
Listen to what your heart really longs for.
What's important is
for you to feel truly happy.
[Wang Zhan]
You were the one who sent the text about
Yingxiu being sick to Wang Zhan, right?
I was right.
If someone is trying to make it public,
they wouldn't have sent it to him alone.
I asked someone to investigate your schedule
and found out that on the day I brought Wang Zhan to the company for training,
you came to talk to Yingxiu.
I don't think
this is a coincidence.
Yes, that's right.
I sent it.
I brought you here today to teach you about
the services we provide.
Like pre-need contracts, funeral services,
and a place in the cemetery.
So next...
Brother?
You're back.
Thank you.
Kevin.
Take him to familiarize the company's services.
We can't disclose
your illness.
If something happens to me,
I'll be counting on you.
Got it.
You've been keeping this secret.
So why did you suddenly send that text to Wang Zhan?
What are you up to?
What am I up to?
I'd been keeping it in.
But I kept seeing you hurting Wang Zhan,
yet Wang Zhan wasn't unable to let you go,
so I couldn't stand it anymore.
I can only find a way
to let him know what kind of person you really are.
That you're a hypocrite.
Since you heard it,
you should know
Yingxiu and I kept it from him
because we were afraid he couldn't handle it.
It's wrong to hide it to start with.
You were hurting Wang Zhan.
Forget it.
You're just Yingxiu's tool.
You only listen to him.
You don't know
how to treat Wang Zhan well.
And you treat him well?
Or are you trying to take this opportunity
to keep Wang Zhan away from me
so that you can get close to him?
So what if I'm selfish?
Where were you when he was being bullied
in the company?
Where were you when he was upset
and looking for you?
You always run away when there are problems.
If you don't dare to accept him,
then don't show up in front of him!
Why don't you fight back?
Wang Zhan!
Ji Huiyu?
I've been looking for you.
You scared me.
You're right.
I was wrong.
All this time,
I've been running away.
I'm running away from reality, myself,
and Wang Zhan.
I hurt him.
It's my fault.
For the past three months,
I thought I was teaching Wang Zhan.
But actually,
he was also teaching me.
I can't let him down.
He accompanied me,
encouraged me, and comforted me.
I promised him
I'll try my best to say goodbye to my past...
and face the present with him.
Tang Duzhi.
I'll wait for you to come back.
Don't think by saying that,
I'll give up on Wang Zhan.
I won't back down.
You're saying it's Ian who texted me
about my brother's illness?
Yes.
Du has gone to get even with him.
Are they fighting again?
I have to go back.
Hey!
Don't tell Du that I told you.
Remember! Don't tell him!
Alright!
Who are you?
Let me go!
Let me out!
Hey!
Wang Zhan!
What are you doing?
Hello?
Call the police!
Where are you going?
Tang Duzhi!
Mr. Zhuang must be behind this.
The flowers he sent this morning
must be up to no good.
Can you calm down?
This is Mr. Zhuang's place.
Check if there is anyone or any car
suspicious around.
Let go of me!
Who are you?
Is Tu Jinghe inside?
Zhou Youning?
Why are you here?
Looks like you had fun last night.
Zhou Youning, it's my fault.
I want to talk to you.
What happened last night
was not out of impulsiveness.
I've liked Jinghe for a long time.
We had many concerns
and misunderstandings.
But now,
I don't want to miss him anymore.
I know
it will cause a lot of distress to
your family and you.
I made a huge mistake.
But I will face it together
with Jinghe–
I'm sorry.
The person I want to marry
is not Tu Jinghe.
We can continue this act, right?
Isn't this Ms. Vivi, our teacher?
Yes.
I promised my parents to go on a blind date and get married
to provoke her.
What do you mean?
So you already know who you want to marry.
You like her.
We like each other.
But she always says
I'm a rich heiress of a bank
and she doesn't deserve to be with me,
that she can only be my friend.
But who wants to be her friend?
This sentence...
sounds familiar.
Anyway, let's put on a good show
until the plan succeeds.
I was just like you.
I was shocked too.
Then Vivi and you...
Last night at my bachelorette party,
she agreed to go out with me.
So,
the wedding is cancelled.
I'll take full responsibility.
I'll take care of both our parents.
I'll pay for
what your company has provided.
My ex-fiancée
is so cool.
You're so cool
that I pale in comparison.
You can be cool when I leave.
I've tried to matchmake you two
many times.
Do you think I fall sick that easily
and I happen to need a consultant?
Be happy.
So you planned to break off the engagement
but just didn't tell me about it on purpose?
I was forced then.
Or...
you want to confess again?
This time,
I won't just say we're friends.
This is Wang Zhan's bracelet.
Let's go.
Breakfast.
I'll go get Boss.
I found Wang Zhan.
I'll send you the location.
This way.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Tang Duzhi?
Let's get out of here first.
Where are you going?
Go now!
Ian!
Over there.
Tang Duzhi!
Wang Zhan!
Ian!
I got this!
Just go!
Go.
Ian!
Here.
How did you know I was here?
I told you that
I would help you
no matter what.
He must still be around here!
Find him!
Hide here.
Tang Duzhi!
Let's go.
Wang Zhan!