[Exclusive Love]
[Episode 12: Just so you become exclusively mine]
Tang Duzhi!
Let's go.
Wang Zhan!
I forgot to ask you to make a wish when eating the cake just now.
Make a wish to me.
Make a wish that
I'll always be by your side.
Tang Duzhi.
I'll wait for you to come back.
This is your birthday gift.
It shielded me from the stab.
Tang Duzhi.
Just trust me.
As long as we are together,
it will all be fine.
The police have caught them.
It was Mr. Zhuang who planned all this.
He said he just wanted to teach Wang Zhan a lesson.
With Yingxiu not around,
he's becoming worse.
We won't let him go.
Thank you for saving me with Tang Duzhi.
Don't say that.
That'd make me feel worse.
Go back first.
I'll take care of the rest.
Also,
I won't be going back to the villa.
I'll ask someone to get the luggage.
Tang Duzhi!
Take care of Ponyo for me.
Its name is Hua.
I already told you I'm a pet communicator.
It doesn't like that name at all.
Also,
you have to take good care of Wang Zhan.
Do you hear me?
Of course.
If Tang Duzhi treats you badly,
let me know.
I'll come back and beat him up.
When did you
become good friends?
We're leaving.
Bye bye.
Du!
You must be happy!
What are you looking at?
So you're Ji Huiyu.
You were the one who investigated me.
It was also you who sowed discord between Wang Zhan and I.
Because you were trying to tear them apart.
You'd better keep your word.
Don't get involved in their relationship anymore.
As long as Wang Zhan is happy,
I won't do anything.
Me too.
As long as Du is happy,
I won't do anything.
I'm hungry.
After settling the things,
let's go eat.
How's braised pork rice?
Do you eat it mixed up or not?
Mixed up, of course.
That's right. Otherwise it's not delicious.
Let's go.
Give me the bracelet.
It's broken.
All fixed.
You're finally willing to wear it.
Once I wear it,
I won't take it off easily.
Is this your answer?
This...
is my answer.
Morning, Mr. Wang.
Having attended so many funerals,
it's my first time attending my own.
Brother.
Everything is ready.
Do you know why I want to do it?
In a normal funeral,
those who have passed can't hear anything.
Only by doing a living funeral
can everyone have the chance to tell their true feelings.
That's right.
Yingxiu, please.
Let's go.
Thank you for coming to my living funeral.
Being in this industry,
I've seen too much.
You never know what will happen next.
So,
I still want to hold a funeral.
What worries me the most now
is my brother.
Wang Zhan.
I'm leaving the company to you.
I believe you can do it.
Don't forget you're a funeral director.
Yingxiu is currently your client.
Brother.
I'll wait for you to return.
It's okay.
I have your amulet.
[Three years later]
[I'll be the successor. I'll become a pig if I break my promise.
Wang Zhan!]
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Give me a minute.
Let me finish reading this proposal.
Stop reading.
Are you ready?
Let me finish reading the proposal first.
Tang Duzhi, what are you doing?
Let's go!
Tang Duzhi!
Will it kill you to let me finish reading it?
Put me down!
Are you going to put me down or not?
Be good.
Or I will put you in the boot again.
That again?
Do I look good?
Are you satisfied,
my groom?
Yes.
Very much so.
Really?
Yes.
Do you not see us?
My Qing
is the most handsome groom, okay?
Why do you have to get married
on the same day as us?
You insisted on choosing the same venue with us.
Yes, you're not original at all.
You're the copycat.
He's been copying us since we were in high school.
We had this time slot booked long ago.
We've been vying this place for a long time.
You've been copying me since high school.
For how long more are you going to keep this up?
Stop arguing.
You look like a chive
and a sweet potato.
The wedding is about to begin.
Don't let this affect your mood.
Look at this cold-blooded instructor go again.
-You two look like a pair of blue and white slippers.
-Shut up.
-I don't like to repeat myself.
-He doesn't like to repeat himself.
The perfect relationship in life
is to find a lifelong partner
who'll hold an umbrella when you're caught in the rain
and understand you even when no words are exchanged.
From the moment you exchange your wedding rings,
you will start a new journey
to a whole new world.
♫Suddenly far and suddenly close♫
♫Only you can redefine love♫
♫Always running away♫
♫But I see you in my dream♫
♫It's weird but sweet♫
♫This special relationship♫
♫I can understand you without words♫
♫Fly to the vast universe♫
♫I'll fly everywhere with you♫
♫I'll hold an umbrella up when you're caught in the rain♫
♫I want to be closer to you day by day♫
♫I want to write our story with you♫
♫I want to go to a new world with you♫
♫People don't need to understand♫
♫Is it an accident to meet you?♫
♫I want to be closer to you day by day♫
♫I want to write our diary with you♫
♫We defy gravity♫
♫And have come here to exchange rings♫
♫Unveiling our secret♫
Newly-weds, please turn around.
Toss the blessed bouquet in your hands
towards everyone.
Everyone, are you ready?
Yes!
Three, two, one.
Go!
The wedding is so busy.
I'm still hungry.
I've been learning cooking from you for three years.
But Wang Zhan still says my cooking is like trash.
Instant noodles should be fine, right?
Is it good?
Your cooking is as always.
I knew Wang Zhan was talking nonsense.
You're the best.
You never lie to me.
There's something I lied to you about.
I want to confess to you about it.
What is it?
Are you regretting it now?
Actually, when we spent the night here
last time...
Gosh, I was nervous for nothing.
I fell asleep last time.
I forgot.
I've got to do it again when I'm conscious this time.
Didn't I tell you I had to do this event proposal first?
They're rushing us now.
Road running with the urn.
Immersive death experience.
After you took over,
you've been coming up with all these tricks.
Next, I'll be playing
peaceful music to calm the family down.
I'll operate it myself.
Okay.
Ignore that for now.
Today,
you are mine.
Very well.
Do you want to have dinner first
or go for the dessert directly?
It's your turn now.
It'll be difficult to surpass us.
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
I won't lose to them.
♫As if I'm trapped in a noisy world♫
♫Should I wish for a better tomorrow?♫
♫I can't say I love you♫
♫The grey sky♫
♫It's as if it's laughing at me♫
♫Expectations always bring more disappointment♫
♫But in love, who doesn't get hurt?♫
♫The sky is so vast♫
♫There will be someone who will always be the light of each other♫
♫Holding your hand♫
♫Love has to go to the end♫
♫Let's take each other as the exit of life♫
♫Announce to the world I just want to stay for you♫
♫I want this forever♫
♫Okay?♫
[The End]