I'll be off now
See you
Mr. Sheng
Yes?
When you’re free, please let me know
I still owe you that dinner
Go home
It’s late and cold
OK
Mr. Sheng
Good night
this is Miss Shu’s expense statement for the month
She spent a total of 1.24 million
All charged under your name
And what’s this?
It’s
from Secretary Hua and he asked me to pass it to you
He’s really serious about repaying the money
He said he’s very grateful for your help
He’ll do everything he can to pay you back soon
Who asked him to hurry
Who knows how much he had to scrimp and save to come up with this
Twenty thousand?
That wouldn’t even cover the silverware on one of Shu Xin’s handbags
There are far easier ways to repay me
yet he insists on going the hardest route
Stubborn idiot
Mr. Sheng
Yes?
The research team has put together an updated proposal
on the targeted drug development
A few years ago
X Holdings’ lab published a paper on their LYTAC technology
which uses the lysosomal degradation pathway for protein targeting
Our direction has been trying to build on that
to develop
an autophagy-based targeted chimera degradation technology
specifically for the pheromone glandular carcinoma
Unfortunately, we haven’t had any breakthroughs
X Holdings leveraged autophagy pathways
to develop AUTAC
and even more advanced, ATTEC targeted degradation technologies
These two
are considered their most critical and classified core technologies
in their drug development pipeline for AAS gland cancer
Originally
X Holdings is the original inventor of this tech
Trying to catch up to them
we are facing a serious gap in both tech and talents
And HS Group holds the exclusive license to X Holdings’ confidential technology
They're leveraging the foundation
built by industry giants to gain broader vision
Mr. Sheng
should we consider poaching talent from HS Group?
Throw enough money at a problem, and risk-takers will line up
It’s difficult. Shen Wenliang treasures talent.
HS Group’s equity incentive system
isn’t any worse than ours at SHENGFANG Biotech
Even if we spend a fortune to poach people
we’d likely just get some irrelevant staff
and end up alerting them
Not be worth the effort
We’ll wait and see now
Yes
Mr. Sheng
should we consider starting with Hua Yong?
I heard that although he only recently joined
Shen Wenliang trusts him a lot
He even brings him along to board-level decision-making meetings
Trusted?
If he were truly trusted
how could he not even afford his sister’s medical bills?
Na?ve
Let’s not get into risky business like recruiting spies
Mr. Sheng, did you receive the 20,000 I repaid?
Mr. Sheng
Yes
What are you doing?
You look like you’re sneaking around
Waiting for Mr. Shen to finish a meeting
This late
Humph
Shen Wenliang sure knows how to make use of people
pays you peanuts
but works you to the bone
Mr. Sheng, about the money I paid back, did you not receive it?
What money?
I asked Secretary Chen to give it to you
That brown envelope
Oh
That one
Did you receive it?
Nope
You repaid me?
I didn’t even know
That can’t be
Secretary Chen promised he’d pass it on
Hua Yong
what time do you get off work
In half an hour
Hard to explain over the phone
I’ll swing by and pick you up
and talk in person
Umm
OK
Why are you standing there? Get in
Mr. Sheng, about that money
Oh?
That
Chen Pinming just messaged me
Said he forgot to give it to me earlier
He’ll pass it along tomorrow at work
Thanks god
Oh right
next month
when I get paid
I’ll send over the next repayment
No need
Once every six months is fine
How much you repay each time
it’s up to you
That amount means nothing to me
But
But what?
Doesn’t your sister still need further treatment
You’ll need money for all that
If you give it all back to me
how are you going to pay for her care?
Then?
Beg the doctor again to give you more time?
Thank you, Mr. Sheng
Hua Yong
Yes?
Are you hot?
Why is your face so red
Oh
I’m not hot
By the way, Mr. Sheng
Yup?
May I
add you on Wechat?
Mm
Sure
Thank you
Come on
I’ll take you home
Mr. Sheng, thank you for taking me home
Be careful on the way back
OK
You’re the new tenant in 106, right?
Getting off work this late
Yeah
The guy who dropped you off just now is your friend?
He was nice to bring you home so late
He is
He’s pretty nice
Not bad
You have a lot of well-off friends
Last time, the guy who helped you move in
looked like he is rich too
Hello, Mr. Sheng
This is Hua Yong
Did you get home safely?
Mr. Sheng
Also, please take a look at this
Here’s the plan from earlier
Everyone
that concludes today’s meeting summary
Meeting adjourned
Get back to work
Okay
Let’s go
I'm at the office
Morning, Mr. Sheng
I baked some cookies this morning
and had them delivered to your company’s front desk
I wasn’t sure what flavors you liked
so I made the original ones
I hope you don’t mind
and enjoy them
Go pick up some cookies from the front desk
Someone sent them for me
Cookies?
Yup
But don’t you usually avoid sweets?
It’s fine to have a couple now and then
Understand
I’ll bring them to your office shortly
Umm
Here’s today’s second home-made cookies
The first batch
burned a bit
from temp control issues
But I didn’t waste them
I ate them all
Mm
Burnt cookies aren’t good to eat
They’re carcinogenic
No worries
I made sure to spit out all the really burnt bits
Some say that
human affection is like muscle
both can be trained into existence
The method is
pushing boundaries relentlessly
then offer sweetness
after each retreat
When someone who despises sweets
begins tolerating sweetness for you
That is
Love’s first tremor
Help
Set the alarm wrong
Overslept
Took the wrong subway line
and was exactly one minute late
Bye my attendance bonus
Visited my sister today
She's much better after the surgery
Hope she recovers quickly
His mouth is sharp
but his heart’s softer than clouds
Thank you
My Mr. X
Why does he post everything on social media?
Idiot
What is he, first year in school?
Where are the cookies?
No cookies for a whole week
Has student Hua Yong gotten too much homework?
Cookie attendance rate is dangerously low
Did the flour factory shut down?
Good morning, Mr. Sheng
Sorry, I was really tired yesterday
and fell asleep early
Been a bit busy lately
working overtime and trying to move
What about you?
Are you on the way to work now?
Why haven’t you been baking cookies lately?
Mr. Sheng, I’m preparing to move
Might crash at a friend’s place temporarily
Won’t be convenient to use their kitchen
so no cookies for a while maybe
Which friend?
Why are you moving?
Oh
My old neighborhood is getting demolished
My landlord gave me three days to move out
When did this happen
Last week
Where are you right now?
At my friend’s apartment
Housing in the city center is hard to find
Been looking at places with an agent
but nothing suitable yet
The landlord already changed the locks
Said whenever I can move
She’ll come and unlock the door
Sorry, Mr. Sheng
I guess you’ll have to wait for your cookies
until I’m settled
Hua Yong
Yes?
How can you let people walk all over you like this?
You’re never like this with me
If your landlord won’t open the door
you just give up?
What, are all the locksmiths in JIANGHU disappeared?
Mm
Mr. Sheng
He didn’t give permission
I can’t just break in with a locksmith
Don’t teach the little pumpkin bad things
Then, my little pumpkin
what about your lease?
It’s expired
The landlord doesn’t have to renew it
and he stopped taking rent
But
my deposit’s still with him
Since I didn’t move out in time
I probably won’t get it back
Forget the deposit
I’ve got a vacant apartment
near your company
Do you want to rent it?
Huh?
Your apartment must be super expensive
Not really
It’s just sitting empty anyway
I only charge you thirty thousand
Four bedrooms
includes maintenance fees and two parking lots
Interested?
Mr. Sheng
That’s way too expensive. I can’t afford it
What’s your budget?
Two thousand
Per week?
Per month
Great
Two thousand it is
I’ll send you the address and door code later
You’re moving in after work today
I’ll pick you up
Ah
that’s not really okay
Don’t worry
30k to 2k is too big a difference, isn't it?
The place is empty anyway
I hire a cleaner every month
you can move in and take over the cleaning
Consider it rent
That still isn't enough
Our corporate hub's nearby
When I work late
you'd cook midnight snacks
to offset the rest of your rent
This feels inappropriate
Why?
Don't trust me alone with you?
It’s not that
I trust you, Mr. Sheng
I just hate owing more favors
Feeling not that well
Nothing
Debts weigh nothing when piled high
Just accept it
Hua Yong
Need it or not?
You owe favors to friends anyway
Might as well owe them to me
Wouldn't want a pupil getting confused with keeping the aacounts
Thank you, Mr. Sheng
No worries
I'll send the address and the door code soon
and pick you up after work
to help you move
Youth these days
Moving in and out like stray cats
You young folks
are so flaky
Only someone like me
would put up with this
anyone else would've kicked you out
Hmm
I shouldn't have made Mr. Sheng
drive out of his way to pick me up
I took the subway back
See you soon
Your neighbor said that
you come back at all hours
and different rich Alphas drop you off
and pick you up
Listen, Hua
you’re young
don’t go down the wrong path
Physical attractiveness doesn't justify repeatedly enticing Alphas
Excuse me
Is the handover done?
Hey, what's with the attitude?
Noisy
You're ignoring me
while playing on your phone
Input the number
and shut your mouth
If you take the money
and can’t still keep quiet
I'll make sure you disappear for good
Well
It’s been late. I gotta go
Mr. Sheng
isn't this place too big?
Most people complain about small places
Don’t tell me you’re complaining the room’s too big
I think
the monthly rent is more than 30k
Don't worry about it
It's vacant anyway
Thanks, Mr. Sheng
Well
Stop saying that
I got tired of hearing that
Get some rest
I’m leaving
Good night
Umm
Good night, Mr. Sheng
What?
Why should I go to that banquet
The new JIANGHU Chamber of Commerce chairman
what’s that to me?
Fine
Tell the host
to seat me, you and Sheng Shaoyou at the same table
Understood
Hey
Mr. Sheng, Chairman Zhang
Welcome, welcome
You're
the most successful second-generation successor in JIANGHU
I've wanted to acquaint you for ages
You flatter me, Chairman Zhang
You're a legend in JIANGHU business circle
My father often
spoke of learning from your expertise
Nothing
No force could prevent my attendance at your ascension celebration
Thank you
Secretary Hua
didn't expect to see you here
Oh?
You know each other?
Mr. Sheng brought Secretary Hua
to a friend's party before
That’s why I know him
Wow
Secretary Hua has a busy social life
Your social calendar
accommodates our rivals remarkably well
No, Mr. Shen
I didn't say anything to Mr. Sheng
especially about our work
It’s because he helped me last time
No need to explain
Oops
My mistake
Allow me to toast to my oversight
Don't worry, Mr. Shen
It’s our private time
We met privately
and nothing to do
with your business
However
if you're still concerned
feel free to fire Secretary Hua
Our company
is always hiring
Mr. Sheng
You flatter me
ou’re already surrounded by such capable people
like your efficient assistant Secretary Chen
and a beautiful Omega companion like this young lady
I’m sure you don’t really need someone like Hua Yong around
I suppose
Secretary Hua would be more useful staying at HS
So that’s Hua Yong?
He looks even better in person than in photos.
No wonder Mr. Sheng’s always checking his Moments
Welcome, everyone!
Mr. Shen
thank you for having me tonight
Let’s have a drink
Apologies, Chairman Zhang
I’ve caught a bit of a cold
and just took some medicine
This is my secretary, Hua Yong
He’ll drink
on my behalf tonight
Well
I'm sorry President Zhang
Mr. Shen isn't feeling well today
Alright
Though as the junior
and subordinate
Your two drinks shall count as one of mine
Cheers
Chairman Zhang honors me beyond merit
I have something to take care of later
You can head back on your own
Mr. Shen
do you need me
to take you home later?
No need. You go ahead
I’ll take Secretary Hua home myself
OK
Guys
I have something else to attend to
so I’ll head out first
Let’s meet again sometime soon
Hi
Chairman Zhang
Secretary Chang
This is Sheng Shaoyou from SHENGFANG Biotech
and Mr. Sheng
this is
well-known Chang Yu
Secretary Chang
That is
a quite rare guest in the social circle in JIANGHU
Secretary Chang here
manages the Chairman’s office at X Holdings
He is the second to none
Eh
He just told me
he wanted to meet you
So of course, I brought him over immediately
You two
are in the same field
There’s plenty for you to talk about
Go on
Nice to meet you, Secretary Chang
Nice to meet you, Mr. Sheng
I’ve heard much about you
The legendary young entrepreneur of Jiang-Hu
Now that I’ve met you
you truly live up to the reputation
Thank you
Hello, the user you dialed is currently unable to answer
Mr. Sheng is here
Hello, Mr. Sheng
My phone was on mute
I just saw your message
What’s up
Did you get home?
Yes
I just got in
Anyway
What cookie flavor do you want next week?
Why aren’t you speaking?
Is it possible that
you anna make cookies with me at my place?
Mr. Sheng
Open up
Gifting cookies but making me help bake them
just how sincere is Secretary Hua anyway?
I’ll always be sincere with you
Mr. Sheng
Oh really?
Prove it
Is it enough?
Good Morning, Mr. Sheng
Morning
Chinese breakfast
I hate eating Xiaolongbao,
congee and noodles first thing in the morning
Oh
I didn’t know what you liked
so I just prepared a little bit of everything
Did you sleep well last night?
Huh?
The congee and noodles, I made those myself
and the xiaolongbao and side dishes are takeout
Try it and tell me if it’s good
Mr. Sheng
Did you sleep well last night?
Umm
Not really well
Why
You tell me
Hangover from drinking in place of Shen Wenlang
I thought
No
It’s because of the fast heartbeat
Really?
Yes
It’s never beaten that fast before
Hmm
And that kept you awake?
What do I do from now on?
From now on
Yeah
What should I do
Mr. Sheng
if I date you
will I get a heart attack?
Why "if"?
Hua Yong
what am I to you now?
Taming desire like training an animal
feed it disliked food
reward it with kisses
Come in
Mr. Sheng
Here is a list of the suppliers we work with
Please take a look at it
The last time we were in a technical meeting
Sales Director of LISUI Technology
sprayed with our fragrance Drunk Branch
So I specially put the LISUI
removed from our list of suppliers
Keep them
We've used their purification equipment
for years
Don't change for any trivial reasons
Understood
And
HR just submitted the final inquiry
Last week, Chen Ke from Lab Group A left his post
without following protocol
Should we proceed with dismissal?
Deduct this month’s performance penalty
And stay on for observation
Yes, sir
Mr. Sheng seems to be in an unusually good mood lately
Mr. Sheng
Mr. Sheng, you've been working since you got here
even during dinner
Now why don't you eat some fruit?
Take a break
and rest your eyes
Mr. Shen
now
Okay
Mr. Sheng
Mr. Shen just asked me to bring a file over to him at the office
I’ll be right back
What time is it?
What kind of proper Omega goes running off
to deliver documents to another Alpha this late at night?
Hua Yong
let me give you a piece of advice
After midnight every night
you’re not allowed to take care of any other Alpha
Except me
Every time you come home from work
you smell like Shen Wenlang
But when you’re with me, I can’t even touch you
Mr. Sheng
I’m the Secretary of him
It’s only natural that
I pick up his scent from time to time
If you mind it
I’ll shower as soon as I get home
But don’t make it sound like I’mÿ
I never said there was anything between you and him
Then why won’t you ever let me touch you?
I have pheromone dysregulation
And I’m still undergoing treatments
The doctor said physical intimacy is prohibited
Unless
Unless what?
Nothing
Hua Yong
It’s not nothing
I want you to tell the truth
Unless
you’re willing to permanently mark me
I can only have sex with an Alpha who’s willing to give me a permanent mark
Permanent marking means exclusive partnership
I know that’s impossible
Mr. Sheng
I’m not greedy
Just being like this is already more than I ever hoped for
For real
Fine
If you don’t want to have sex , then I won’t
Don’t overthink it.
Mr. Sheng, there’s a company dinner tonight.
I’ll be back a bit late
Been leaving early and coming home late all week
what the heck are you even doing?
When will you come back?
Shaoyou
Come to TIANDIHUI and have a few drinks with us
We haven’t seen you in a whole month
I’m starting to forget what you look like
Busy
Don’t reject us that fast
What’s going on with you?
What kind of spell did that orchid-scented Omega cast on you
You’re practically abstinent for him
Come on. don’t be that friend who vanishes when they see a pretty face
Got it
Wow, handsome guy
Bet he’s an S-class Alpha
Be more confident, no need to ¡°bet¡±
He is S-class
Hey Shaoyou
Feels like the last time I saw Shaoyou
was in another lifetime
It's been a long time indeed.
Why do you look a little upset today?
Why would I be upset?
ShaoYou
You didn't
have a fight with that orchid-scented Omega, did you?
Why would we fight?
Good
Come on, the three of us haven't seen each other in a while
Let's drink till we drop
Drink up
C’mon, c’mon
One for all
Here we go
Bottoms up!
Bring a bottle of Royal Salute
Call over a few more Omega pals who can hold their liquor
Let’s liven things up
Yes, Mr. Zheng
Secretary Hua, take care of Mr. Sheng
I will
I’ll take my leave
Where did you go?
How was your company dinner?
Went to a noisy Korean BBQ place
Super noisy
and not fun at all
What about you?
Where did you go?
Came back so late
What's it got to do with you where I go?
None of your business
None of my business?
Such a strong Omega scent
I can smell it even through the door
Mr. Sheng
Did you let an Omega mark you?