[ABO Desire]
[Episode 5]
Ignoring what the doctors tell you
and taking inhibitors is one thing,
but taking painkillers with inhibitors
when you're in heat?
Seriously, do you want to die?
It reeks. Get lost.
Wash that stench off before you come back.
[Injection-type inhibitor]
[Salbutamol sulfate inhaler]
Mr. Sheng.
Did you miss me?
What do you think?
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
I rushed back
right after I got off the plane.
Great timing.
I'm making dinner.
It'll be done soon.
Okay.
Hello, Boqiao.
Shaoyou, finally picking up.
When you're in rut,
aren't the nights alone long and tough?
Hah.
Get to the point,
or I'm hanging up.
I'm just concerned.
I know how tough it is.
Why don't you let Yushan introduce
a clean and pretty Omega to you?
No thanks.
I'm back in Jianghu.
What? You're good already?
I guess Yushan's Omega is mine then.
If there's nothing else,
don't make such ridiculous jokes.
It'll upset him.
Fine, fine.
It sure is different when you're taken.
Forgive me for being short-sighted.
Alright.
I'm going to have dinner.
Bye then.
The crucian carp soup I just learned.
See if it's to your liking.
How is it? Is it good?
So delicious.
Phew. I was worried
I'd butcher it on my first try.
Mm.
Have you been busy with work?
Yeah, a little.
Recently,
my company's been strict
with employee screening.
I think they even
formed a risk control team.
Really?
Yeah.
I think
it's about serious corruption
in the targeted-drug R&D department.
It also involves
the leak of classified info.
Anyway, it seemed complicated.
You have to be careful then.
Me?
I'm just a secretary,
not from the technical department.
Besides,
I'm very professional, okay?
Professional?
Yeah.
When you're dating
the owner of a rival company?
Mr. Sheng,
you've never asked me
to steal classified info.
So don't worry.
I'm very safe.
Great weather today.
[Shengfang Bio Group]
The client told me to contact him again.
Morning, Mr. Sheng.
-Morning, Mr. Sheng.
Hey.
Don't you think
Mr. Sheng seems chirpy lately?
Totally!
Did something good happen?
I doubt it.
I heard we weren't invited
to the industrial tech exchange meeting
hosted by X Holdings.
Nor have we made progress
on the pheromones' targeted drug.
Maybe he's in a good mood
because the stock price went up
from the overseas orders
our sales department received?
Hey.
Could Mr. Sheng be in love?
No way!
Who is Mr. Sheng?
Shh. He's not the type to be lovestruck.
There's no way.
Yeah, no way.
You're right.
Seriously...
Mm.
The orchid nearing its heat cycle
smells so good.
What's wrong?
I'm still not feeling well.
You still have a slight fever.
Yeah.
It's been three days.
Go see a doctor.
I did.
What did the doctor say?
They said it's pheromone disorder.
But don't worry.
I'm taking medicine.
Hua Yong.
Will you get better
if you're permanently marked?
Mr. Sheng.
A permanent mark is an important decision.
If it's out of pity, I don't want you to—
It's not because I pity you.
I still don't want you to be so hasty
with this important decision.
If you regret it in the future,
we'll both suffer.
I'm not being hasty.
All right.
I got it.
Thank you, Mr. Sheng.
I've to get to work.
I'm going to be late.
Mr. Sheng, what do you want for dinner?
Rest up since you're not feeling well.
I'll bring home some takeout.
How's that?
I still want to cook myself.
Takeout isn't healthy.
Crucian carp soup then.
It's delicious.
Sure, got it.
I'll get going.
Alright, see you tonight.
Okay.
Bye.
The subscriber you're trying to reach
has their device switched off.
Why isn't he back yet?
The subscriber you're trying to reach
has their device switched off.
[Shen Wenlang]
[Chen Pinming]
Mr. Sheng.
Chen Pinming.
Send someone to look for Hua Yong.
What happened to Mr. Hua?
He hasn't replied my texts since 3 PM.
When I called him at 6 PM,
his phone was off.
He's still not home.
I tried Shen Wenlang
and his phone's off too.
Chen Pinming.
Anything new about HS Group?
Or did Shen Wenlang commit a crime
and get in trouble?
Mr. Sheng, calm down.
I'll send someone to investigate.
[Shengfang Bio Group]
We've made a police report.
No news of Mr. Hua so far.
Based on surveillance footage,
Mr. Hua got off work at 5:30 PM as usual.
He got into a ride-hailing car
in front of the company,
which drove to a surveillance blind spot
and never showed up again.
Checked the license plate?
Yes, it's a stolen car.
That's all we've got.
Sorry, Mr. Sheng.
It's my fault.
How so?
M-Mr. Sheng,
Mr. Hua might be in danger.
What danger?
Mr. Shen Wenlang of HS
values Mr. Hua a lot.
He brings him to every meeting.
To get more info about their R&D,
I...
I put a bug in Mr. Hua's briefcase.
Who told you to do that?
Sorry, Mr. Sheng.
-HS' security is airtight.
-Enough.
It doesn't matter now.
[Shen Wenlang]
Chen Pinming.
Do you have
the number of Shen's secretary?
Yes.
Call him!
Okay.
Hello.
This is the chairman's office of HS Group.
I'm Mr. Shen's secretary, Gao Tu.
How may I help you?
Hello, Mr. Gao.
Sheng Shaoyou of Shengfang Bio.
Mr. Gao.
Where is Mr. Shen?
Oh, hi, Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Shen is seeing a guest.
He isn't available.
I can relay a message to him for you.
Ask Shen Wenlang when he's free.
Tell me when he's free,
and I'll be right there.
Okay.
After his meeting,
I'll ask him
and get back to you.
Come in.
What's the matter?
Mr. Shen.
Don't just stand there like a statue.
I didn't hire you
to be an ornament in the office.
Besides,
you're not attractive enough to be one.
Mr. Gao.
I'm sorry.
I'm here to tell you
Mr. Sheng Shaoyou
from Shengfang Bio called.
What did he want?
He didn't elaborate.
He just
asked when you're free,
and he'll call again.
Just a few days without news of Hua Yong,
and he's this anxious.
What a loser.
He can't reach Mr. Hua?
Didn't Mr. Hua ask for leave?
Why do you know so much about Hua Yong?
You interested in him too?
Mr. Hua and I are in the same department.
No one knows his schedule better than me.
Besides,
there must be many people who care for
an outstanding Omega like him.
Omega this, Omega that.
Enough already.
If you lose focus
and make stupid mistakes again,
you can pack your things and go home.
Well,
about Mr. Sheng...
Let him wait.
Better if he loses his mind.
That bastard is so arrogant.
The first time we met,
he actually said 35 billion.
As if Shengfang Bio prints money.
About time he learns a lesson.
Don't ever answer his calls again.
Gao Tu.
You're my secretary,
not Sheng Shaoyou's messenger.
Get your head straight.
Don't cause me any trouble.
Yes, I got it.
Mr. Sheng,
I've called Allen,
the most famous private investigator
in Jianghu.
I'm sure there will be news
of Mr. Hua soon.
I'm really sorry.
It's all my fault.
I put the bug without your permission.
That's why...
It's not your fault.
I'm the one who told you
to prioritize results.
Really, it's my fault.
Please don't say that.
By the way,
Mr. Gao just called me
saying that Mr. Shen's busy
and won't be free anytime soon.
That bastard is clearly avoiding me.
I'll go to his office tomorrow morning.
Let's see where he can hide.
Rumor has it that
Mr. Shen was able to
connect with X Holdings
because he's involved with
the gang in Country P.
If he wants to,
it shouldn't be hard for someone like him
to hide Mr. Hua away.
Jianghu is a legal society.
If Hua Yong even so much as breaks a nail,
I'll kill Shen Wenlang.
So much for a legal society.
Mr. Sheng.
I feel terrible.
I want Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Sheng, I can't let you in.
Mr. Sheng, you can't go any further.
I really can't let you in.
Mr. Sheng, please stop.
Mr. Sheng! Mr. Sheng! You... Mr. Sheng!
Mr. Sheng.
Sorry, Mr. Shen is busy.
Whatever it is,
I can relay it for you.
Move.
I'm sorry.
You can't go in.
Mr. Sheng, you really can't go in.
[HS Group]
Let him in.
Mr. Sheng.
Here unannounced
first thing in the morning.
What can I do for you?
Shen Wenlang, where is Hua Yong?
Oh.
So you're looking for someone.
But
shouldn't you go to the police?
This is a biotech company.
I'm afraid I can't help you.
Shen Wenlang, I'll ask you again.
Where is Hua Yong?
[HS Group]
Mr. Hua is on leave.
What?
Didn't he tell you?
I thought a guy like Hua Yong
would report everything
to his dear Mr. Sheng.
After all,
he even came to work with a bug.
He actually betrayed me
and the company
to help you steal classified info.
Why would he
hide his whereabouts from you
and make you worry?
Stealing classified info?
Yes.
I was shocked too.
But we caught him red-handed.
Can't doubt a fact.
My dog is
fed by me
but wagging his tail at another man.
Of course I need to teach him a lesson.
Mr. Shen.
Jianghu is a legal society.
Employers and employees are equals.
Hua Yong works for you,
but he's not your slave.
Where is he?
You'd better not drag this out.
Or else...
Or what?
You're influential in Jianghu.
But as you said,
Jianghu is a legal society.
Our HS operates legally.
Not illegal
nor in debt.
No matter how capable you are,
what can you do to me?
To be honest,
Mr. Hua and I are in love.
He chose me
and wants nothing to do with you anymore.
As we all know,
I hate Omegas.
But Hua Yong is the only one
who can get my attention.
His pheromones smell just like him.
Usually plain...
Hah.
But during a special period,
he's exceptionally passionate.
Oh.
You know,
he seemed to have a fever the first night.
He was delirious
and called out another Alpha's name
in front of me.
Mr. Sheng.
You know him so well.
Why don't you take a guess?
When he spent the night with me,
who do you think he called out for
while crying?
Just because you're an S-tier Alpha,
you come to my territory alone,
and always try to subdue me
with your pheromones.
What a bully.
Where is Hua Yong?
Give him back to me!
Now you feel for him?
As an S-tier Alpha,
you actually made an Omega
risk it for you.
Isn't it a bit late
for concern?
Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Shen.
Please calm down.
Let's talk things out.
Get lost.
Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Hua is really not in the company.
What Mr. Shen just said was out of anger.
Please contain your pheromones.
Fighting won't solve the problem.
Let's sit down and talk things out.
Don't waste your time with this fool.
Does he look rational enough
to have a sensible dicussion?
Crazy bastard.
Shen Wenlang!
Stop talking.
Contain your pheromones!
Shen Wenlang!
Let go of me!
Gao Tu.
Are you okay?
Throw this rabid dog out
of my company!
Shen Wenlang.
This is not over.
Prepare a car now.
Inhaler...
My inhaler.
What?
What did you say?
Give me my inhaler.
Inhaler?
For your asthma?
Yeah.
I'll help you find it.
Where is it?
No, I can do it myself.
Stay away from me.
You're a Beta,
not sensitive to pheromones.
Gosh,
you reek of Sheng Shaoyou's pheromones.
Damn it.
His pheromones sure stink.
No wonder you have an asthma attack.
Ugh! Don't move!
Is this it?
Go to Heci. Drive faster.
No.
Not Heci.
-It's the best hospital in the city.
-Mr. Shen.
Not Heci.
Where should we go then?
Mr. Shen, I'm not going to Heci.
I don't want my sister to worry.
Okay.
Where do you want to go?
To No. 7 Hospital.
That's where I always go.
Gao Tu.
Gao Tu!
Hey.
Did you witness the fight
between Mr. Shen and Mr. Sheng?
Gosh, it was so scary.
Mr. Gao got hospitalized
from mediating it.
Thank goodness he's a Beta
who isn't sensitive
to pheromones.
If it were a low-tier Alpha or an Omega
mediating two S-tier Alphas,
they could've died on the spot.
Of course.
I was scared to death.
But why did Mr. Sheng fight with Mr. Shen?
Why else?
Because of Mr. Hua.
What does this have to do with Mr. Hua?
Is there a misunderstanding?
Of course not.
Think about it.
Other than Mr. Hua,
does Mr. Shen ever interact with Omegas?
Mr. Shen even only drinks tea
made by Mr. Gao.
He avoids us Omegas
like the plague.
But doesn't Mr. Shen hate Omegas?
That's why I wondered about
his sexual orientation.
Now that you mention it,
the puzzle is complete.
Huh?
Think about it.
Mr. Shen hates Omegas,
and Mr. Sheng is an S-tier Alpha like him.
They're a perfect match.
Maybe they were already dating.
And now, Mr. Hua has come between them.
No wonder Mr. Sheng was fuming.
He stormed right here
and lashed out at Mr. Shen.
Two S-tier Alphas together?
You have such a crazy imagination.
Alright, stop chatting during work.
Go back to your seats.
Doctor.
Yes?
How is he?
He's better after the drip.
However,
his body is too weak.
He can't recover in a day or two.
He needs further treatment.
Wait.
Aren't you the Alpha
who spends all day with him
even though
you hate the scent of Omegas?
Yeah.
Oh.
Finally acting like
you care about him now?
Humph.
Why don't you just focus on
torturing him less?
Hating Omega's scent?
Just man up already.
Psycho.
You...
Who told you to be
so good at keeping secrets?
Leak news to let him know where I am.
Mr. Sheng, the target is at X Hotel.
He seems to have an appointment.
Keep watching him.
Allen.
Be careful.
You must not alert them.
Don't worry, Mr. Sheng.
I'm the top private investigator
in Jianghu.
Mr. Sheng,
don't hang up.
Keep the line open.
Boss.
Boss, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Boss.
I-I-I'm sorry, Boss.
I'm sorry, Boss. I'm really sorry.
Boss, I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry.
Shut up.
You're hurting my ears.
Hello? Yes, got it.
What took you so long?
Something came up.
What's with your face?
Who hit you?
Who else could it be?
Sheng Shaoyou?
That rabid dog.
Even my secretary is in the hospital.
Damn my luck.
Listen.
Boss has only just calmed down.
He's in rut
and suffering mate-seeking compulsion.
You'd better watch your mouth.
Why should I baby him?
I even got a beating.
He's such a princess.
Sigh.
He got himself hurt all over
because of the mate-seeking compulsion.
Once he recovered a bit yesterday,
he started to deal with
the drug dealing of Country P.
Those who were just punished
are considered accomplices.
The six main culprits
who arrived yesterday
are all in the hospital,
four minors and two majors.
What are you talking about?
Four with minor injuries,
two serious injuries.
Holy.
Is he crazy?
So brutal.
It's not Boss' fault.
Someone used the new route to sell drugs
while Boss was away from HQ.
Super bold,
but not too smart.
The first batch was intercepted
before leaving the city.
If it were before,
Boss would've never let them leave alive.
Boss showing mercy? What a miracle.
Does Jianghu have good fengshui?
Hah.
Who knew there'd be such a day?
Who knows?
I heard
he's doing it for the man he loves.
Pfft.
Crazy.
We're here.
Once the door's open,
don't talk unless you have to.
Have you seen
the Omega in Room 9901?
That Omega with an orchid scent?
That pretty one.
He's obviously a good kid.
Gosh, what a pity.
Why?
That he is being
abused senseless by those violent Alphas.
Really?
I saw him from afar the day he moved in.
I didn't see his face clearly.
But an Omega who attracts so many Alphas
must be quite a looker.
Not just that.
That Omega is loose,
but he has an aloof face
like he has no urges.
If I were an Alpha,
if I saw him cry,
I'd do anything for him.
But Zhang from the night shift said
they go crazy in his suite.
A few nights ago,
he was covered in blood
and carried out by an executive.
Regardless of the business he's in,
it has to be a sin.
Why does a beauty like him
put himself through all that?
Leave him be.
Who knows? Maybe he's into it!
You saw it just now.
Just now, a bunch of Alphas
left his room all mighty.
A bunch of them!
You caught them in the act?
Not really.
Maybe I was mistaken.
Oh, come on. Stop lying to yourself.
How could you be wrong?
The 99th floor,
where X Holdings
receives VIPs exclusively.
Rich and powerful men
who can get whatever they want
are always looking for new thrills.
Besides,
with what goes on in Room 9901,
there must be many customers
who covet him.
If they take turns one at a time,
it will take forever.
So,
for efficiency,
appropriate overlapping is good news.
Many of his regular customers
are familiar with each other.
It's common for friends to engage in
group activities.
After all,
sharing an Omega is
also a kind of cooperation.
It shows their bond.
So you mean
he was covered in blood
because he was dealing with multiple...
-Multiple...
-Yes.
One Omega serving multiple Alphas,
entertaining them all at once.
Allen.
Bring him back.
W-What?
Allen, bring him back! Allen!
Allen!
Bring him back right now!
Mr. Sheng, I hear you just fine.
Please don't shout.
I don't want to be deaf.
As long as you bring him back,
name whatever price you want.
I'll owe you a favor for life.
Okay, don't worry.
Boqiao, have you been to X Hotel?
What's wrong, Shaoyou?
You sound off.
Cut the crap and answer me.
I'd been there a long time ago.
But not often. My brother didn't let me.
That is Country P's turf.
They're super wild, different from us.
My brother was worried
I'd be taken advantage of.
But I heard the new owner of X Holdings
made adjustments.
I don't know the details, though.
Shen Wenlang.
Shen Wenlang!
How dare you...
You're out of your mind!
After beating our men up like crazy,
how's he sleeping like a baby?
Get up.
Wenlang.
Get up!
So noisy.
Shen Wenlang.
Did the sky collapse?
The sky's fine.
But Wenlang was
beaten up by Sheng Shaoyou.
I warned you to be careful
since he can get
aggressive.
Did you fight back?
Of course!
I was being attacked!
You hurt him?
It's self-defense, get it?
No.
Where did you hurt him?
He wanted to strangle me,
so I kicked him.
Just one kick.
Mm.
Are you crazy?
How can you blame me for that?
I'll let this go.
You're inexperienced.
Be careful next time.
Don't hurt Mr. Sheng again.
There won't be a next time.
Hua Yong.
Do you think I enjoy this?
I'm repaying you for your help
when I started my business.
You're also my partner in HS.
Or else, do you think
I'd get involved in this drama?
Sheng Shaoyou is a dumb masochist
clinging onto you,
but I'm not dumb.
If it weren't for your stupid plot,
would I've got beat up?
Wenlang,
being grateful is a great quality.
I helped you, so you helped me.
If you need my help
in the future,
we can make a deal again.
Fair exchange of good karma.
Fair exchange of good karma?
Then could you please do me a favor
and be gentler
when you teach the subordinates a lesson?
Leave some men intact
for me and Chang Yin.
Anyone who leaves your room
becomes incapacitated and can't work.
Those guys from yesterday
are still lying in the ICU.
No, I can't.
Sigh.
Wenlang.
With a few losers
who want in on the drug business gone,
the world still keeps spinning, no?
You know
how much effort it took me
to bring the sinking ship
of Beichao Holdings ashore.
Anyone who wants to dirty my deck
has to be killed.
It's reasonable.
If anyone dares to do such business again,
I'll kill them right away.
You don't have to dirty your hands.
That's the spirit.
I know
your and Chang Yin's job
of managing the men isn't easy.
But Wenlang,
I showed them mercy.
After a few whips,
I let them go with their limbs intact.
Why're you still complaining?
Just a few whips?
A few more whips
would've killed them.
I didn't use much force.
If this kills them,
they're to blame for being too weak.
Alright, Wenlang.
Boss has left them a way out
to turn over a new leaf.
It's their blessing.
Don't cross the line
by getting involved with drugs.
Discipline your men.
Don't let me down again.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
Have you leaked the news
I asked you to?