[ABO Desire]
[Episode 2]
[Building 1, Unit 2,
Almond Lane 12, Room 106]
I'm sweating a lot.
Hope I don't smell.
I should've used the injectable inhibitor.
Secretary Hua.
It's me.
Secretary Gao.
Mr. Shen, Secretary Hua.
Here's the document for Monday's meeting.
Thank you.
We appreciate it, Secretary Gao.
You even came in on your day off.
You're welcome.
If there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave.
Happy weekend, both of you.
See you next week.
Wait.
Secretary Gao,
you're leaving in such a hurry.
Are you going back
to comfort your partner again?
Sorry, Mr. Shen.
I'm sorry...
for the sudden leave.
It's nothing.
There are enough secretaries on the team.
We'll do just fine without you.
Yes, sir...
Understood.
Do you have any other orders, Mr. Shen?
Make sure to clean yourself up
when you come back to work next week.
Don't you know how strong
your Omega scent is?
Sorry.
Don't come near me
with that filthy Omega scent.
It stinks.
[Shengfang Bio Participates in the
10th Global Biopharma Innovation Summit]
[Every second counts. Win or bust]
What are you doing with my phone?
Give it back.
Hold on.
Let me check
Mr. Sheng's WeChat Moments again.
There are only a few posts,
but you've looked a hundred times.
Give me back my phone.
Don't be so stingy.
You think I'm stingy? You're insane.
[Shengfang Bio:
Care for stray animals, alaways in action]
You dragged me out this morning
to help you move
to this godforsaken place.
Is it really that bad?
I think it's alright.
You call this alright?
Then go ask Sheng Shaoyou to move in!
Why are you so grumpy?
Did you take the wrong meds today?
You took the wrong meds today.
By the way,
why did you say that to Secretary Gao?
His sage scent actually smells kinda nice.
It's not as good
as floral scent or fruity scent,
but it's not bad at all.
Why did you have to rag on him?
If I say he stinks, he stinks.
It's none of your business.
Are we done moving here?
Give me back my phone.
I'm leaving.
With that awful temper,
no one's going to like you.
Mind your own business.
I'm not you.
I don't need to be liked.
Oh?
Is that so?
[President's Office]
Billions invested every year,
and no progress on targeted drugs?
Was the lab team completely useless?
The lead scientists
work overtime every day,
but drug R&D
indeed has its uncertainties.
There will always be results,
if you keep trying enough times.
Pheromone gland cancer hits 1 in 200,000,
but still no highly effective meds yet.
Do you know what that means?
It means once you get it,
you're basically waiting to die.
It also means
the market potential is huge.
Now my dad needs this medication too.
We're one of the top
biopharmacy companies in the country.
We've poured in manpower and resources,
yet there's no progress in research.
So we just sit and wait
for scraps from others? Pathetic!
Mr. Sheng,
we have...
No need to explain.
Chen Pinming,
you know better than anyone
how much Shengfang Bio
has invested into R&D.
I've spent billions.
And as my chief secretary,
you're telling me about uncertainties?
Tell me, how can X Holdings
and HS make breakthroughs,
but not Shengfang Bio?
Sorry, Mr. Sheng.
Secretary Chen,
I'm not being personal.
X Holdings and HS's targeted drug
hasn't even launched yet,
but Shen Wenlang already rejected
our deal without hesitation.
If we don't speed up,
once their drug launches,
Shengfang Bio's decade-long lead
in targeted drugs field will fall behind,
and our group will be stuck
in a more passive situation.
Is this what you want to see
as a founding member of the group?
Besides,
my dad needs this med to save his life.
If we don't make progress soon,
next time I see Shen Wenlang,
I'll be on my knees begging for the drug.
Shengfang Bio's chairman
leads on a targeted drug
for pheromone gland cancer.
It used to be big news.
Chen Pinming, you were also there.
You should know better.
Now we have to
beg others for their targeted drug
to save my dad's life.
How ironic is that?
If we can't make a breakthrough,
Shengfang Bio's reputation is done.
Mr. Sheng, that won't happen.
I'll organize all teams immediately
to break down the project's goal
and assign R&D tasks
precisely to every lab tier.
If there is any progress,
I'll report to you right away.
Okay.
Get back to work.
Hey, Shaoyou.
It's Boqiao. Are you free tonight?
Let's hang out at Royal Sky Club.
Not interested.
What's wrong? Are you in a bad mood?
Even if I were in a good mood,
I wouldn't waste time partying with you.
What do you mean, partying?
It's called socialnetworking.
Well,
then it's useless networking.
Rumor has it
that the X Holdings' person in charge
came to Jianghu a few days ago.
He might be at Royal Sky Club tonight.
You've always wanted to make a connection
with X Holdings, right?
Don't say I didn't inform you.
What time? What's the room number?
I haven't been here for a while.
Exactly.
It's already 12:30.
I have a meeting
tomorrow morning, I'm leaving.
Shaoyou,
don't leave yet.
Mr. UKW
might be on his way here. Just wait.
What UKW?
That mystery guy behind X Holdings.
He controls Country P's market,
but never shows his face.
You know who.
Boring, I'm leaving.
Hey, Shaoyou.
You haven't hung out in ages!
Stay a bit longer.
Let me tell you.
I've got some juicy intel for you.
It's all about that mystery guy.
Is your intel reliable?
Of course.
It came from my brother's
cooperative partner in Country P.
It's 100% reliable.
Apparently, X Holdings
used to be called Beichao Holdings.
The current person in charge
is the youngest son
of Beichao Holdings' founder,
and he's an illegitimate kid.
I heard he's not even 30 yet.
But don't let the age fool you.
He was the one who turned
Beichao Holdings
from a local giant in Country P
into a global titan
with branches all over the world.
They say this mystery man
has a strange personality.
He's extremely lowkey
and never socializes.
No one knows
what he looks like
except his confidant.
And there's something even weirder.
What is it?
It is said that
the first thing he did
after taking over the company...
was rename Beichao Holdings
to something totally bizarre, X.
Come on, cheers.
Come on, let's drink.
Hey.
Hold on.
How can I help you?
Sit here and have a drink with me.
Sorry.
I don't drink.
You work in a place like this,
and you say you don't drink?
Don't worry.
I'll give you tips after this.
Sorry,
I need to serve drinks in other rooms.
Excuse me.
Have fun.
Now in Country P,
the X family's so rich
that they could buy the entire country.
They run the game with an iron fist.
Why did he change its name?
Who knows?
They say "X" stands for mystery.
He renamed the company to match the fact
that Mr. UKW never shows his face.
Is that so? Maybe it stands for dumb.
Shaoyou,
you still hate illegitimate kids, right?
In my opinion,
people can't choose their birth or looks,
so the kids shouldn't be blamed.
My brother's cooperative partner
in Country P
has a few major deals with X Holdings.
That Mr. UKW is sharp, calculating,
and smart.
He's a top-tier talent.
No wonder he can easily
beat all the other heirs of that old man.
People also say
that Mr. UKW doesn't socialize
because he’s ugly,
and that's why he hides his face.
Isn't it good not to see people?
A rat in the gutter
should stay in the gutter.
An illegitimate kid like him,
even if he climbs to the top,
he still has to hide in the dark.
What a shameful person.
Shaoyou,
if you hate illegitimate kids that mcuh,
why are you trying to get close
to X Holdings' person in charge?
I keep business and personal separate.
If it's necessary,
let alone an illegitimate kid,
as long as it's profitable,
even cats can do business with rats.
Shaoyou,
are you heading home alone tonight again?
Are you sure
you don't want to bring a cutie with you?
Listen,
I'm very generous, you know.
You can pick one first.
No thanks. Keep them for yourself.
Guys with mysophobia are so picky.
Picking up an Omega at a club
won't kill you, right?
Enough.
It looks like tonight
the X Holdings fool isn't showing up.
I'm leaving.
Enjoy yourself.
[Aquarius]
You're too cute to just serve drinks.
Have fun with me.
[Sagittarius]
I'm very rich!
Name your price.
I'm sorry. I really can't.
[Sagittarius]
Hey.
You can't?
Don't play innocent with me.
Don't piss me off.
[Aquarius]
[Sagittarius]
Mr. Sheng.
Help me.
A little Omega dares to reject me?
What's going on?
It looks like two Alphas
fighting over one Omega.
That Alpha is releasing
the dominance pheromones.
Oh my!
He's an S-tier Alpha!
Shut the door, quick!
Here, Mr. Sheng.
I'm the OPS manager of Royal Sky Club.
I sincerely
apologize
for tonight's trouble.
Hua, why are you just standing here?
You caused such a scene on your first day.
Hurry up and apologize to Mr. Sheng.
Sorry, Mr. Sheng.
I...
No need to apologize.
A rude customer brought you bad luck.
But being unlucky is not your fault.
You're absolutely right, Mr. Sheng.
In our service industry,
it's rare to meet someone like you
who's willing to step up for others.
Hua is lucky enough
to have your help.
Isn't this place supposed to be
the most famous club in Jianghu?
What's with the bandit-style customer?
How can you accept a thug like that?
What's wrong with your boss, Zheng Yushan?
Is he really that desperate for money?
No, no, no.
Mr. Sheng, please let me explain.
What happened today
was just a small misunderstanding.
Our boss Mr. Zheng
often mentions you.
He says whenever
Mr. Sheng visits Royal Sky Club,
we must provide the best service.
We've already handed
the troublemaker to security.
You'll never see him here again.
Hua,
hurry and thank Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Sheng helped you a lot today.
Thank you, Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Sheng,
why don't you return to your room?
We'll send two fine bottles to you later.
It's on the house today.
No need.
Mr. Sheng,
I understand your time is precious.
Take care.
Hua, go see Mr. Sheng out.
[Aries]
I didn't expect to see you here.
Secretary Hua, your hands are really full.
You're so busy.
I...
No need to explain.
I don't have the time or interest.
Mr. Sheng,
could you give me your number?
No.
But...
If it's just to say thanks,
don't bother.
Or... do you want to come home with me?
No, I didn't mean that.
No need to throw yourself at me.
I'm not like Shen Wenlang,
so I'm not interested in stuffs
that deliver themselves to my door.
So cute.
[Innovative Bio Pharmaceutical]
Come in.
Mr. Sheng, Secretary Hua
from HS Group just came by.
Hua Yong?
Yes.
Secretary Hua asked me
to give this to you.
Secretary Hua said
he found one of your cufflinks
at Heci Hospital the other day,
he didn't have your number,
so he reached out to me instead,
and asked me to give it to you.
Mr. Sheng, I'll leave you to it.
I'll take my leave now.
Mr. Sheng,
I found your cufflink
at Heci Hospital the other day.
I've always wanted to return it to you.
That's why I asked you
for your number last night
to return it to its owner.
I'm sorry for the trouble last night.
I'm really sorry.
Thank you for helping me.
I appreciate it.
[Shengfang Bio Group]
Hello?
I got it.
I'll be right there.
The Chairman was in a bad shape,
but his vitals have stabilized for now.
But without highly effective meds
for pheromone gland cancer,
there's not much we can do.
So you're saying you can't cure him,
and he's just waiting to die?
Then why are you wasting my time here?
Sheng Shaoqing.
It's mainly because we don't have
the highly effective meds.
Can you stop screaming in public
while carrying the Sheng family name?
Well, well, isn't this Chairman Sheng?
This is a hospital, am I right?
I didn't expect to see you here.
Where were you when our father was dying?
Did you even shed a single tear?
Or...
maybe our dad's life didn't matter to you
once you got that chairman seat.
Master Shaoqing,
that's not fair for you to say.
Among all the kids in the Sheng family,
only Mr. Sheng works at the group.
He's been working nonstop,
like a spinning top.
[VIP Inpatient Department]
While the other young masters and ladies
can draw as they like,
or get in the film industry as they want.
Flying from Tokyo to Paris
on a whim.
But Mr. Sheng hasn't had
a single day off in three months.
-Even today...
-I'm talking to Sheng Shaoyou!
Who do you think you are?
It's none of your business, right?
Secretary Chen,
no need to waste your time on him.
Waste of time? Fine.
Then, efficient Chairman, Sheng Shaoyou,
answer a question for me.
I remember a year ago,
you started R&D
on the highly effective meds, right?
Where are they?
Show me.
Hey, say something!
The cure doesn't appear out of thin air.
Pharmacy R&D also takes time.
From initial planning to Phase 3 trials,
it takes at least 10 years.
I see.
So Sheng Shaoyou's just mute,
and you're just blind.
Do you want to go in and check
if my dad has ten years left to wait?
It's so funny.
The moment my dad's hospitalized,
everyone thinks they have a say over me.
Are you done?
If you think the research is slow,
why don't you join the lab yourself?
The lab doors aren't locked.
You...
Did I say something wrong?
Dad has more than one illegitimate child.
Sheng Shaoqi, Sheng Shaolin,
Sheng Shaoyue, Sheng Shaoxi,
and Sheng Shaowan.
As long as they are willing
to join the research team,
they're always welcome.
Why should everything fall on me?
Just because I'm the legitimate one,
I deserve all the hard work,
and you illegitimate kids
get to do whatever you want, right?
Right.
Being the legitimate one
is a big deal, huh?
The only difference between you and me
is that your mom married my dad
a little earlier.
Indeed.
That's a big deal.
When my mom co-founded
Shengfang Bio with Dad,
your mom was still
working at the Royal Sky Club.
Sheng Shaoqing,
while I still have patience,
I'm warning you, you better tone it down.
Or one day,
-when I stop cleaning up Dad's mess,
-You...
you might have to live off
your mom's old gigs.
You...
Sheng Shaoqing,
if you want
to join the meds research team,
you're always welcome.
But with your
high school dropout education,
I'm afraid you won't have
any constructive suggestions.
Chen Pinming, get the car ready.
What are you waiting for?
Get in.
Thank you, Mr. Sheng.
I've already
explained the overall situation.
You must pay the surgery fee this week,
or your sister's surgery
will have to be postponed.
Doctor, is there any way...
Can you do the surgery first,
and I'll pay later?
I'm really sorry.
I really sympathize with her condition.
But the cost is 600,000 yuan.
That's too much for post-payment,
and it goes against our hospital's policy.
Besides, you still owe some medical bills.
I already did my best
to save your sister's bed 291.
Sorry, doctor.
Thank you.
I'll try everything to get the money.
-That cufflink...
-HS's salary...
It seems like
your company treats you quite badly.
Secretary Hua,
you go to work in the morning,
flirt with the boss at night,
and even serve drinks
at a club after midnight.
You're working that hard,
yet you still can't get 600,000?
Instead of being an escort
at Royal Sky Club,
why not just steal a watch
off Shen Wenlang's wrist?
That alone's worth more than 60,000.
Mr. Sheng,
I work part-time as a waiter at that club,
but I don't do escort work.
And Mr. Shen and I are just coworkers.
Last night, when I asked for your number,
I didn't mean anything else.
I just wanted to return your cufflink.
Could you not assume the worst of me?
So they're just coworkers.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Do you remember
what that doctor just said?
What was his sister's bed number again?
Bed 291.
[Cashier Counter]
Hello, this is the bill for bed 291.
Could you please...
delay the payment for me?
I'll pay it back as soon as I can.
There's no outstanding balance
for bed 291.
In fact, 600,000 yuan was already prepaid
for the surgery and post-op care.
What? Prepaid?
Yes. You're the family
of the patient in bed 291, right?
Your friend already covered it.
My friend?
Are you sure there's no mistake?
There's no mistake.
[Cashier Counter]
He left quite an impression.
He's a tall, handsome S-tier Alpha.
He paid a large sum of money,
so I double-checked
the bed number several times with him.
It can't be wrong.
A tall, handome S-tier Alpha?
Could it be Mr. Shen?
Next please.
Come in.
Mr. Shen.
About the afternoon meeting,
the cooperative partner temporarily
requested to bring their R&D team.
So the venue has changed
from the Media Room 201
to the main conference room.
Got it.
Anything else?
Thank you, Mr. Shen,
for helping pay for my sister's surgery.
I promise I'll pay you back.
It's not a big deal.
Don't mention it.
Thank you so much.
-I will pay…
-You're welcome.
Whether you repay me or not
doesn't matter.
Just don't come to work
with that Omega scent again.
There are 15 minutes left
before the meeting.
Go back to work.
Okay.
I'll go prepare the meeting.
It looks like our Mr. Sheng
finally brought a new friend out tonight.
Gorgeous, what's your name?
Shuxin.
You look pretty,
and you have a pretty name.
No wonder you make people feel at ease.
[Unknown]
Thank you.
Shaoyou, you've changed a lot lately.
What?
Why did you suddenly
bring over an Omega with floral scent?
Don't you always like the fruity scent?
I told you the floral scent is better,
but you just didn't listen.
Why did you suddenly change your taste
and start liking the floral scent instead?
[Aquarius]
[Sagittarius]
Mr. Sheng.
Help me.
Floral scent is not bad.
Busy man, aren't you, Mr. Sheng?
Even at 10 PM on a weekend,
you're still getting calls.
Are you going back to work overtime?
Hello, Mr. Sheng.
I'm Hua Yong.
I got your phone number
from Heci's cashier.
I have something urgent to tell you.
[Unknown]
Mr. Sheng, sorry to bother you.
Hey,
who is this Hua Yong?
Since when do you take calls
from unknown numbers?
What if it's a scam?
Mr. Sheng, are you busy now?
I can call back later.
No need. What is it?
Did you pay for my sister's hospital bill?
I don't know why you did it,
but I really want to thank you.
I'll pay you back as soon as possible.
Besides money,
is there anything else you want to say?
Mr. Sheng, are you free this Saturday?
I'd like to treat you to a meal.
Don't be so formal with me.
You make me sound like I'm 60.
Sorry.
Mr. Sheng, are you free this Saturday?
Saturday?
I've got plans.
Oh.
Then maybe another time...
I've got plans with friends this Saturday,
why don't you just come to my place?
If it's inconvenient for you,
then just forget it.
A meal without sincerity
isn't worth my time.
No, I can make it.
Thank you, Mr. Sheng.
Please send me the exact time and address.
Okay.
-No way.
-Really?
Shaoyou,
tell me the truth.
We met right there.
Who exactly is this Hua Yong?
He even got you to break
your "no unknown calls" rule?
Keep drinking.
Hello, Sir.
This is a private club.
Sorry,
I'm here looking for a friend.
Do you have an invitation?
I didn't know I needed one.
I'm sorry.
You don't have an invitation,
so you can't enter this place.
But Mr. Sheng invited me here.
We get scammers claiming to know Mr. Sheng
from here to New York.
I'm not a scammer.
Since you said you're Mr. Sheng's friend,
then please give him a call.
Sir, please make a call somewhere else.
You're blocking the entrance.
Hua Yong.
Mr. Sheng.
What took you so long?
Because Line 2 was down for maintenance.
Sorry, I'm late.
It's fine.
Come in.
What are you waiting for?
Come on, hurry up.
Sorry, Mr. Sheng.
You said it's just a meal with friends.
I didn't expect something so formal.
If it's not appropriate,
I can leave right now.
Leave? Why?
You look just fine.
Hasn't Shen Wenlang
ever brought you to events like this?
Nope.
I just started working for him.
Mr. Shen usually brings Secretary Gao.
So today is your first time?
Yes.
Hello, Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Sheng.
Maybe I should go.
Why?
Because I'm not dressed properly.
What do you mean?
You might lose reputation because of me.
Well,
now that you mention it,
a little bit, yeah.
Then... I'll leave now.
I'll treat you to a meal next time.
You're already here.
And I've got a pretty big reputation,
even if you cost me a bit of it,
I'll be fine.
You can treat me
to a meal some other time.
But...
No buts.
You've already embarrassed me
with what you're wearing.
If you ditch me now
and let me walk in alone,
that'd be even worse.
Let's go.
This time, let's for get it.
But next time I invite you to a meal,
make sure to dress properly.
There won't be a next time, right?
No next time?
Yeah...
Mr. Sheng,
I don't have any other decent clothes.
That's easy to fix.
I'll have Chen Pinming
take you shopping sometime.
Shaoyou, I've been looking for you.
Why don't you come in?
Let's go.
Okay.
Here, try this.
Okay, thank you.
Here, have some more.
Yushan, I think next time
we should meet at your club.
No problem.
You can go to our club next time.
I'll arrange it.
Darn it.
I throw parties like this every week,
but they're never this lively without you.
I didn't get a chance to ask earlier.
Who is this?
He looks unfamiliar.
I don't think we've met before, huh?
I haven't seen you in a while,
where did you find this gem?
It's none of your business.
He also has the floral scent.
Hey, relax!
I'm sorry.
I mean...
I was just taking a whiff.
Don't get mad, okay?
Alright, Boqiao, stop it.
He's an Omega.
Behave yourself.
Don't scare off our new friend.
Fine.
I won't get too close.
Can I at least ask your name?
Hua Yong.
You are Hua Yong?
The one who got Sheng Shaoyou
to answer an unknown call?
I've heard a lot about you.
You're harassing my friend to my face now?
Li Boqiao,
can you act like a normal person?
Come on, I've hit on
your other friends before.
Why are you overreacting today?
Can't I sniff on him?
A little touch
won't cost him a finger anyway.
Boqiao.
Shaoyou barely comes to these gatherings.
If you keep this up,
he won't come again.
Fine.
I'll keep my hands off his gem.
How about this?
Let's drink.
We can still drink, right?
-Okay. Come on.
-Come on.
You're drunk.
It's not safe for you to go home alone.
Let me see you off.
By the way, Mr. Sheng,
Here's my repayment plan.
[Repayment Plan]
I know...
it may take a long time,
and the interest is low.
Technically, I don't have any collateral,
so I should be paying
more than the bank rate.
But once I pay off the principal,
I'll keep paying interest
at four times the bank's rate,
until everything's fully repaid.
There's a faster way, you know.
Sorry.
I don't have much salary.
Before I get promoted and get a raise,
this is already the fastest I can get.
Hua Yong,
be my partner.
If you say yes,
you don't have to pay me anything.
Sorry.
Mr. Sheng.
It might take a while,
but I'll pay you back as soon as possible.
Okay.
Shaoyou.
That Hua Yong you brought tonight,
I really liked him.
If you guys ever break up,
just let me know.
I wouldn't mind it.
Mr. Sheng, I'm here.
I'll walk you upstairs.
No need.
This alley is not safe,
I'm afraid your shoes might get dirty.
Okay.
I'll leave now.