Everyone is here.
Mm.
Likes to cry, big eyes, red lips,
has a narrow face, is fair and pretty.
These are what Mr. Sheng's
past partners have
in common.
The 32 exes you want to see
[A summary of Sheng Shaoyou's
Omega preference]
[Personal Information]
[Name: Chen An]
are all here.
He has such a bad taste.
It is said that Mr. Sheng
has never been in a relationship.
The exes you see
are just
his bed partners.
But, while Mr. Sheng
has a short-lived passion for his lovers,
his taste is very uniform.
Some people even joke that
in some way,
Mr. Sheng is also being
quite loyal like this.
Please...
don't be upset.
In my opinion,
Mr. Sheng may not have true feelings
to these exes.
Theoretically,
if they didn't truly love each other
while they were dating,
Mr. Sheng still haven't had
his first love yet.
Is that so?
Of course.
Among these Omegas,
Song Huancheng was with Mr. Sheng
for the longest,
and it was only for half a year.
If he really liked him,
[Personal Information]
[Name: Song Huancheng]
how could he get
tired of him in six months?
The one in white is Song Huancheng.
What are you waiting for?
Come here.
I broke up with Shaoyou long ago.
His pheromones are so strong.
Who is this person?
When my boss is asking about something,
even the Imperial Family of Country P
dare not talk to him standing up.
Sorry, I didn't know the rules.
Please be the bigger person
and forgive me.
How can he still be releasing pheromones
despite having a inhibitor patch on?
Why did he gather
all the Omegas
that Sheng Shaoyou had dated?
Is he seeking revenge on Mr. Sheng?
Sir,
Shaoyou and I broke up a long time ago.
He may not even remember my name.
Shaoyou?
What an intimate way
of calling him.
N-No.
I really haven't been in touch
with Mr. Sheng for a long time.
You were dating Mr. Sheng for half a year.
Are you trembling?
Don't be afraid.
Tell me.
What kind of Omegas does Mr. Sheng like?
One hour and six minutes.
I'm really sorry.
This is already the most effective
inhibitor patch in the market.
Unfortunately, it's still
not enough for you.
But don't worry.
The lab has designed
an effective injection inhibitor for you.
Once it has passed its testing,
you can start using it.
Please give me 10 more days.
Three days.
Chang Yin, three days at most.
I need to get an effective inhibitor.
Yes, I got it.
[N Years Ago]
Recently,
a sudden virus infection
and quickly invaded the world.
According to incomplete statistics,
there are more than
two billion people in the world infected.
The virus infection
has caused a huge panic
and strain on the medical resources
in the world.
But the degree is more serious.
Once infected, it would seriously affect
the patient's normal life.
Experts have found that
the virus can be transmitted...
These symptoms are similar to a cold,
but they are very serious.
Once infected,
it will seriously affect
the patient's normal life.
Experts found that
this virus can be transmitted
through droplets and air.
Everyone is now forced to wear a mask.
And it feels like everyone
in the world is getting sick.
When we treat a virus like this
as a normal flu,
huge amounts of deaths
will spread like a plague.
There is a high
mortality rate for the infected.
The professional team
made an official explanation
and answer to the questions
the press has.
Currently,
the experts have officially
named this global virus
[RV-Y46]
Y46.
They are also currently conducting
a deep investigation for
the infection caused by the Y46 pop virus.
According to the experts' research,
the mortality rate of
those infected by Y46 is very high.
Among the patients with AB blood type,
and patients with special blood types,
the mortality rate is nearly 100%.
A and O blood type patients
have a mortality rate of 86.5%.
B blood type patients are less likely
to have severe symptoms.
Their mortality rate is 0.5%.
Within the six months of Y46 virus attack,
those with AB blood type
have been wiped out.
The survivors,
apart from their distinction of gender
given their sexual organs,
according to their blood types,
there is now a distinction of
Alpha, Beta, and Omega
[Alpha, Beta, Omega]
that replaces
traditional gender distinction.
[Toilet]
It's becoming a new, mainstream,
gender distinction.
Alphas and Omegas who take up less than
15% of the population have developed
sexual glands. With that,
they develop pheromones,
and the cycle of sensitivity
and heats.
In order to mark
their spouse,
Alphas have evolved to bear fangs
when marking.
Biologists from the
University of Nottingham Medical School
believe that the Y46 virus
has revolutionized the human reproductive system.
A few experts even belive
it is a form of reintroduction...
The ABO gender system is named
the Omegaverse by sociologists.
These three major genders
[Omegaverse]
play different roles in the society.
Among them,
regardless of female or male,
an Alpha can impregnate their partner,
and Omegas can get impregnated easily.
On the contrary, B blood types that had
the highest survival rate,
while they make up
86.9% of the population,
their pregnancy rate is extremely low,
at less than 10%.
Many people believe that
this ABO social construct
is infinitely close to those of wolves
in some aspects.
[Desire]
[Episode 1]
Most people
are also used to the fact that
S-tier Alphas are
the highest of human beings
and are better than others in genes.
But recently, scientists found that
other than the existing
Alpha, Beta, and Omega,
there might be another
unique and rare gender,
Enigma.
Though the probability of one becoming
that is less than one in a billion,
it still shocked the whole academic world.
It's been so long.
Why haven't those bioexperts
figured out the evolution ABOs yet?
Experts are mostly unreliable.
That's normal. The expert also said
the peak of human evolution
is not S-tier Alphas
but the niche Enigma.
I heard that Enigmas
can also mark Alphas.
Shaoyou, what does Shengfang Bio,
the head of the business of
biochemical production in Jianghu City,
think about this situation?
Pure nonsense.
Just sensationalism.
Have you ever seen a niche gender
that can mark an Alpha?
Yushan, of course
Shaoyou wouldn't believe this.
He's an S-tier Alpha.
He's born with top pheromones.
He's used to being a king.
Of course he wouldn't believe
this one in a billion
Enigma that greatly surpass S-tier Alphas
the experts speak of.
Yushan.
You changed your perfume?
Yes. My new Omega bought it for me.
This perfume's quite popular these days.
It's not just popular.
This pheromone perfume is
called Drunken Branch.
It's so popular it's difficult to get one.
I heard HS Group
made a lot of money from this.
But...
But what?
It smells
exactly the same as Shaoyou's
own pheromones.
Shaoyou has always been very
conscious about the fact that
his scent has become something cheap
that can be bought.
That's why he hates the boss of HS, Shen Wenlang.
Shaoyou,
is that true?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
How could it be?
Don't listen to Li Boqiao's nonsense.
What nonsense?
When Shen Wenlang
invited you for a gathering,
didn't you find excuses to reject him?
Why do you suddenly change your mind?
Don't hate him anymore?
We're friends in business.
How could I hate someone?
I've always found it a pity
for not meeting Mr. Shen at the gathering.
Besides, if I really hate Mr. Shen,
why would I ask you to be the middleman
to ask him out?
I even agreed to meet at HS Group
at his convenience tonight.
What?
Shen Wenlang asked to meet at this hour?
It's so late.
How insincere.
It's your first meeting,
yet it took Wenlang so long to agree.
It's indeed not appropriate.
But his schedules seem
quite packed lately.
He might be busy during the day.
Shaoyou,
don't mind it too much.
HS Group is so successful,
doing well not only in common chemicals,
but also in biology medication.
Shaoyou. That sounds so superficial.
I'm just telling the truth.
HS Group
started making medication for less than
half a year, yet they were
chosen by the biggest
pharmaceutical company X Holdings of
Country P as the only collaborator
for their
pheromone gland cancer medication.
As the top decision-maker of the group,
Mr. Shen must be busy.
Yushan,
thank you.
For setting this up.
We are brothers.
You're welcome.
You two have fun.
A friend of mine is here,
I'm going to go say hello.
Okay, you go ahead.
Shaoyou. Did Yushan tell you?
What?
Shen Wenlang hates Omegas the most.
Don't bring an Omega with you
when you're going to meet
him for the collaboration.
Don't worry. You're well-informed.
I'll only take you with me.
No.
Not me.
I only know how to flirt with girls.
I feel sleepy when I hear you
talk business.
Oh, right, Shaoyou.
Did you ask Shen Wenlang to meet
because of your father's illness?
With the authorization of X Holdings,
HS Group has become the company that is
most likely able to find a cure
for pheromone gland cancer in China.
That's why you agreed
to meet Shen Wenlang
despite the late timing.
Mr. Sheng.
Director Wang, how is my dad?
He's still in a coma.
But he's out of danger.
The condition is not very optimistic.
Although the cancer cells haven't spread yet,
but the location of the tumor is special.
If we remove the tumor,
it would damage the gland.
For Alphas,
the survival rate of
a gland damage is zero.
So we dare not operate rashly.
It's the best result we can achieve
by maintaining this situation given
we don't have medication.
Is your father getting worse?
Although it's an indolent cancer
and doesn't spread easily,
thinking about it,
your father has been sick
for two to three years.
Could it be...
Nonsense.
My dad is still the same.
That's good.
It's almost time.
I'm leaving.
Help me tell Yushan.
Leaving so soon?
I heard that New Money Shen
is very narrow-minded.
He'd get back at people
who are late.
You do hate him.
Capitalists all don't speak their mind.
[HS Group]
Hello, Mr. Sheng.
I'm Mr. Shen's secretary, Gao Tu.
Welcome to HS Group.
Nice to meet you, Secretary Gao.
I'm Chen Pinming,
Mr. Sheng's secretary.
We came so late.
Thank you for working overtime,
Secretary Gao.
You're welcome.
Mr. Shen just finished his meeting.
Please come in.
All the lights are still on
at this hour.
Your company deserve its reputation.
Mr. Shen always leads by example.
Of course his subordinates
dare not slack off.
Please come in.
Mr. Sheng is here.
Come in.
Welcome.
Why are you here?
I'm sorry.
[HS Group]
This is my new secretary, Hua Yong.
What?
Mr. Shaoyou, you know him?
Yes.
I've always wanted to know Mr. Wenlang.
If I knew he is your secretary,
I would've asked him for your contact
instead of asking Yushan for help.
Hua Yong, you're really something.
You know our famous Mr. You.
If you had written on your resume
that you know Shengfang Bio's Mr. Shaoyou,
HS Group wouldn't make you
just a mere assistant secretary.
M-Mr. Shen.
Shengfang Bio is a competitor
according to our contract.
If anyone knows people from Shengfang Bio,
they must report in advance before
starting their jobs.
I really don't know Mr. Sheng.
I didn't mean to hide it.
Yes, we don't really know each other.
We just met at Heci Hospital once.
Secretary Hua didn't notice
and bumped into me in the lobby.
It was you.
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you earlier.
I'm sorry about that day.
I went to the hospital to visit my sister
and bumped into Mr. Sheng.
I'm really sorry about that day.
What's the use of saying sorry?
Go.
[HS Group]
Apologize to Mr. Shaoyou properly.
No need.
It's not a big deal.
[Hua Yong]
Mr. Sheng, my name is Hua Yong.
I'm really sorry about that day.
No need.
Secretary Hua, I'll keep the business card for Mr. Sheng.
[Hua Yong]
[HS Group]
Secretary Chen.
Mr. Shen and Mr. Sheng
are friends at first sight.
I believe they have many things
to talk about.
How about this?
Let Secretary Hua and I
take you to the lounge next door.
Let's have tea while waiting for them.
Mr. Sheng, I'll wait for you outside.
Please, Secretary Hua.
Mr. Wenlang really thinks highly of us.
Putting us in your list of competitors.
Of course.
Shengfang Bio dominates the industry
in Jianghu in terms of scale.
Of course you're an important competitor.
Those talks about scale
is just what outsiders think.
In my opinion,
HS's business structure is healthier.
From common chemicals
to targeted medicine research,
HS is diversifying very quickly.
The winner takes them all.
Are you trying to say that I'm
but a jack of all trades?
Not at all.
Compared to the Shengang Bio,
HS entered the biomed industry a little later.
As the saying goes,
"To stand on the shoulders of giants."
Unlike you, who does everything with
pure skills,
we are just lucky.
To have gotten the
exclusive information on
pheromone gland cancer medication
research results
from X Holdings.
You're too modest.
In the whole world,
X Holdings is also a super
domineering in the industry.
Twenty years ago,
80% of Country P's
main grain transaction was by them.
After the pandemic,
they developed
the global patent for
pheromone inhibitor.
The annual income of X Holdings last year
was 30%
of Country P's GDP.
One could say they're
a monster in the industry,
and a super powerful
organization of Country P.
To be able to stand on the shoulders
of such shoulders,
Mr. Wenlang, you are no ordinary person.
You flatter me.
Mr. Shaoyou,
are you using our
popular pheromone perfume, Drunken Branch?
I'm so forgetful.
You're an S-tier Alpha.
Why would you use our
pheromone perfume?
I've heard of it.
Your own pheromones smell
very similar to our Drunken Branch.
This means I'm fated with HS.
Yes.
If there's no fate,
why would we sit together and chat?
Since it's fate,
I'll cut to the chase
and stop going in circles.
Shengfang Bio,
as the first research institute to
research on pheromone gland cancer,
is very interested in the
targeted drug research
HS has.
Shengfang is willing
to purchase 60% of HS's shares.
The premise is that you have to share the
-research results of the targeted drug–
-Mr. You.
The current society is very impatient.
Many people call themselves entrepreneurs,
yet they manage companies like they're
raising pigs,
fattening them up to sell them everywhere,
thinking of only cashing out.
But I founded HS singlehandedly.
I'm raising it like my own son.
I love it deeply.
I never thought of
selling shares or our core technology–
Three billion.
Mr. Wenlang,
I'm a straightforward person.
No one will betray their son
just for a lot of money.
3.5 billion.
Many people don't sell their sons
not because they don't want to sell them,
but because the buyer
is not sincere enough
and the price is not high enough.
Mr. Shaoyou is really sincere.
Thank you for your appreciation.
Unfortunately, I'm not short of money.
I'm afraid I'll have to let you down.
Even 35 billion can't convince you.
It seems the rumor is right.
Your family background
is really unfathomable.
But it can never be compared to
how rich and generous Shengfang Bio is.
3.5 billion without batting an eyelid.
How generous.
Of course it's because
HS Group is worth it.
To be honest,
I'm determined to get
the targeted drug's research outcomes.
A gentleman helps others
with their wishes.
Since Mr. Wenlang doesn't want to
give up the shares,
please consider selling
the targeted drug project.
We are willing to continue
investing with you
to speed up the clinical trial
of the medicine
so that the targeted drug can be
sold in the market as soon as possible
and benefit more patients.
Mr. Shen,
I want to make friends with you.
But that depends on how highly you think
of us Shengfang.
Damn it. He is so persistent.
When I get the core technology
of the targeted drug,
let alone 3.5 billion,
I wouldn't give you even 350 bucks.
I do feel a connection between us.
I'm sure we can be good friends.
However, let's just forget
about the collaboration.
Why?
Do you HS look down on us Shengfang?
Of course not.
It's just the patent of targeted medicine
is our core asset.
Even brothers would
separate their assets.
Although I want to make less friends with you,
I can't sell our core technology
just for this.
I understand what you mean.
It seems the fate
between Shengfang and HS is
not quite there yet.
We need to build it up more.
In that case,
I won't bother you.
Mr. Wenlang, let's talk another day.
I'll find a way to pay for the surgery.
Okay, thank you for your understanding.
Mr. Sheng...
He's so petty.
How cute.
Secretary Hua.
You're still here?
I was just taking a call.
Are you getting off work?
Secretary Hua, where do you live?
Don't think too much.
You may not know, but
a full-time employee who
gets off work after 9 p.m.
will get their taxi fare reimbursed.
Secretary Hua, you're still
on your probation period, right?
If it's on the way, I can send you
home by cab first.
No. 12, Xingren Lane.
Thank you, Secretary Gao.
I'm sorry,
but I happened to overhear in the lobby,
that...
Secretary Hua, you have family
hospitalized in Heci?
Heci is a well established
hospital in Jianghu.
Though the building is a little old,
they have the best
medical funds and equipments in Jianghu.
It's just, they're a little expensive.
They are.
I have a sister who is also
in Heci hospital.
It's been many years.
We've been waiting for a surgery.
So,
I understand how you feel.
[Shen Wenlang]
Okay, I got it.
You said you didn't like Omegas.
Secretary Gao.
Are you a Beta?
I heard from HR that
Mr. Shen and you were high school classmates.
You've been working
with Mr. Shen for many years.
It must be hard working with Mr. Shen.
Not at all.
Mr. Shen is actually a good boss.
Although he has high
requirements for work,
he never gives his
subordinates a hard time.
Since middle school,
Mr. Shen rarely came into contact
with any other Omegas.
Speaking of which,
you're the first Omega
working with Mr. Shen.
I've heard about it
since my first day of work.
That Mr. Shen hates Omegas.
Did Mr. Shen tell you that?
No.
Secretary General Qin said it.
I see.
If you need my help
in your work,
just let me know.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you, Secretary Gao.
See you tomorrow.
Ma'am.
Can you go to a nearby
convenience store?
I need to buy something.
Okay.
[Desire Convenience Store]
Welcome to Desire Convenience Store.
HS's laundry products have been launched.
Please take a look.
[Spray inhibitor]
[Spray inhibitor] [Painkiller]
Sir, inhibitors can only
be used during heats.
If you use it long term, it will cause
pheromone disorder and severe headaches.
If it's serious, it might cause shock
and endanger your life.
In addition,
you can't use painkillers
and inhibitors at the same time.
Thank you.
But I'm a Beta.
The painkiller is for my headache.
I'm buying the inhibitor for my friend.
Okay.
In compliance with
the drug control measures,
I need you to register here.
Thank you.
This is a spray inhibitor.
Just one spray can help
inhibit pheromones.
But the most common ones
are patches.
She doesn't have to explain this to me...
I'm probably an expert
when it comes to inhibitor use.
Come in.
[HS Group]
Mr. Shen.
Where is Gao Tu?
I haven't seen him all morning.
Secretary Gao applied for
a last minute leave.
Leave?
Yes.
I told you to report anything related
to Gao Tu
to me directly, didn't I?
Sorry, Mr. Shen.
You were in a meeting.
I didn't get the time time to tell you.
Why did he ask for a leave?
He's on leave to help his partner
with their heat.
Secretary Gao isn't married, is he?
You're right.
But according to
the Omega protection regulations,
when Omegas who have cohabitated
with their partners for more than
two years are in heat,
their partners are required
to accompany them.
Got it.
Okay, Mr. Shen.
I'll get back to work.
Stop right there!
Where's the money?
Where did you hide my turnover money?
There's none! You lost all the money!
How can I have money?
How can there be no money?
Give me your bag!
-No!
-Give me your bag!
Darn it. There's really no money.
Go sell your body if you have no money!
You're an Omega.
It's worth something, isn't it?
You bitch!
You gave birth to a useless Beta son.
And our daughter is an Alpha
that's always sick.
Just you wait.
I'll come again.
Make sure you have money by then!
Mom, I've differentiated.
I'm not a Beta–
Shh...
Little rabbit, you are a Beta.
You're a Beta with asthma.
You've just became an Omega,
yet I'm leaving.
There are many things
I can't tell you one by one.
But you must remember one thing.
Don't let anyone
know you're an OMega.
This is an inhibitor inhaler.
I've taken off it's label.
If anyone asks you,
just say it's asthma.
You must use it long term.
Don't let anyone smell
your pheromones.
Do you understand?
You have to promise me.
Understand?
Say yes.
Do you understand?
Mom, I understand.
I won't tell anyone.
Mom, don't cry.
Remember, you're a Beta.
You're a Beta.
Hello?
Secretary Gao.
You finally picked up.
Secretary General.
Is there anything urgent?
Sorry to bother you when you're resting.
But it's urgent.
I gave you a encrypted
hard disk last weekend.
Do you remember?
It's with me.
The information and data report
for this Monday's meeting
are all in this hard disk.
Secretary Hua is in charge of
the Monday regular meeting.
Should I ask Secretary Hua to pick it up
or could you pass it to him?
-The whole house reeks of pheromones now.
-Hello?
-I can't let anyone come.
-Secretary Gao, are you listening?
I-I'll deliver it to him.
Thank you so much.
This means so much to me.
But...
is it okay to leave your Omega
home alone
in their heat?
It should be fine if it's just
for a short time.
Okay, thank you so much.
My fever has gone down.
My heat should be over.
It should be fine to
deliver it to him, right?
Mr. Gao, your long-term abuse
of pheromone inhibitors
has caused great damage to your
pheromone gland.
Based on your current situation,
you can't use any inhibitor
for the time being,
especially injected ones.
Your heat is coming.
Your glands are worn down.
I suggest you stay
[Pheromone clinic]
in the hospital for this heat cycle.
Doctor, I can't stay in the hospital.
You should at least take a leave and rest.
Doctor.
What should I do if I don't want
my pheromones leak?
Other than my sister,
no one knows I'm an Omega.
I can't use inhibitor patches.
Mr. Gao.
You've been here
for years.
With all due respect,
you should see a psychiatrist.
You refuse to acknowledge
your identity as an Omega
and are even very self-abased.
Is it because of your partner?
Does he not like your scent or...
Sorry.
This is mainly my guess.
After all, the amount of inhibitors
you've used is too high.
Using huge amounts of inhibitor inhalers
every day
is a huge burden to your body.
At the same time, I want to remind you,
if my guess is true,
your other half is suspected of abuse.
According to the
ABO Equal Rights Agreement–
No.
It's not like that.
Doctor, I'm single.
That's even worse.
It's very dangerous for a single Omega
who is not pregnant to use
inhibitors this much.
This will cause pheromone disorders.
It'll even endanger your life.
Besides, using injections during heats
is already a toll for your body.
Don't you feel pain?
I take painkillers.
Nonsense!
Ignoring what the doctors tell you and
taking inhibitors is one thing,
but you're taking painkillers while using
injected inhibitors during your heat?
Do you want to die?
It's just passing a document.
It's not like I'm going to be
in contact with people for a long time.
I'm sure I can cover my pheromones
by taking an inhibitor.
Secretary Gao.
I live in Room 106, Unit 2, Building 1, No. 12, Xingren Lane.
Please send it over. Thank you.
[Room 106, Unit 2, Building 1, No. 12, Xingren Lane]
I'm sweating so much.
Hopefully I don't smell.
I should've used an injected inhibitor.
Secretary Hua.
It's me.
Secretary Gao.