[Episode 6]
Did you spread the word like I told you?
Yes.
We've got a tail, persistent little rodent.
Probably snuck into the hotel by now.
How long will these injuries last?
You should thank your rut and mating disorder.
They drained most of your stamina.
With your freakish healing ability,
it's a miracle that you're still alive.
He heals too fast.
What if Mr. Sheng can't see it?
Then let him take you home.
Give Chang Yu a break.
Let's get down to business.
After this meeting,
I need to go to the hospital.
Thanks to Sheng Shao You,
my secretary's hospitalized
and still hasn't woken up.
Secretary Gao?
Yeah.
Orchid scent, should be here.
Found him yet?
Not yet.
Oh, Wen Lang.
I heard from the pharmaceutical
development team
that the targeted drug has already
entered the formulation development stage.
Overall, progress has been going smoothly,
and they've also secured special approval.
That's enough for today.
I'm leaving.
Mr. Sheng will harrass you again.
Better rest up.
Get tough enough to take a beating.
You think I need to get tough for that?
Psycho.
We'll meet again soon.
These days have been rough.
He used to be with Sheng Shao You every day.
Leaving a rut partner is hard enough,
plus dealing with these assholes.
With his temper,
enduring this must have drained him.
Great summary.
Don't do that again.
Boss is in a mood.
You might get dragged down.
I spotted a target.
If you can take out Shen Wen Lang,
I'll add another 100 million.
Mr. Sheng, I'm a detective,
not a hitman.
Bring him back by any means.
Don't worry.
Don't be afraid.
Mr. Sheng sent me.
He sent you to take me home?
Yes. It's not safe here.
Let's go.
How do I know you're not lying?
Mr. Sheng, the target
wants to confirm with you.
Was it really you who sent me here?
Put him on the phone.
Here you are.
Yong, it's me, Sheng Shao You.
Mr. Sheng.
Where are you?
Almost there.
Okay.
I'll go downstairs now.
Mr. Sheng, please prepare a long coat.
Fine.
Show some professionalism.
You're paid.
Keep your eyes shut.
Don't be afraid.
If he stares again,
I'll gouge his eyes out.
Hua Yong.
Let's go.
We're here.
Don't be afraid.
It's over.
Let's go home.
There, there.
Don't be scared.
Hua Yong.
It's me, Sheng Shao You.
Look at me.
It isn't anyone else.
Don't be afraid, it's me.
Mr. Sheng…
Yes, it's me.
See?
It's me.
- Mr. Sheng.
- I came to take you home.
Is it really you?
Am I dreaming?
It's me.
For real.
It's not a dream.
Hua Yong, I'm sorry.
I was too slow and made you wait too long.
Change your clothes, okay?
I want to take a shower.
You have too many injuries and can't get wet.
Let the doctor check first, okay?
I don't want a doctor.
I want a shower.
Fine.
Take a shower first.
I'll wait outside.
Call me if you need anything.
I'll be right here.
I won't move an inch.
Okay.
Hua Yong, I won't do anything.
I just want to check on you.
If you won't see a doctor,
let me inspect your wounds.
I need to know how bad they are.
Done.
It'll be okay.
Everything will be okay.
Don't be afraid.
It's all over.
Mr. Sheng.
You want intel on the targeted therapy
for glandular cancer, don't you?
Well, I've got it.
The full list of core members
from the research team.
I'll give it to you, okay?
You don't want this?
Don't think about that now.
All I want is for you to feel better soon.
But if you don't want it...
I have nothing left.
This is all I have.
Don't say that.
You have me.
Hua Yong, you have me.
Morning.
Why don't you sleep a little longer?
I just can't.
Then it's perfect timing.
I bought breakfast.
Let's eat together, okay?
Didn't you lose your phone?
I got you a new one.
Thank you, Mr. Sheng.
Don't mention it.
I already installed the usual apps for you
and got you a new SIM card.
If anything comes up, you can call me anytime.
Okay.
I'll stay home with you these few days.
Once you feel better...
Mr. Sheng, I know...
you fell behind on work looking for me.
You must have a lot to do.
You don't need to stay with me.
I'll be fine.
I can't leave you alone.
Why?
Because I like you a lot.
[President's Office]
[Drug dev core members, link]
[Elioy Huang, Kipuka Qiu, Seeky Li,
Ocean Jiang, SDU, SSDU]
Mr. Sheng?
Has Shen Wen Lang arrived at HS?
Yeah, he just entered the parking garage.
I've been watching him.
Good, keep him there.
I'm on my way.
You know I hate Omegas,
but Hua Yong is the only one who interests me.
Mr. Sheng.
Your face...
Got it from a scrape.
Did you eat dinner?
Yeah.
What'd you eat?
Is the temperature
of the air conditioner too low?
Your hands are freezing.
Does it still hurt?
Nah.
Why the smile today?
Because you look cute with a bruise.
Cute?
Yes.
Very cute.
Hua Yong.
You might not believe this,
but I didn't ask Chen Pin Ming
to plant the bug in your bag.
Two years ago,
my father contracted pheromone gland cancer.
I did need the targeted drug intel,
but I'd never put you at risk.
Don't cry, it's my fault.
But I won't let this happen again.
I won't let you get hurt again.
Trust me, okay?
Mr. Sheng...
Yes?
Promise you won't fight anyone again.
I'll worry.
Why?
Because I like you a lot, too.
Mr. Shen.
Can't you find a decent place to live?
What are you doing here?
HR gave me your address.
The road's too narrow.
I parked at the intersection.
Walked the rest of the way in.
This place isn't for you.
Cut the crap. That's up to me to decide.
Open the door.
Gao Tu.
Aren't you gonna invite me in?
It's not convenient
I've been sick these days,
so I haven't cleaned the room.
The place is a mess, and…
That Omega lives here too?
What Omega?
The one who goes into heat often.
No, there's no one here.
Then there's nothing wrong with me entering.
Do you live alone?
Yeah.
Am I not paying you enough?
Why live in a dump like this?
The company pays me well.
I just have a lot of personal expenses.
If you know money's tight,
then stop paying me back that much every month.
Didn't I tell you?
What I lent you doesn't matter.
- You don't need to pay me back.
- That won't do.
I'm already immensely grateful
that you're covering for me.
Not paying you back wouldn't feel right.
I don't usually have guests over.
Is water okay?
Anything's fine.
Take a seat.
What brings you here, sir?
Can you stop with the "sir" all the time?
This isn't the office.
You aren't even 30 yet. Don't be so stiff.
Okay, but you came all this way
just to tell me I'm stiff?
What happened to your face again?
Don't ask.
That idiot Sheng came after me
this morning in the parking lot.
We got into another fight.
You two aren't middle schoolers.
Why are you always fighting?
I didn't start it.
He picked a fight with me.
Why did he do that?
He...
How's Secretary Hua doing?
Is he back at work?
Why do you care how Hua's doing?
Is he that important to you?
Sorry. You're right, it's none of my business.
Always fussing over an Omega
or meddling in other people's lives.
Worry about yourself first.
Don't make mistakes
like adding an extra zero in the budget again.
You're right.
I'll be more careful.
Anything else?
It's getting late.
If there's nothing else,
maybe you should head back.
You're kicking me out?
This area isn't very safe at night.
It'd be better if you got home earlier.
You think I want to stay in this dump?
The whole place reeks of Omega.
If someone likes it, let them stay.
What are you doing?
Why are you kicking my door?
You crazy?
Sorry, I bumped into it.
The hallway light's been out for a while.
So, it's easy to trip.
The young man upstairs
came back from working overtime last month.
The corridor had no lights
and he was climbing the stairs,
looking at his phone and sending messages.
He almost fell down.
It's very dangerous, so you must be careful.
You got it?
Okay.
Thanks.
Sir, I've fixed all the hallway lights.
Your friend won't fall again coming home.
Great.
This place is a dump.
Even the streetlights are dim.
What if he gets hurt coming back at night?
Replace all the streetlights
with brighter bulbs.
That's the city's job.
I'll pay you triple.
Just get it done. Now.
No problem.
Go on.
Mr. Sheng, try not to worry too much.
The patient's condition is much better
than when I first saw him.
His recovery speed
has exceeded my expectations.
That's good.
If there's nothing else, I'll take my leave.
Doctor Wang, thanks for making the trip.
You're too kind.
I was just passing by on my way home.
It's my honor to help.
Let me walk him out.
Okay.
Oh, Mr. Sheng.
You mentioned that
during your last rutting period,
you had a pheromone disorder
and lost an important client because of it.
Does that still happen?
I haven't lost control recently.
But I've been feeling exhausted,
weak all over for no reason.
Your next rut is approaching, right?
Yes, in a few days.
As a high-level Alpha, this should be rare.
If it were an Omega
I'd suspect targeted luring pheromones
from an Alpha causing passive heat.
But as an S-class Alpha, that's unlikely.
Most likely, work stress is causing
transient pheromone disorder.
You're young, Mr. Sheng.
Take care of yourself first.
Your career is a marathon, not a sprint.
Thanks, Doctor Wang. I understand.
Oh, Mr. Sheng, one more thing.
As an S-class Alpha,
the patient is still too weak
to tolerate Alpha scents.
To prevent secondary harm from passive heat,
keep some distance during the rut.
I'll prescribe the same Omega
calming pheromone spray as last time.
It should help during your rut.
Thanks.
We've recruited an elite team
from Wall Street's top firms
specifically for this short-selling plan.
HS Group has a concentrated equity structure
with a high proportion of pledged shares.
If the value of Shen Wen Lang's
pledged shares drops drastically,
he'll have to inject cash flow
to cover the deficit
to avoid forced liquidation.
Right, this makes it easier
for our bidding team to snatch their projects.
Those projects require
huge capital investments.
Shen will be stretched thin
trying to cover the market value loss.
Also, our bidding team has completed
preliminary talks with the design institute.
Many standards in the project blueprints
already favor us.
- Chen Pin Ming.
- Yes.
I want their stock price below IPO
within a week.
Mr. Sheng, you're being too conservative.
Based on the plan you drafted,
Shen Wen Lang will count himself lucky
if he avoids forced liquidation.
Understood, Mr. Sheng.
[Why is HS' stocks plunging?]
[Internal trading and stock manipulation?]
[HS manipulating stock sales for profit!]
[HS bombarded by complaints]
[Jiang Hu's authorities investigating...]
[HS stocks continue to drop!]
[HS stocks take massive plunge for annual low!]
[HS stocks take massive plunge for annual low!
Many speculate reasons for it!
Mr. Shen.
Have a seat.
Mr. Shen, we lost all three projects
we bid on recently.
Who won them?
- Sheng Fang Biotech.
- Why?
They colluded on bids with ultra low prices,
sabotaging our efforts by all means.
Mr. Shen, regulatory authorities
received numerous reports
alleging we manipulated our own stock.
CSRC has launched a task force to investigate.
Mr. Shen, our securities department got a query
from the the industry Stock Exchange.
Regulators require us
to explain promptly the project losses
announced in our statement
to stabilize the stock price
and restore investor confidence.
It's just a few projects.
Long-term, they won't
affect company operations.
HS has robust cash flow,
as well as healthy debt-to-equity and profits.
Short-term market fluctuations
are just temporary competition.
Yes.
Secretary Gao summed it up well.
Long-term, our diversified business structure
and broader profit sources
give us stronger risk resistance.
Also, the pheromone gland cancer targeted drug
developed with X Holdings
has completed formulation,
securing expedited clinical trial approval.
It should launch soon.
Yes.
Third-party data shows pheromone gland cancer
has a 5/100,000 incidence rate.
The special drug's value is obvious.
Launching it will elevate HS in pharmaceuticals
and also and open a massive revenue stream.
- Right.
Secretary Gao is correct.
Let's check again.
Okay.
[Resignation Letter]
Don't come near me
with that filthy Omega scent.
It stinks.
As everyone knows, I hate Omegas,
but Hua Yong is the only one who interests me.
His pheromone smells just like him,
faint on normal days,
but surprisingly intense during his heat.
Here's the thing.
The first night,
he had a fever and was delirious.
He called another Alpha's name
right in front of me.
Mr. Sheng, since you know him so well,
guess who he cried out for that night
while lying beside me.
[Resignation Letter]
[Gao Tu]
Secretary Gao.
Secretary General.
Secretary Gao, your speech was brilliant.
- Thanks.
- These are tough times.
Luckily, Mr. Shen has
a right-hand man like you,
so in tune with him.
Otherwise, he'd be even more stressed.
Old classmates are different.
One look from Mr. Shen
and you know exactly what to say.
No wonder colleagues say he's more at ease
in meetings with you around.
All right, I won't keep you.
I'll prep the next meeting's materials.
Okay.
Good luck.
[Resignation Letter]
[Gao Tu]
Maybe at a later time.
Hello?
Mr. Hua, it's me.
Secretary Chen.
Yes.
Sorry to call so late.
I need to tell you
Mr. Sheng has something urgent
and won't be home for a few days.
He asked me to let you know
so you wouldn't wait up.
Oh.
Okay.
Get some rest.
Sure.
Staying out for a rut is a bad habit.
You need to change.
Mr. Sheng, you're back.
Did you miss me?
Yes.
What's wrong?
You look a bit down.
No.
Just tired lately.
Is it because you missed me too much
that you're exhausted?
I missed you a lot.
Mr. Sheng.
Are you asleep?
Yeah?
What's wrong.
Do you think I'm filthy?
Nonsense.
Then why did you spend your rut
with another Omega?
When did I…
Can't you stay with me?
You...
Do we have to go all the way?
Hugs, kisses, sharing the same bed...
Was none of it enough for you?
Stop overthinking.
It's late.
Go to sleep, okay?
Hua Yong.
Doctor, Hua Yong just passed out.
His pheromone overflow is really bad.
What should I do?
Mr. Sheng, calm down.
I gave you a suppressant.
There should be a vial at home.
Look for it. An injectable small bottle.
I found it.
Find it and give him the shot.
He'll feel much better after that.
But you still need to
bring him to the hospital.
My student's on duty tonight.
I'll have him wait for you
in the emergency room.
Given his condition,
he may need to be hospitalized.