[Episode 7]
I found it.
Find it and give him the shot.
He'll feel much better after that.
But you still need to bring him
to the hospital.
My student's on duty tonight.
I'll have him wait for you
in the emergency room.
Given his condition,
he may need to be hospitalized.
I'm so fucking sick of Sheng Shao You.
Keep your voice down. I'm in the hospital.
Sheng Shao You is sick?
Why can't it be me?
You're sick?
What are you doing here?
If I didn't come, Chang Yu would
and it'd be worse if Sheng Shao You saw him.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sick.
Can't you tell?
I'm asking about how this happened.
I increased the dosage of my pheromone modifier.
Are you crazy?
Yeah.
Mr. Sheng spent his rut on a island
with some other Omegas...
For seven days.
So what?
Look at you.
Your face is as pale as paper.
Why torture yourself like this?
What are you trying to get from this?
Are you trying to compete for attention
against other Omegas?
Are you hoping Sheng Shao You will care?
Is that so wrong?
You've gone completely mad.
Mr. Sheng is too charming.
The multitudes who adore him
would drain oceans with their devotion.
What choice do I have but to try?
You're the reason
Sheng Shao You has been harassing me non-stop.
I thought he was a romantic,
but he's just a cheating bastard.
He just hit you a few times.
You didn't lose a limb.
Why's an Alpha being so petty?
You sure are gracious.
Well, why do you care who he has sex with?
It's different.
Mr. Hua, are you awake?
- Don't come in.
- Okay, but it's time for your checkup.
I'll bring the doctor in ten minutes, okay?
Sure.
There are bodyguards outside.
How did you get in?
You climbed the window?
This is the fourth floor.
Didn't expect you to care about me.
I just don't want your death
to mess up my plans.
I never understood what Sheng Shao You had
that made you go to such lengths,
chasing him from Country P to Jiang Hu.
Now I fucking get it,
you're both goddamn lunatics.
Thanks for the compliment.
But since you climbed four floors to my ward,
you must want more than just to flatter me.
Have you seen the news?
Sheng Shao You shorted HS stocks maliciously
and sabotaged all our bids.
He then reported us to CSRC
like a thief crying thief.
So?
So, you two are perfect for each other.
Get married tomorrow, lock yourselves up,
and stop ruining the lives of ordinary folk.
Mr. Sheng is amazing.
Yes, so amazing.
CSRC already sent a query letter.
Hua Yong.
Your amazing Mr. Sheng
caused huge losses to our company.
What will you do to make up for that?
Mr. Sheng has always been amazing.
How is that my problem?
Besides a duck in hand won't fly away.
Wen Lang, you just failed to hold on.
Whose fault is that?
Why should I pay?
Because the Alpha I chose is better than yours?
Better my ass.
He colludes on public bids
and undercuts us at cost price.
If you agree,
I'll collect evidence and sue him.
No, I won't break my Alpha's heart for money.
Tell you what, I'll cover the losses.
But from now on, avoid Sheng when you can.
Do you think I can avoid him?
He's the one hunting me down.
By the way,
your bidding team needs serious work.
Learn to handle collusive bids quickly.
Hindsight is useless and just a waste of time.
If you want something, take it.
Anything less is just incompetence.
You're awake.
Yeah, just woke up.
Mr. Sheng will be back soon.
If you have nothing else, leave now.
So, I have to scram as soon as he arrives?
Shen Wen Lang, you're so useless.
Consider this a favor.
Don't rough up Mr. Sheng again.
It took him half a month to heal last time.
I didn't like that.
Next time, don't ask me for help
with your love life.
I don't like that either.
You have to help me.
Maybe I might help you in return.
Let go. I don't need your help.
You don't?
You'll probably die single on your own.
Bullshit.
Wen Lang, I hope
you'll find someone soon, like me.
Fuck off.
I heard you shouldn't
go straight home after discharge.
You need to eat and rest somewhere first,
so you don't bring that sickly energy back.
You're superstitious?
When I was a kid,
my mom told me that after hospital stays.
What about you? Don't believe any of it?
I don't buy superstitions,
but I believe in you.
Yong, you weren't raised in Jiang Hu, right?
I wasn't.
But I used to visit often.
For your sister's medical appointments?
To see you.
Such a sweet talker.
If I ask where you're from,
will you say you're from my heart?
Is that the case?
Yes.
Come in.
Mr. Shen.
Wen Lang, is Yong with you?
Why isn't he answering my phone?
He isn't. No idea.
You're both in Jiang Hu.
How can you not know?
So what if we're both here?
You're his cousin,
yet you can't get through to him either.
Fair point.
What's the matter?
Just finished an emergency joint meeting.
We designed response plans
for Sheng Fang Biotech's actions against us.
Got it.
Well...
Mr. Shen.
[Shen Yu]
Shen Wen Lang, I know your company
in Jiang Hu is in trouble.
I know how hard Brother Yi worked to raise you.
So, apologize and come home now.
If you do, I might spare your legs
and help you through this.
Whether Dad had it easy or not, he's dead.
You should know best how he died, Shen Yu.
Just give up.
That place stopped being my home
the day I walked out.
What did you say just now?
The car you asked for is ready.
It's waiting in the parking garage.
Where are you heading?
Do you need any preparations?
I'm heading out for lunch.
Is this a last-minute business lunch?
Who else is joining?
I can prepare in advance.
You don't need to prepare anything.
Just come with me.
Oh.
I prepared a gift for you.
Thank you for being so nice to me.
A watch?
It's just the basic model.
I can't afford anything too luxurious yet.
Basic models are great, versatile.
Does it look good?
Mr. Shen, isn't this a business lunch?
No.
Well...
What's today's date?
May 19.
You forgot your own birthday?
Let's go. I'll take you out for a meal.
I ordered a birthday cake.
You're like a bad penny.
And you reek of Drunk Branch.
People might think
a toilet scrubber came to life.
HS Group used my pheromone scent
to develop products without permission.
Shen Wen Lang, you hate Omegas,
but you keep clashing with me over Hua Yong.
You follow me everywhere.
Do you have a crush on me?
Paranoia needs early treatment.
Save your confession.
There's a limit to being crazy.
Sheng Shao You, I heard you never date Omegas
who've been with Alphas.
Hua Yong is useless to you, then.
Why not give him to me?
Shen Wen Lang!
Several X Holdings executives
are interested in him.
If you hand him over,
I might share the targeted drug technology
with Sheng Fang.
Gao Tu, you leave first.
Don't let toilet fumes trigger your asthma.
Mr. Sheng, forget it.
Let's go.
Just you wait.
I'll wait for you to decide
if you'll trade Hua Yong for the tech.
You're better off waiting for your death.
So, what's between you and Mr. Sheng?
Sheng Shao You is insane.
He picks fights for no reason.
What about Secretary Hua?
Birds of a feather flock together.
He's just good-looking.
What about you?
What about me?
If you hadn't done nothing,
why would Mr. Sheng retaliate so violently?
How should I know?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Gao Tu.
You don't think
I'd do something to Hua Yong, do you?
I don't know.
What do you mean by that?
It means I don't know.
Gao Tu, whose side are you on, mine or Sheng's?
I get paid by the company,
so I view things
from the company's perspective.
That's not what I asked.
If you ignored your paycheck,
whose side are you on?
The moral side.
Oh.
Sheng Shao You abuses power
and picks fights in public.
He's definitely immoral.
And you?
You made Secretary Hua act like an escort.
Is that moral?
Do you know who you're talking to?
Sorry, Mr. Shen.
I spoke out of turn.
It's 1 P.M.
Shouldn't you return to the office?
Do you think I want to stay in this dump?
If it weren't your special day...
Do you think I'd want to?
Yeah.
Yes, my small and shabby place
isn't fit for you.
You should leave.
First Hua Yong,
now Sheng Shao You.
Why do you always argue with me
over those baffling people?
Do you like them?
Now I get why a Beta like you
is so sensitive to Sheng Shao You's pheromones.
You like him, don't you?
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
You're burning up.
Do you have antipyretics?
No.
I'm fine.
How can you be fine?
You forgot your birthday
and didn't even say a word about your fever.
Even kids know to see a doctor
when they're sick.
How old are you, really?
I'll buy medicine.
You don't have to, really.
Shen Wen Lang.
Can you stay with me a little longer?
Okay.
Happy birthday.
What did you promise me?
Be reasonable!
Sheng Shao You attacked first.
I was defending myself.
If you fight Mr. Sheng again,
I won't help you.
Seriously, who's helping who here?
Feeling better?
Yeah, the medicine helped.
Oh right.
Bo Qiao just signed his first order.
He called to invite everyone
for dinner this weekend.
Will you come with me?
Okay.
Mr. Sheng, I'm dressed. Let's go.
I told you to dress casually.
I did.
Casually.
Get it?
Who told you to look this handsome?
Fine, since you look so good today,
I'll tell you a secret.
What is it?
Don't show up this handsome
at gatherings again.
I'll get jealous.
Then I'll just go out without washing my face.
What about you?
You're always attracting others.
I get jealous, too.
Jealous? What are you going to do about that?
I'll do this.
Come on, drinks on me tonight.
Come on.
Here comes Shao You...
And Yong.
Should he be "Mrs. Sheng" now?
Shove off, he's shy.
Don't talk nonsense.
Congrats on the deal.
Thanks, Yong.
Yu Shan is over there. Let's sit there.
[Chen Pin Ming]
I need to take a call.
- Wait here.
- Okay.
Yu Shan, Bo Qiao.
Go ahead.
We'll look after Yong.
Didn't know you can hold your liquor.
Are you bored without Shao You?
Come on.
Let me keep you company.
I'm not bored.
Yong, heard you went missing for a while.
Shao you really freaked out when you were gone.
Was Mr. Sheng really that anxious?
Anxious?
He nearly turned Jiang Hu upside down.
Honestly I've never seen Shao You like this.
Not for any Omega.
Mr. Sheng, intel shows board members
are plotting a chairman re-election
to remove you from power.
Why?
Recently, we've snatched all HS bids,
shorted their stocks,
and spent heavily on targeted drugs.
Shareholders say this has caused
irreversible impact on Sheng Fang.
Our cash flow is healthy.
The HS projects we won are all model cases.
I don't think there is any issue.
As for the targeted drugs...
Exploring innovative drugs
won't hurt Sheng Fang Biotech.
What really causes harm
is resting on past achievements
and refusing to move forward.
- Chen Pin Ming.
- Yes.
First thing tomorrow,
organize reports on our recent winning bids
and bring them to my office.
I'll handle the board.
Yong, Shao You isn't the only Alpha around.
Why don't you add me on WeChat?
If you ever break up with him,
you can come find me.
Break up?
Yeah.
If that day ever comes, I'll be right here.
Whatever Shao You can give you, I can too.
You can't.
You haven't even told me what you want.
How do you know I can't?
Because I'm not breaking up with Mr. Sheng.
So sure of that?
Yeah, I only like Mr. Sheng.
But feelings change.
You haven't known him that long.
Life is long, Yong.
Today you love him,
tomorrow you might love me.
Or maybe not tomorrow.
Maybe in three, five, ten years.
Yong.
Someone like you must have a lot of admirers.
It's only a matter of time
before your heart shifts.
You don't have to answer me now.
If you ever change your mind,
think of me first.
I won't change my mind.
Didn't expect you to be quite the romantic.
Fine, let's say you won't waver.
But what about Shao You?
You haven't been with him that long.
From what I know of him,
he doesn't believe in forever.
You two haven't even hit a year, right?
But this is already
the longest relationship he's ever had.
Mr. Sheng, here are the proposals
for the 17 projects we secured this quarter.
Please take a look.
Sales performance has been solid
and the fixed asset turnover has improved.
Since the door's closed,
no need for pleasantries.
The board's stance was clear
in this morning's meeting.
We've had it easy for too long.
The moment there's even a hint of risk,
they all want answers from me.
The last mile is always the hardest.
Drug development is full of uncertainty.
Most people collapse just before dawn.
Mr. Sheng.
But my father always said something very true.
Life is just a big amusement park.
The brave get to enjoy the ride first.
The drug project isn't without hope.
Since we got the list
of HS's senior technical staff,
the recruitment team
has already met several of them.
We should see new progress soon.
Also, regarding your request
to track X Holdings' Chang Yu,
I received word that he'll
be in Jiang Hu tonight for a private event.
What kind of event?
The Minister of Commerce
from Country P is visiting Jiang Hu.
Tonight's a private dinner hosted by him.
Heard that ugly guy from X Holdings
is pretty tight with that minister, right?
Yes, there are rumors about that.
Rumor has it X Holdings
sponsored the whole event,
from venue to security.
All handled by X Holdings.
They've been very active in Jiang Hu lately.
After they excluded us
from the last industry summit,
people have been talking.
There are rumors that they look down on us
and think we lack
true research and development capabilities.
Ridiculous. Of all the companies they invited,
none can match our R&D strength.
Send me the time and location of the event.
There are rumors in the second-gen circles
that ugly freak from X Holdings
has been hiding out in Jiang Hu.
I'll try my luck.
Okay.
The event requires every Alpha
to bring an Omega companion.
Should I find someone for you
or invite Mr. Hua?
Events like this are always full of riffraff.
Isn't Shen Wen Liang enough for you?
Apologies, sir.
How about Miss Shu?
It's just a party.
Anyone's fine as long as it's not Hua Yong.
A pleasure working with you both.
I truly enjoyed our talk today.
I hope we can start working together soon.
Sounds good.
Long time no see, Secretary Chang.
Long time no see.
Sheng, you're surprisingly approachable today.
No need to clear the room with your pheromones?
You flatter me.
And this is?
Shu Xin.
Hello, Secretary Chang. I'm Shu Xin.
I'm Mr. Sheng's girlfriend.
Miss Shu is very beautiful.
Mr. Sheng, you have great taste.
See you around.
Secretary Chang.
Minister Wang, I heard you were coming.
So, Jiang Hu's elite showed up in full force.
Quite the turnout.
Not at all.
All honors are but reflections
of your esteemed influence.
It's nothing.
And who might this be?
Minister Wang, let me introduce him.
This is the president of Sheng Fang Biotech,
Mr. Sheng Shao You.
And this is Minister Wang
from Country P's Ministry of Commerce,
one of the key figures
behind Country P's economic rise.
Minister Wang, pleasure.
I've heard a lot about you.
The pleasure's mine.
I've heard Mr. Sheng
is a bold and forthright man
Tonight, I see it for myself.
Cheers.
- You hold your liquor well.
- He can drink a lot.
Minister Wang, I'm Shu Xin.
I've heard so much about you.
It's an honor to meet you.
You're truly graceful and elegant.
Minister Wang, Mr. Sheng
is one of Jiang Hu's rising stars.
A young and talented entrepreneur.
And Minister Wang's been a driving force
behind Country P's boom.
Without him, it wouldn't be where it is today.
So, I hope the two of you
will have many chances to work together.
And that Sheng Fang Biotech
can rely on Minister Wang's support
as it expands into Country P.
To our future cooperation.
What do you say, Mr. Sheng?
Bottoms up.
Shao You, do you have a headache?
Let me give you a massage.
That Secretary Chang was too much.
He kept making you drink
and wouldn't even let me help.
What are you doing?
Shao You, you're drunk.
I don't feel safe letting you go home alone.
My place is nearby.
Why not stay the night there?
I can take care of you.
Get off me.
Stay away.
Chen Pin Ming.
- Yes?
- Take Miss Shu home
Okay.
Miss Shu, please show some respect.
Sheng already has an Omega he cares about.
Please sit properly and take your hand off him.
Mr. Sheng, we've arrived.
Okay.
Another night wasted.
All that, just to meet Chang Yu again.
Is that rat from X Holdings
afraid to show his hideous face?
Always hiding in the dark.
Like totally a monster.
He'll get what's coming for him.
Mr. Sheng.
Did he drink too much?
Yes, he's been going to
a lot of dinners lately.
Sorry to trouble you with looking after him.
No trouble at all.
Mr. Sheng.
You stink.
I stink?
I don't like smelling someone else on you.
I hate it.
So, I'll wash it off.
Mr. Sheng.
You were so drunk last night.
I made you hangover soup,
but you wouldn't even drink it.
I must've kept you up late again.
Next time I'm drinking like that,
just leave me alone.
I don't want to tire you out.
Okay.
Come in.
Mr. Sheng, Secretary Chang just messaged.
The gentleman from X Holdings
is inviting you to his private banquet.
Seems like last night's drinking
wasn't for nothing.
Also, this month's monthly meeting
is set for 2 P.M. in the main conference room.
You don't look too well, sir.
Have you been pushing yourself too hard
with all these social engagements lately?
Might be good to get some rest before then.
The bio pharmaceutical industry
is entering the next decade
of digital transformation.
The Metaverse is reshaping how companies
interact and coexist with their customers.
We surveyed 100 senior executives in the field.
85% said the Metaverse
has had a positive impact on their lives.
It is significantly higher
than the average across other industries.
Mr. Sheng!
Chen Pin Ming, get my inhibitor patch now.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Sheng, let me take you to the lounge.
Mr. Sheng.
Someone call a ride
and get him to the hospital now!