credit
♫ ♫
[Desire: The Series]
[Episode 4]
Such a strong Omega scent.
I can smell it even through the door.
Mr. Sheng.
Did you let an Omega mark you?
My matters are none of your concern.
You're is right.
I'll go back to my room.
Good night.
Why are your hands so cold?
Hua Yong.
You've been waiting for me, haven't you?
9:30 A.M.: Buy coffee for Mr. Shen.
11:30 A.M.: Remind Mr. Shen to eat.
1:30 P.M.: Remind Mr. Shen to rest.
3:30 P.M.: Remind Mr. Shen
of the department meeting.
Shen Wen Lang isn't brainless.
Why does he need someone to remind him to eat?
That's insane.
That little brat.
He even cares
whether Shen Wen Lang rests in the company,
but he comes home
and gives me the silent treatment.
Not even a word to me.
Fine, if he's ignoring me,
why do I even bother coming back here?
Mr. Sheng, thank you
for your hospitality these days.
I've thought about it.
I realize that's really inconsiderate
to bother you by staying there.
Recently, I found another place to stay at.
I will move out tonight.
Dinner is in the fridge.
Don't forget to eat.
Also, I'll repay the money you lent me on time.
Unless necessary,
let's never see each other again.
What does he mean by that?
Where are you going?
Mr. Sheng.
You're back just in time.
I wanted to thank you in person for everything.
Thank you for all your kindness.
Goodbye.
You think you can come and go as you please?
What do you take this place for?
A shelter?
Sorry.
So, what do you want?
What do I want?
Do I get to have what I want?
No, I…
If this is about meeting again, forget it.
Why?
Tired of our little game of kissing but no sex?
Or...
Did you find an Alpha
willing to permanently mark you?
No.
I just can't do this anymore.
Why?
Because I really like you.
Every time I think of you with other Omegas,
jealousy twists me into someone awful.
Into someone I don't recognize.
I hate who I become.
So, let's end up this relationship.
Let's never meet again.
Mr. Sheng.
I wish you happiness.
You can't leave in the middle of this.
I've said everything I needed to.
But I haven't agreed.
Hua Yong.
Don't go.
Let's sit down and talk.
Okay?
Say it here.
After that, I'll leave.
It's not that simple.
Stop fooling around.
Put your luggage back in the room.
Listen to me.
Thank you.
Yong.
Let's make up.
No more fighting, okay?
Okay.
We won't quarrel anymore, right?
Fine.
Mr. Shen, you have a business dinner tonight.
Tomorrow, you're scheduled to
meet with Mr. Chu from Yuan Nan Group.
As of now, you have
no engagements the day after.
I'll email the materials
for Monday's weekly meeting to you shortly.
Okay.
Where is Gao Tu?
Secretary Gao took ten days of leave.
But don't worry,
he completed the handover in advance.
Your personal affairs
are now being handled by me.
On leave again?
And the reason?
Well...
Seems like it's because of some family matters.
What family matters?
Probably off taking care of that Omega
who gets into a heat every other day.
Whatever.
Since he loves playing
the model partner at home so much,
he might as well not come back.
Reassign his responsibilities to someone else.
Understood.
What are you standing around for?
Return the airplane.
Excuse me, Shen.
Could I bother you for just one minute?
Gao Tu.
Excuse me, please make way.
Shen, I only need a minute.
I'm not asking for anything.
I just want to push myself, is that okay?
Apologies.
You should go push someone else's boundaries.
Shen is very busy.
So annoying.
Even if it's a rejection,
I want to hear it from Shen himself.
Who the hell are you?
His watchdog?
- No, I'm not.
- Not what?
You're just a Beta who sticks around
an S-Class Alpha all day.
All you do is fend off his admirers.
Who knows what you're really plotting?
I doubt your intentions are pure.
I bet you want to monopolize Shen's attention.
Pathetic, shameless.
Gao Tu.
Why waste so much time on an Omega?
Hurry up, let's go. You're making me sick.
I hate Omegas the most.
Next week, when you come back to work,
make sure you've cleaned yourself up properly.
Don't you have any idea
how strong that Omega scent on you is?
Don't you dare come near me
with that filthy scent.
Disgusting.
Hello.
Dad.
Gao Tu! What took you so long
to answer the phone?
You know, I...
I've come across a great
business opportunity lately.
Big returns, very promising.
But…
I'm just missing a tiny bit of start-up money.
How much do you need?
Not much, 10,000 would be enough.
10,000?
You're gambling again, aren't you?
Huh? Since when was 100,000 a big deal?
You work at such a big fancy company now.
You must be making a ton.
And you can't even spare a bit
for your own father?
After all I've done for you,
this is how you repay me? You ungrateful brat!
Dad I'm just a regular employee.
What does the company's size
have to do with my paycheck?
And besides, Qing's still in the hospital.
Well, well, well.
Oh, please. Qing's been sick
since she was born.
Just a burden on all of us.
Treatment after treatment,
but still no progress.
If you ask me it's just a waste of money.
Better to give up now than drag this on.
How can you say that?
Qing is your daughter.
Fine, fine, treat her if you want, whatever.
But what about the money I asked for?
When can you transfer it?
I don't have that much.
- At most, I can give you 2,000.
- What?
2,000?
What the hell can I do with that?
You make all this money
and can't give your old man a cent?
People would call you a heartless bastard.
I swear, if you don't give me the money,
I'll show up at your company and make a scene.
Go ahead.
Whatever.
But once you've caused a scene
and I lose my job,
you won't even get the 2,000.
You…
Secretary Gao,If possible,
you'd better come back early.
Mr. Shen's been furious
about your recent absences.
He even dropped the ultimatum.
He said you might as well not come back.
Explain to him when you return
or he might target you.
He doesn't need me at all.
I'm the one who keeps
watching him from afar, unwilling to let go.
He's like the moon,
brilliant, surrounded by countless stars.
And me, I'm just one of those ordinary stars.
Sir, this is our latest bestseller,
the ABO Desire series
which includes a shower gel,
body lotion, and shampoo.
They all smell amazing.
This one's sage-scented and that one's iris.
We also have orchid and rose
which are also popular.
And sir, since you're a Beta,
you don't have a natural pheromone scent.
You can pick whatever suits your preference.
All are long-lasting fragrances.
If you buy the whole set you'll also
get a bonus pheromone suppressant patch.
Yes, and if you're not ready to buy just yet,
you can find and follow our account online
by searching "Desire ABO Universe".
Our account is "Desire ABO Universe".
We do live streams weekly.
All products in the convenience store
will be offered at their biggest discounts
during our live stream sales.
Check out, please.
I'll take everything in the cart.
I'm just going to pick up a few other things.
Hey.
Are you a quadruplet?
Huh?
Oh.
Um...
Library assistant in the morning,
KFC server at noon,
fruit market loader in the afternoon,
and convenience store cashier at night.
Hey.
We're from the same school, right?
What's your summer homework?
A field survey of the service industry?
That'll be 24 yuan.
So, is working all these jobs your hobby?
No, I…
This skincare line sounds interesting.
Tell me about it.
This one just hit the shelves.
It's on promotion right now.
Buy one set,
get a free pheromone suppressant patch.
Would you like one?
I'll take this.
Check out these, too.
School starts in a few days.
Are you done with your summer homework?
How much can you make from part-time jobs?
Studying should be your priority.
Wen Lang, don't be like that.
He's from a low-income background.
Tuition at our private school is steep.
He relies on part-time jobs
and your family foundation's scholarship.
Gao Tu, I'm sorry.
Wen Lang didn't mean it.
It's… okay.
Shen Wen Lang!
You forgot a drink.
And your free suppressant patch, too.
Keep it.
Why?
A return gift.
The breakfasts on my desk every morning
were bought by you, right?
Wait, seriously?
Gao Tu, why would you
buy breakfast for Wen Lang?
He doesn't even eat breakfast.
Especially that kind of stuff
loaded with additives.
He'd never touch it.
Stop buying things for others.
Spend it on your own lunch.
You eat less than a kitten.
Stop buying that junk for me.
Eat more meat, would you?
You're so skinny. It's not a good look.
I should've given up a long time ago.
This dream was never going to come true.
But...
giving up is so hard.
I can't let go, I can't.
So, i can only inject suppressants like crazy
just to keep pretending I'm a Beta
and just to preserve this fake friendship.
But...
it's a friendship built on lies.
Ten years.
Ten years is the limit.
Shen Wen Lang.
I'm sorry.
I'm in love with you.
From Q1 until now,
we've invested nearly four billion.
Yet, there's still no clear result.
The pressure from the board is increasing.
Several major shareholders with voting power
now believe that
Sheng Fang Biotech going all-in
on the development of a targeted drug
for pheromone gland carcinoma
is just your abuse of power
for personal reasons.
What did PR say?
Things aren't positive.
Negative press
is dragging down our stock price.
To make things worse,
HS Group is leaking information
that they've just been granted special approval
and that their targeted drug
may complete Phase III trials
and enter the market within two years.
Though, that might just be a move
to inflate their stock value.
It could all be fabricated positive news
Mr. Sheng, you don't have to worry too much.
How can I not worry?
We've burned through billions
with nothing to show for it.
And to give the lab more autonomy,
I pushed for the technical center restructuring
which cut into the board's turf.
If things keep going like this,
opposition from within will only grow bigger.
Sheng Fang will end up isolated on all sides.
The lead scientists have made a formal pledge.
Everyone's working overtime to speed things up.
We've also been actively recruiting
top experts in the field.
Good
Mr. Sheng, there's something else.
What is it?
We've confirmed that
a high-level rep from X Holdings
will be visiting soon.
They're likely looking for a new partner.
Are you sure?
Yes.
They've already sent invitations
to the top biopharma companies in this region.
And I heard that person will be in town
to personally meet with whoever's chosen.
That's great.
If we can connect with X Holdings
and get access to their patent tech,
we won't be stuck in this corner anymore.
I don't believe Sheng Fang
can't land what HS did.
The one thing is...
What is it?
Sheng Fang isn't on the invite list.
- Why not?
- PR is still trying to figure out why.
It's odd some companies that got invited
are nowhere near our level.
Find out why and report back to me.
Yes, Mr. Sheng.
Chen Pin Ming.
Who's leading
the X Holdings delegation this time?
It's Chang Yu.
Okay.
Got it.
- You can go.
- Okay.
- Mr. Sheng.
- Yes?
Your rut period is coming up, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- You look tired.
Take care of yourself.
Your health matters more than anything.
Thanks. I'll keep that in mind.
Why were we the only ones left off that list?
I even spoke to Chang Yu
at Zhang's dinner party last time.
We didn't have any conflict.
Why would they shut us out?
Mr. Sheng, I'm the technical director
of Huanyu Biotech.
Hello.
Hey, why aren't you going to say hi
to Mr. Sheng from Sheng Fang Biotech?
Look closely, check out the back of his neck.
Is that a suppressant patch?
Yeah, looks like he's entering his rut.
He is an S-class Alpha.
I'm just a B-class.
Better stay away during his rut period.
One wrong move under
that kind of pheromone pressure,
and it's game over.
Mr. Sheng.
- Has Chang Yu arrived?
- He has.
But he didn't come through the main entrance.
He went straight into the V.I.P lounge
through the side door.
There are guards posted outside.
A few people who know him
tried to say hi and all got turned away.
Better not force it.
Yes.
We'll try to offer him a drink privately later.
Got it.
Mr. Sheng, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Just...
This rut feels different somehow.
It's harder to control.
You're sweating a lot.
The suppressant patch is soaked through.
I brought a spare.
Would you like to step into the restroom
to apply a new patch?
Got it.
[ABO Toilet]
Sorry, Secretary Chang.
Mr. Sheng is inside?
Wow, what a grand setup.
Even going to the restroom
requires clearing out the space?
I've really seen
the arrogance of Sheng Fang Biotech now.
Mr. Sheng, you don't look well.
Orchid... Smells so nice...
Mr. Sheng, are you feeling okay?
Come lie down for a bit
I feel awful.
I know.
Let me help you to the bed.
Okay.
Thank you, Secretary Chen.
I'll take care of Mr. Sheng from here.
You can go.
I'll take good care of him.
I feel horrible.
Mr. Sheng, let go.
How am I supposed to help you change like this?
No.
I won't change my clothes.
I want to sleep like this with you.
You can't sleep in these clothes.
You might feel uncomfortable.
I'm not tired.
Yong, I feel so awful.
This feels like hell.
Don't you care at all?
Of course I care.
Lie down first, Mr. Sheng.
Do you like the way
my soothing pheromones smell?
I hope you sleep well tonight, Mr. Sheng.
Good night.
Mr. Sheng there are rumors
that HS Group suddenly formed
an anti-corruption task force
targeting the core
of the pheromone-targeted drug research team.
Mass probes has sparked public anxiety.
Should we take advantage of this situation?
Since ancient times,
trouble always starts from within.
If Shen Wen Lang is stirring this up now,
he's digging his own grave.
Have HR set up a dedicated headhunting team.
While their internal morale is shaky,
we should poach as many key people as we can.
Got it.
But...
HS's confidentiality measures are airtight.
We've only identified that
the investigation targets
are mostly in the research group.
The list?
Still working on it.
But it's difficult.
Chen Pin Ming.
Yes?
I'm not asking if it's difficult.
I'm asking for results.
You have full authority of this matter.
I want the names of their core personnel
within a month.
Do whatever it takes.
Understood, Mr. Sheng.
- Hello?
- Shao You.
Shao You, your rutting period is coming, right?
Why don't we go on vacation again this time?
Haven't I told you that
we shouldn't contact each other anymore?
Shao You, I know you hate it
when I go out a lot.
But I've changed.
That's none of my business.
Don't be like that
I know you're with that orchid-scented Omega.
Bo Qiao told me.
Platonic love is romantic.
But Shao You, as an S-class Alpha,
you don't have to endure your rut alone.
How I spend my rut is no one else's concern.
It was just a fling between us.
If you want me to pay for more bags,
just call my secretary.
Don't call me again unless necessary.
What is it now?
Shao You, it's Bo Qiao.
Why so pissy?
Who pissed you off?
Keep my private life to yourself,
and I might calm down.
No way.
You know me,
can't keep a secret to save my life.
Oh, your rut's coming
I'm heading to Country P for a few days.
Wanna join?
Country P's entertainment scene is lit.
Tons of hot Omegas.
Count me out.
Why not?
Come on, it'll be fun.
Yu Shan's going, too.
Bo Qiao, stop pressuring him.
You know Shao You.
He never goes to Country P unless he has to.
Do it for my sake.
Join us.
No.
See?
Told you that he'd say no.
I know he hates Country P,
but I'm trying to help him get over it.
It's all because he lost
his family pocket watch there as a kid.
He's held a grudge ever since.
Once he carries a grudge, his heart
is smaller than a pore on your face.
Hua Yong, what are you doing here?
Why make that face?
Shut up!
Who said that?
You're interrupting my nap.
How dare you ask who I am?
Sh-Sheng Shao You?
An Alpha is bullying an Omega?
Come here.
Close your eyes.
Just a paper tiger. It's been scared off by me.
Don't be afraid,
I'll release some calming pheromones.
You'll feel better.
Just relax.
You'll feel better soon.
No pheromone scent.
You're not an Omega, you're a Beta.
- Huh?
- I've never met such a cute Beta.
Guess calming pheromones
don't work on you, then.
No, I'm not a Beta.
I just haven't presented yet.
I guess that's why I can't smell your scent.
But I'm about to present.
What scent do you like?
I should go.
Sheng Shao You.
What?
I need to grab something. Be right back.
Oh.
Can I have your contact info?
To thank me?
Don't bother.
If you meet bullies again,
don't just stand there.
If you can't fight, run.
At least protect yourself.
I'll get going. Bye.
Secretary Chen, would you like tea or coffee?
Either is fine. Whatever's convenient for you.
Sorry for dropping by without letting you know.
No worries.
I'll make you some Kumquat tea.
Sounds good.
Thank you.
Mr. Sheng is away on a business trip.
He was worried you'd get bored alone,
so he asked me to bring you a book.
What book?
Oh, this one.
I mentioned it to Mr. Sheng a while ago.
I loved it since I was a kid.
And I'd always wanted
to read it a few more times.
I've been working with Mr. Sheng
for a long time.
It's clear he cares a lot about you.
He is very kind.
Secretary Chen.
Yeah?
Did Mr. Sheng go on a business trip
because of his rut?
That's part of his private schedule.
I'm not really sure.
Private schedule.
I understand.
Oh, I also baked some cookies.
Would you like to try some?
Of course. Thank you.
Don't be shy. I made two flavors.
Try both.
Secretary Chen.
You seem to really like
our company-issued briefcase.
If you want one, I can give you one.
Oh, is this yours?
I thought it was Mr. Sheng's.
I was going to restock his business cards.
Last time at a business banquet,
his cardholder was empty and he was furious.
Mr. Sheng does have
a bit of a temper sometimes.
Thank you for taking care of him.
Not at all, it's my job.
Go on, try the cookies.
Freshly baked.
I just remembered.
Mr. Sheng asked me
to stop by the lab again today.
I should get going.
Of course. Work comes first.
I'll pack the cookies up for you.
Thank you.
Come in.
Mr. Shen, here's your white tea.
What's going on with you?
You look awful
I'm fine.
Don't give me that.
Have you even looked in a mirror?
You call that fine?
Sorry, I haven't been sleeping well lately.
I'm feeling a bit dizzy.
Dizzy?
Gao Tu.
You're not a kid.
If you're unwell, go see a doctor.
Don't you know how to do that?
Gao Tu.
What the hell are you doing?
I've seen one.
It's asthma.
Got some injections, too.
I'm better now.
Fine.
Mr. Shen.
Here's next month's procurement budget summary.
- Gao Tu.
- Yes?
This is the report you prepared?
You added an extra zero in the total column.
Gao Tu.
Are you blind?
Sorry, I didn't check it properly.
Checking it?
I think your brain's off somewhere else.
Let me guess, off fantasizing
about that Omega who's constantly in heat.
How could you even get the numbers wrong?
Even a primary schooler
wouldn't make a mistake like this.
Mr. Shen, the report was drafted jointly
by the finance and procurement teams.
I was only in charge of delivering it.
I wasn't around earlier this week,
so I couldn't review it myself.
HS Group doesn't keep freeloaders.
And I don't have time for your excuses.
Understood. I'll correct it immediately.
Also...
You know how much I hate Omegas.
Yes, I know.
How dare you walk into my office
reeking of some Omega's stench!
I...
Disgusting! Get out!
Don't come back
until you've scrubbed yourself clean.
I'm sorry, Mr. Shen.
I'll leave now.
No doubt he just came off someone's heat.
Makes me want to kill someone.
And that Secretary Chen was so clumsy.
He made such a fuss planting a bug.
Why are all the people around me so useless?
Whatever, the timing is perfect.
Proceed with the plan.
Lunatic.