[Episode 8]
Mr. Sheng.
How do you feel?
I'm fine.
Was anyone else hurt?
Just one colleague twisted their ankle
on the way out.
They've already been approved
for medical leave.
No other serious issues.
Okay.
Good to hear.
Dr. Wang, what's wrong with Mr. Sheng?
The blood test results are back.
Our preliminary diagnosis
is pheromone dysregulation syndrome.
What?
His free-type pheromone level, type T,
is more than five times the normal range.
That's extremely abnormal for an Alpha.
Even Omegas only reach that level during heat.
Is it serious?
How do we treat it?
To be honest, given Mr. Sheng's age
and S-class Alpha status,
he shouldn't be developing this.
But considering his high stress,
long working hours, and irregular routines,
we have to take the possibility seriously.
For now, I'll prescribe oral medication
to prevent extreme overflow
that could harm others.
Let's wait until he's hospitalized
and conduct a comprehensive inspection.
Hospitalized?
Can't I just take the meds?
Mr. Sheng, I know you're busy,
but your body belongs to you.
Pheromone dysregulation
is a serious endocrine disorder.
We still don't fully understand the cause.
And it's already mid-stage
on your first checkup.
Please take this seriously.
But I don't have the time to be hospitalized.
It's your body and your time.
But as your doctor, this is my honest advice.
At this point,
I don't think you're fit for discharge.
Thank you, Doctor.
- Mr. Sheng.
- Let's go.
You should stay in the hospital and rest.
Fine.
Then I want daily summaries of meetings
and project updates delivered to me.
Don't worry, I'll have everything organized,
and report to you every day.
Okay.
And don't tell anyone that I'm hospitalized.
Yes, sir.
Good.
Come in.
Mr. Sheng.
These are flowers from Mr. Hua.
He's orchid-scented, but he sent me sunflowers.
Sunflowers symbolize sunshine and health.
Mr. Sheng, Mr. Hua said he'd like to visit you.
An Omega shouldn't be coming here.
Tell him to stay home and rest.
Okay, got it.
Put these flowers in a vase.
Okay.
What's up?
Heard Sheng Shao You is sick.
Who told you that?
That's none of your business.
Hua Yong, there's a limit to being crazy.
Using luring pheromones
to make an S-class Alpha go into heat?
Only you'd think of that.
What, Mr. Hardcore Bachelor gonna teach me
how to pursue my Alpha?
I'm not here to teach you.
Just heard Sheng Shao You's is hospitalized
with pheromone disorder.
Just wanted to let you know.
Do not add another case study
to the medical textbooks.
No one would expect
an S-class Alpha to go into heat.
What are you doing?
Making soup.
You can cook?
Planning to poison someone?
Shut up.
You're not going to send soup
to Sheng, are you?
So domestic.
Shen Wen Lang, you should worry about yourself.
Oh, when are you paying back
the money you borrowed for your start-up?
Oops, I'm busy.
Talk later, okay?
Wishing you and your heat-prone S-class Alpha
a lifetime of happiness together.
Hope you have a child soon.
May you always be of one heart and mind,
and grow old together lovingly.
Why are you here?
I told you to stay home.
I haven't seen you in so long.
Don't you want to see me?
We video chat every day.
I have pheromone disorder.
What if my dominant pheromones hurt you?
I made fish soup for you.
Would you like to try some?
Okay.
You shouldn't have come.
What if I hurt you?
I won't get hurt.
That's nonsense.
An orchid-scented Omega like you?
I could break ten of you with one hand.
Isn't one enough?
When plucking flowers, the more the better.
Fine.
I understand.
What do you understand?
Mr. Sheng, I just reviewed
your latest blood test report.
All indicators have improved significantly.
After one more week of observation,
you can be discharged if there's no recurrence.
Thanks, Dr. Wang.
You're welcome.
Seems like you're my lucky star.
What?
I feel much better after seeing you.
I'm not as tired, and my headaches are gone.
The doctor says I can be discharged next week.
Aren't you my lucky star?
Getting discharged on a rest day is perfect.
Take a day to rest at home.
There will be live-streamed biopharma
innovation forum on Monday, 10 A.M.
At 2 P.M., you have afternoon tea
with X Holdings' executive.
Don't worry, I'll remind you again.
Good.
Thanks, Secretary Chen. Have a good weekend.
You, too.
Mr. Sheng, how do you feel?
Any discomfort?
I'm a little tired,
but I didn't leak dominant pheromones
during the public speech.
Would've made the news otherwise.
I'll change your inhibitor patch.
Okay.
Mr. Sheng, done with work?
Yes, I just finished.
What are you doing?
I'm watching TV.
What's on?
Watching you in the forum.
You looked so handsome.
Where are you going next?
To see someone I hate.
Huh?
Anyone hated by you is so unlucky.
Why say that?
You're so great, everyone wants your favor.
So, being hated by you must suck.
My mung bean soup is boiling over.
Gotta go. You can have some when you're back.
Bye.
Leave.
Can't be late
for my first afternoon tea with Mr. Sheng.
Yes, sir.
Such a fuss,
with inspectors as patrol officers.
Is the guy from X Holdings
some overlord from Country P?
Mr. Sheng.
Hope you've been well.
Thanks to your master's hospitality,
it's my first afternoon tea here
with inspectors standing guard
and commissioners directing traffic.
Even a small country president's private visit
wouldn't have this much fanfare.
You flatter us.
We owe it all to your city's kindness.
This way, please.
Have you thought about how this will end?
I have.
I love him.
I could play an Omega beside him forever.
What if he wants to permanently mark you?
I'll remove my gland,
say it was injured and I became a Beta.
Remove it? Don't say that so easily.
You think it's tonsillectomy?
Accidental pheromone gland injury
has a zero-percent survival rate.
My body functions better than S-class Alphas.
I might survive.
You might survive?
You're completely insane.
All this trouble for love.
How touching.
It's nothing.
This way, Mr. Sheng.
Please have a seat, Mr. Sheng.
These are the key heads
of X Holdings' pharmaceutical division.
Our boss said you'd
share common ground with them.
I'll leave you to it.
Excuse me for a moment.
Secretary Chen, since there's no seat for you,
please stand for a while.
Sir, Mr. Sheng from Sheng Fang Biotech is here.
Chang Yu, bring a chair for Mr. Sheng's team.
Secretary Chen, please sit.
Pin Ming, sit when told.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Sheng, why not take this opportunity
to introduce your company?
Didn't know I came for a job interview.
What are you saying, Mr. Sheng?
X Holdings had an industry exchange conference.
Sheng Fang's absence was a real pity.
We've invited you today
to build basic mutual understanding.
X Holdings is a global industry leader.
It's our honor that you wish
to learn about Sheng Fang.
Pin Ming.
Yes.
Hello, everyone. I'm Chen Pin Ming.
I'm head of Mr. Sheng's secretariat.
Allow me to introduce Sheng Fang Biotech.
Founded over 20 years ago,
we specialize in bio pharmaceutical research,
holding one of the most targeted drug patents
in Jiang Hu and nationwide.
Next, I'll detail our targeted drugs.
Look at your Mr. Sheng,
talking and charming on the surface,
but arrogantly treating everyone with contempt.
Would it kill him to make an introduction?
Wen Lang, can't you stop trashing my Alpha?
Your Alpha? Is he really yours?
Is he really yours to claim?
Chang Yu said at the last banquet
an Omega named Shu Xin
called herself Sheng Shao You's girlfriend.
Do you know about that?
Sheng Fang's patented
active targeted drug delivery
based on blood circulation
and penetration technology
is widely used in the industry.
Orchid scent, it's Hua Yong.
No, this pheromone is too dominant.
It isn't Hua Yong.
It's an S-class Alpha's...
Luring pheromones?
Targeted, too? Are you crazy?
Next, I'll introduce our core technology.
Sheng Fang Biotech has the worldwide patent
for the fourth generation CRISPR.
It is three times more effecient
than regular CRISPR models.
It's MOP rate is lower than 0.1.
Mr. Sheng, what's wrong?
You look pale, Mr. Sheng.
Mr. Sheng.
Secretary Chang, it's a misunderstanding.
Mr. Sheng has been suffering
from pheromone disorder recently.
Shut up! Hands on your head!
Secretary Chang, we meant no offense.
Besides, if there's a misunderstanding,
X Holdings shouldn't be
killing anyone in broad daylight.
Quiet.
Boss.
He fainted.
Yes.
Sir, please trust us.
Mr. Sheng didn't do it on purpose.
- He…
- What if he did?
What if he didn't?
But...
Are the room and doctor ready?
Yes, all arranged.
Pitiful.
An S-class Alpha like you
would never have thought
you'd go into heat like an Omega.
No wonder you released
dominant pheromones unconsciously from panic.
Since you look so handsome today,
let me help you.
I knew you'd do something crazy.
I should've stayed away.
You don't know how much
Sheng Shao You's dominant pheromones hurt me.
No, I don't feel it.
Using targeted luring pheromones in public?
Hua Yong, any S-class Alpha
with an ounce of shame
wouldn't use such advanced abilities openly.
You already said it. "S-class Alphas".
What's that to me?
Hua Yong, have some decency.
Inducing an S-class Alpha
to have their heat in public...
If word gets out, you'll be dissected in a lab.
Don't be naive.
Whether an Omega or an Alpha,
anyone I want becomes mine.
To make that proud S-class Alpha
my exclusive Omega,
I need some tricks
Mr. Sheng is so precious.
He has more admirers than ants.
Without some tricks, I'd never get close.
Precious? Is he a diamond or encrusted?
Wen Lang, envy gets you nowhere.
Learn from me.
Gotta go. Mr. Sheng is waking up.
Mr. Sheng, how do you feel?
Where is this?
This is a suite at X Hotel.
You had pheromone disorder,
released dominant pheromones, then fainted.
X Holdings arranged this room and a doctor.
The doctor wanted to inject an inhibitor,
but I refused to ensure safety.
Got it.
Did you see that person's face?
They had guns.
Before that man appeared,
bodyguards blindfolded me.
Despicable tactics.
Someone's coming.
Don't worry, Secretary Chen.
Earlier, my boss was present,
and Mr. Sheng released
dominant pheromones suddenly.
We had to take precautions.
Secretary Chang, thank your boss
for the room and the doctor.
You're welcome.
I'm here to say my boss won't pursue this.
You can leave anytime.
Mr. Sheng, rest well.
See you soon.
You're back late.
Did everything go well?
What's wrong?
Ran into a lunatic.
Did you eat?
Yes. What about you?
I went straight to the office.
Didn't have time to eat.
I'll make you some noodles.
Or do you want the mung bean soup
I made this afternoon?
Do you want it hot or cold?
Either's fine.
Okay.
I also made double-boiled conch
with cordyceps flowers.
I can use it as broth for the noodles.
Or would you rather have rice?
You know how to make soup?
- Yeah.
- You're good at everything.
I'm not that good.
I dozed off this afternoon
and let the first pot boil dry.
This is a fresh batch.
Go sit on the couch.
I'll heat up the broth and make noodles.
It won't take long.
Want to join me for a bowl?
Okay, I'll have some mung bean soup first.
If you like it, you can ask for more.
Okay.
Tough meeting this afternoon?
Yes.
Offended someone crazy.
I offended him slightly,
and he issued a statement immediately,
saying he won't cooperate
with Sheng Fang Biotech short-term.
Now, everyone in the industry
is asking about it.
The PR team is still working overtime.
How could this happen?
Cowardly bastard.
Better not let me find out what he looks like.
You don't know who he is?
Yeah.
Few have seen him.
No one knows his appearance.
A person's face reflects the heart.
With such a filthy heart,
he can't be good-looking.
Yes, you're right.
So, what now?
Will it have a big impact?
No.
Before the market closed,
someone spread rumors that Sheng Fang
has cash flow issues, even bankruptcy.
It caused stock fluctuations at first,
but PR has publicly denied it.
It's no big deal.
Okay. That's good.
Mr. Sheng, it's me.
What is it?
Secretary Gao from HS called
saying Mr. Shen wants to talk urgently.
I've got nothing to say to a bastard.
I'm busy, don't bother me with this again.
But... Shen Wen Lang said
he wants to talk to you
about the targeted drug patent.
That's all they have of value.
There's nothing to discuss.
I don't believe
X Holdings can develop drugs
that Sheng Fang can't.
But Secretary Gao said
if you agree to Mr. Shen's terms,
HS is willing to do an equity swap
and merge the companies.
And in the future...
Mr. Sheng.
It's a boring proposal.
Ignore them.
The terms are very favorable.
Please reconsider it seriously.
Hello, Yu Shan.
Hey, Shao You.
It's been a long time.
You haven't been hanging out with us.
You know I've been busy,
I have no time.
Saw the news last night.
Who would spread such rumors?
So pointless.
Let me know if you need help
I got you, bro.
Thanks, Yu Shan.
It's under control.
Good, good.
Oh right, Shao You.
Wen Lang called to say
there's been a misunderstanding.
He wants to have dinner to clear it up.
Hello?
Shao You?
Yes.
Listen, it's better to bury the hatchet.
We're in the same circle,
so we'll always run into each other.
Let me host a dinner.
How about that?
Yu Shan, don't bother.
I can't stand that guy.
Seeing him ruins my appetite.
I just want to kill him.
Truth is, if murder weren't illegal,
he'd have eaten his last meal months ago.
His grave would be covered by weeds by now.
That serious?
Yes.
Forget it then.
My bad, bro.
I didn't know the whole story.
Wen Lang called me multiple times last night
asking me to mediate.
I just think if friends
can sit down for a meal,
maybe some problems can be worked out.
Yu Shan, there's no misunderstanding.
I'll only have dinner with him when he's dead.
I'll send a cash gift for the funeral
and feast for three days.
What are you saying?
All right, I won't push.
Let me know if you need anything.
After all, those Country P folks
are new friends.
We've known each other forever,
and we're closer than family.
Yeah.
If there's anything you can help with,
I'll definitely let you know.
Thanks.
Let's meet after this chaos.
Definitely.
Can't this wait till tomorrow at the office?
Mr. Sheng, the chairman
is in critical condition.
Sheng Shao You.
- How dare you show up.
- Second Young Master.
Look at what you've done to the company!
the stock has hit the limit down.
How dare you face Dad!
Don't touch me.
What?
Can't I scold him after he ruined the company?
Sheng Shao You, listen.
If anything happens to Dad,
it's all your fault.
You're so great.
Dad gave you all the shares,
and this is how you repay him?
You made him sick.
You think you deserve to visit him now?
You don't.
Get lost!
Why don't I deserve to be here?
This company was founded by my mom and dad.
Without me, you think you and your mom
could live like this?
With your pig brain
only good for eating and gambling,
you'd be begging on the streets.
Bastard.
Get lost.
Parasites should know their place.
Don't ever challenge me.
It won't end well for you.
Sheng... Sheng Shao You.
We....
We have the same father.
You're only two years older.
We're both Alphas.
But why?
Why do you inherit everything
while I'm stuck following you like a parasite?
Is it because you're S-class, but I'm B-class?
It's not fair.
Your mother knew Dad was married,
yet she had you anyway.
Was that fair to my mother?
Fair?
If there were any fairness, you wouldn't exist.
Sheng Shao Qing,
stop disgracing the Sheng family.
Go back to being a playboy.
Make way, please.
This way.
- Doctor!
- Please wait outside.
[Want do you want for dinner tonight?]
[Anything's fine, you can choose]
[You recalled a message.]
Mr. Sheng.
Why are you awake so early?
I woke up and couldn't fall back asleep
when I found you weren't here.
Why not?
I'm worried about you.
Did something happen?
Why did you leave so late at night?
My father had some issues, but don't worry.
I'll handle it
I'll wait for you to come back.
No, go to sleep first.
I can't sleep without you.
Are you still at the age
where you need someone to coax you to sleep?
You don't like coaxing people?
I don't like it.
But I can coax you.
You don't need to spend time on me.
Rest more if you have time.
I'll wait for you to come back.
- Mr. Sheng.
- Doctor Wang.
Your father is out of danger for now.
No problems temporarily.
Thank you, Doctor.
But his condition is deteriorating.
Pheromone gland tumors are hormone-sensitive.
Pheromones are vital for Alphas and Omegas.
It's unlike prostate or breast cancer
which are treatable with hormones.
His tumor was originally in situ
and not spreading,
but now,
it's infiltrating surrounding tissues.
Without a targeted drug,
once it spreads,
it will reach severe stages.
Even with a drug then,
it may be too late
I understand.
A pharmaceutical friend said this.
X Holdings' targeted drug
has completed formulation
with excellent results.
If we can contact the person in charge
to get the drug early,
it would help the chairman significantly.
I went grocery shopping for dinner.
If you want something special,
text me when you see this note.
I'll pick it up on the way. Hua Yong.
Hello, Mr. Sheng.
Are you done?
Yes. I just got home
I've bought the groceries
and will be back soon.
Anything specific you want me to buy?
No.
Shall I send a driver to pick you up?
No, the subway is convenient.
Why leave a note instead of messaging directly?
I wasn't sure if you were busy
and didn't want to disturb you.
Mr. Sheng, it's my turn to pay.
I'll hang up. See you soon.
Okay.
See you.
Without a targeted drug,
once the tumor spreads,
it will reach severe stages.
Even with a drug then, it may be too late.
[Chang Yu]
Mr. Sheng, I just finished shopping
and will be back soon.
Mr. Sheng, I'm on the subway
and will be home shortly.
Boss, Mr. Sheng called.
Should we call back soon?
No.
He's probably asking about the targeted drug.
Call back in two hours.
Understood.
The drug formulation just finished.
The maximum dosage test for human application
can start earliest on the day after tomorrow.
Got it.
I've already hinted to Wen Lang.
Tell Mr. Sheng that
the drug's person in charge will contact him.
Yes.
Boss, you oversaw this personally.
The research teams worldwide
rushed the progress
to expedite it for Mr. Sheng's father.
Wouldn't it be a pity
if he doesn't know your intentions?
It doesn't matter if he knows.
I never wanted his gratitude,
so there's nothing worth regretting.
I forgot my book in the bedroom.
I'm going to get it.
[Chang Yu]
Hello, Secretary Chang.
Mr. Sheng.
Why the sudden call?
I need your advice on something.
Is it convenient to talk now?
Go ahead.
I heard X Holdings'
targeted pheromone gland cancer drug
has completed formulation.
News travels fast.
Yes.
Our drug is indeed near clinical trials.
Why the sudden interest?
To be frank,
my father needs this drug.
You mean Sheng Fang's chairman?
Yes.
He's been on medical leave.
It's pheromone gland cancer.
Secretary Chang, I know your formula
is still confidential.
But I'm not calling as a biopharm CEO today.
I'm calling as a son
begging for help for my father.
Please help me.