Clouds never stand in anyone’s way.
All they ever do is drift.
But we often forget
we’re free to walk right through them.
Tanakom
I need your help with something.
Surprise!
Not really...
My friend said you're here to return my stuff.
Is it really that important?
Why make such a fuss?
Just give it to me.
I don’t use anything that’s touched the floor anyway.
You can have it.
Hey—how about something else?
You're not running away again, are you?
What’s your deal?
Alright, alright.
How about a race?
If I win,
you have to let us pick up where we left off.
Do you dare?
Didn’t you say we’d play tennis?
Who said that?
When did I ever agree to that?
If you're that scared to lose, we’ll just cancel.
Fine. Swimming it is.
Hey!
-Go! / - Hey!
Why the heck didn’t you swim?
Plain swimming's not cool enough.
Let’s see who can hold their breath the longest!
You're up first, Trin. I win!
You cheated! You startled me on purpose!
Like I care. You lost.
It's time to keep our promise.
Cheating breaks the whole deal, dork!
When you smile,
You're so damn cute.
I waited at the tennis court for hours.
Since when did you two get this close?
Dear readers,
When you look up and observe
the strands of white clouds in the sky,
what do you see?
A castle in the air—
woven from softness,
sprawling into a wild, endless range of white hills?
Or do you see a dark, looming wall,
one that blocks the warmth of the sun
and chokes the comfort out of light?
Let's have a baby
I'm sorry.
I've got a headache.
That cloud will only thicken into heavy,
pouring rain, or a pale, spectral snowstorm.
And at the first sign of falling drops, we already know
It’s not going to be a good day.
The lyrics of ‘Half of Everything’ by Nora Van
meditate on the irony of love—
how it shifts from dreamlike brilliance into hollow illusion.
And what about your love?
Is it a cotton-white cloud, or a dark, looming wall of threat?
You must’ve listened to the wrong song, Klai Rung.
Or maybe you only listened to half of it, just like the title says.
But ‘half of everything’
doesn’t mean you get to choose only one side.
White or dark, bright or brooding, it’s all just projection.
We see only what we choose to see.
And if love becomes a wall
standing between you and the future,
then maybe there’s no other choice but to tear it down.
A sky without clouds
might be unbearably hot—
but it still glows, and clearly shows the way forward.
Klai Rung, August 1969
What are you reading?
I could hear you laugh from out there.
Just a column.
Are you hungry? Want to head out?
It seems Klai Rung
should stop listening to that song for a while
and try to figure out what love truly means.
Only then can he come back and listen to it again.
Have you read what they wrote about you in the paper today?
What did they say?
Here.
"Colonel Krailert:
New Power Plants Confirmed to Have No Problems."
"The local residents' anxiety
was caused by a misunderstanding."
"The colonel challenged anyone suspecting misconduct
to file for investigation."
Looks like they’re trying to provoke you.
This Siam Daily Mail...
If my father were still here—
Don’t worry about it.
The journalists are just doing their job.
"Colonel Krailert:
New Power Plants Confirmed to Have No Problems."
The chief told you not to provoke him again.
We need to find a way to let people see
what the government is really doing to them.
They should know how disgustingly selfish the elites are.
All they care about is power and—
Hey,
just because someone’s born rich,
does that automatically make them
a villain to democrats like you?
I didn’t mean to blame you, Dao.
Right.
You should take it easy.
It’s too dangerous.
Colonel Krailert isn’t someone you can mess with.
Thank you, Dao.
Let's dig in.
Wanna try this?
Just eat it!
Why?
Let’s cool off with some icy treats, shall we?
This reminds me of when you were in boarding school.
You came to pick me up in your cadet uniform.
You looked so cool.
I was broke back then.
I could only afford to treat you
a scoop of ice cream—like this.
But it helped with the homesickness.
I really miss my farm house.
So?
What’s got you this stressed?
Having trouble adjusting again—
like when you were a kid?
Something like that.
If I were there, I’d be sent to see a psychiatrist.
Is it that serious?
Maybe it’s depression. That’s what I think.
You should see a doctor if you're sick.
But if it’s sadness,
time will heal everything.
That’s the same line you always use when consoling me.
Thank you.
Uncle,
you really were worried, weren’t you?
Is it the news that’s stressing you out?
Oh.
That.
The bid rigging.
Is there some truth to it?
How much truth do you need before it’s called bid rigging?
In any concession,
we have to choose the most capable company—
not just one that’s cheap but low in quality.
The country's benefit must come first.
If the army truly puts the country’s benefit first,
why not be clear and communicate that directly?
That could stop the conflict.
The army's job is to maintain peace and order.
We only need to share what's necessary.
For the rest, society needs to trust us.
Just like when you do your job,
giving your best to draft the policies.
Colonel, sir. Can we have an interview?
Sir, please answer the questions.
Go ahead.
Will the army proceed with
the Huay Kam Saeng power plant project?
And how do you plan to deal with the protesters?
"The army respects the people’s right to freedom—
as long as the law and national security are not breached."
Our job is to maintain peace and order.
I’d like to reiterate that
all freedoms  must operate within the boundaries of the law.
That's it for today.
Colonel, one more question.
Colonel. Sir.
Hey.
Why were you so silent?
Where's your fearless self today?
Did Krailert do something to you?
What? What could he have done to me?
Let me know which record you'd like.
I can give you my recommendation.
Thank you.
Director,
with news spreading like this,
wouldn't it cause even a greater conflict
between the government and the people?
Shouldn't the PR department do more
to help calm the situation?
Umm.
Why don't you ask your uncle?
It's the army's business—
not for my PR department to step in
and correct every single piece of news, bro.
Do you want me to hold a press conference
on their behalf?
It's not our business to begin with.
For people with bias,
no matter how solid the information you feed them,
they’ll just keep protesting.
But they are protesting because they don't understand.
What if we make them see what we see?
You're so damn idealistic.
You’ll understand what I mean
when you face the real thing, bro.
Yeah.
- Cheers. / - Cheers.
Drink up. Don't be so serious.
- I'm leaving. / - Alright.
Good luck, sir.
Look at the rain.
Let's go.
Hey.
This is Chopin's Nocturnes!
Good stuff, huh?
Why so serious?
Life’s short—let’s make the most of it.
I think I’ve made the most of mine.
Come on. Let's play in the garden.
No. It's raining.
We'll just get wet, not die.
Come quickly!
Because it’s great—
people have been listening to it for generations.
That's why it's called classical music.
So you like it 'cause you like it,
or because others like it?
Like is like.
And what about you?
A hippie like you,
must be digging psychedelic rock.
I like all kinds of music.
If we limit ourselves to one category,
how would we know
what we might have missed?
- I'm leaving. / - Stay a bit longer.
You're happy now, right?
Who told you I'm happy?
Since you sat down next to me,
there hasn’t been a single moment
your brows were furrowed.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Then stay.
If we stay like this forever,
That's too long.
moment after moment...
after a moment...
It becomes eternity.
moment after moment...
after a moment...
Dear readers,
The one who truly doesn't know what love
is should be Sarasawadee—
not me.
My self-imposed exile from music
hasn’t helped me understand the song any better.
If you dare as much as you claim,
then be brave enough to keep listening
to the same old song with me,
until we both agree on its meaning.
How did you get here?
Sir,
let me handle him.
That's alright. You can leave.
NW
Bh5A
P. 194
Student,
Thanks for letting me gather data from you.
Why didn't you gather my heart, prof.
Well...
Student,
Prof,
don’t you think you’re being too loud?
Student,
if the power plants could make my dorm room cooler,
I’d have no objections.
You can interview me, prof.
Oh, auntie Noi!
How are you? I miss you, you know?
I miss you too, Tanwa.
Hi guys!
That's our super senior. Tanwa!
Watch where you’re going—don’t fall for me.
Good morning, senior Tanwa.
Don’t greet me with your palms like that—
you’re already a prof!
Oops, my bad. I forgot.
You're still a student?
Hello, Tanwa!
First I majored in history,
now I’ve switched to philosophy.
- Tanwa, how it's going? / - Hello guys!
Have you eaten?
- Of course! / - yes!
It must have been ten years.
Haven't you heard?
Learning is for life. This is
the life I've chosen.
How can you call this a choice?
Not choosing is also a choice.
Trin, do you think it's wrong...
Let's say
a super senior student and an invited lecturer could...
You're a student.
Know your place.
Ran!
- Hello! / - Hi guys.
How y'all
Come here.
Yo girls, where you go'in? How ‘bout lunch with me?
- That's her boyfriend! / - Really?
Yes!
Guys!
This is Ran.
He’s a classmate of our seniors.
- Hello / - Hello
He works at Siam Daily Mail.
He wants to interview us about Huay Kam Saeng.
Are you the one who wrote about Padoem’s
possible bid rigging through Krailert?
Right?
Yes, that's me, bro.
Wow!
You’re so damn cool!
Full respect, bro!
Oh, Ran—
Just now I saw Padoem's son and Krailert's nephew.
going somewhere together.
They looked close. I bet those two families
must have something going on with the bid rigging.
I thought so too.
We gonna join the seniors rallying the mob?
I have a shift at the hotel.
Just take a leave.
It won't hurt.
That's okay. Let him be.
Let's eat. Victor, are you free today?
We can have a meeting as well.
I'm free.
Where shall we go then?
Boom! Since you're free,
we're going to eat at Victor's! Sweet!
Auntie Num's food is to die for.
Simply irresistable.
Ran,
Are you joining us? You should try my mom's food.
Yeah. It tastes heavenly.
Sure, bro.
I'll also interview you guys about the power plants.
(Call number NW A5Bh 2506, P.194)
("My Dear Monster" by Bharadorn Sakda)
Four,
remain in your existence along the path of the world,
where love is nothing but emptiness for you.
Fried duck egg with madan fish sauce. It gotta be mine.
Dream on!
I’m the guest, you’re the host.
It should be mine.
You sure you’re a guest?
You eat here barely less than I do.
Look out! What's that?
Hey—what’cha doin’?
Get something else.
Do you have to fight like this?
Gosh, stop it already.
What a joke—you eat like cows
and still can’t pay for your own feed!
Hey!
Don’t give a damn—just eat.
Wait! The fried egg must be shared equally.
Hands off the egg!
Tiva, don’t say crap like that in front of others, okay?
They'll say you're a fucking commie.
Eat up.
That's at least better than a capitalist dictatorship.
No system is perfect.
Every system has its own flaw.
Uncle, do you want me to bring that to the Reverend?
Thank you, Nuch.
Victor, can you bring the funeral speech from my room?
Yes, Pa.
Ivan Salenko.
Hey, Victor, look at this.
What?
Is the author your Pa?
The (In) visible Cage :
Stalin's Reign of Terror Exposed
by Ivan Salenko
No,
It can't be published.
Why not?
Because I'm living here illegally.
If the Soviet government finds out,
my family will be in trouble.
looks like it won't be easy.
But the situation has changed.
The democratic camp like the US would want it.
It should be published for the world to read.
This could be the chance
for your voice to be heard again, uncle.
Come on, Pa. Things have changed.
A country like the USA,
where they have democracy, would want this published.
and when it's published,
your voice will be heard all over the world.
You'll get your chance again.
Does my voice even matter
in the world controlled by those in power?
It has enough value
for them to want to destroy it,
and force you to leave your homeland.
That's the reason why
it must be published.
Come on, Pa.
Let's do it.
Woohoo! That's it!
Yo, Prof!
Your class is over.
What are you doing here?
No answer?
That means you can’t let anyone know about it.
I'm gathering data from the students for the NESDC
to find solutions for the Huay Kam Saeng power plant project
and align with the needs of the people.
You're not the only one
who wants to change this country.
I'm doing that right now.
Okay.
Why don't you ask me?
Aren't I
a student?
I need enough samples.
I've got loads of friends in the volunteer club.
But you need to get my permission first.
Stir-fried chicken and ginger on rice.
Don't add too much ginger.
One ginger chicken—no ginger!
One thing,
the government is not expelling
people from Huay Kam Saeng.
They want to bring in developers
and help improve the community's basic infrastructure.
If we want to build factories,
first we need irrigation, electricity, roads.
No doubt you're from a military and capitalist family.
You think just like them.
What if they get money,
but have to live with polluted air and water?
How long can they last?
Right, that's why
they need security measures for the community.
And this so-called prosperity,
have the people even asked for it?
Even if they didn't ask for it,
does that give you the right to freeze them?
The world has to move forward.
For someone who lives in comfort like you,
no doubt you only care about materialistic needs.
Mr. Victor,
do you think judging people by their economic status—
saying rich people are bad, poor people are good—
is fair to all parties?
I'm on your side.
I came from the countryside.
I grew up on the farm.
Ginger chicken rice.
This is on the house.
Didn't you say you want to understand the villagers?
Then you must know how to live and eat like them.
This fermented fish chilli paste—
can you eat it?
"For you alone" by Thatsanarth
Page nineteen
Please tell me, all this time,
what is your feeling for me?
Hatred,
like when I thought of the enemy who annihilated me.
Pretentious,
the look in her eyes
betrayed her, revealing the opposite.
Let's say our farewell with this last sentence,
for good.
this life no longer has any meaning,
Now that you know the truth,
please go away.
Did he read it?
Why's there no code this time?
What are you doing?
Is it right? The thing you're doing?
Why?
Is loving someone
a crime?
What are you doing?
If you don't want to see me,
why did you keep leaving messages?
Why didn't you run away?
It's...
- It's because you never stop, I... / - That's not true.
It's your heart that doesn't want to stop this.
Every book you use is all romance.
The sentences you underlined
were trimmed to sound like rejection—
when in truth, the contexts for those
were love scene, plain and simple.
Stop denying it, Naran.
Let's listen to our own hearts.
That's all your thinking.
I feel nothing for you.
What are you looking at?
At a stonewaller.
Who's the stonewaller?
If you don't have any feelings for me,
just walk away.
Why did you kiss me?
Holy shit.
Dear readers,
In truth, there are songs we will never fully understand.
Yet, sometimes,
we should simply let our emotions flow with the music.
(Forbidden Love)
Ma'am,
the guayacan tree you ordered is here?
Should I plant it now?
How wonderful! Thank you, Veera.
Don't you have to accompany the colonel today?
He drove himself today,
so I have time to take care of the house.
I see. Then plant it, Veera.
Oh, Veera—
Let me know how much you've spent on the plant.
I won't allow you to pay this time.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, Wut.
Say which faculty we're in again?
Political science, dude.
Why are you asking?
Why does Victor
look so interested in that invited Economic lecturer?
True. They used to fight like cats and dogs, but now they seem to get along so well.
Excuse me,
but your opinion is truly naive.
Fixing problems at the structure?
Waiting for the next election?
That's how democracy works.
You can't take to the streets every time there's a problem.
Do we have democracy now?
That's why we're protesting.
But taking to the streets won’t fix anything—
except for chaos.
I've seen it with my own eyes.
People actually died.
They could be someone’s children,
parents,
friends,
or people they love deeply.
Who is to be blamed then? Protesters?
Those giving the orders are sure to be blamed.
It's not as important who's right and who's wrong
as losing someone dear to you.
Then what should we do? Pretend to be ignorant
and let them do whatever they want?
Not make our demands heard?
I’m doing my best for the country right now—
through the economic development plan I'm drafting.
That would only benefit the rich and the dictators, like before.
Wait and see.
Thank you for debating with me.
Trin.
They're about to start.
But we're still discussing.
Trin's here for my gig.
The loudspeakers are loud enough.
I'm sure we can hear it from here.
Whoa—
chill out, bro!
You know?
That jerk...