20 July 1969
5...4...3...2...1...0
All engines running. Lift-off. We have a lift-off,
at 32 minutes past the hour. Lift-off on Apollo 11.
Check if everything is okay.
Yes, sir.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
This is the night we shine!
But no one shines brighter than our host, Moira!
Welcome you all to...
Grand Paradiso!
Now comes the historic moment!
On its own now, but with Columbia near at hand,
it coasted around to the back side of the Moon,
and there, while out of direct communication with the Earth,
it fired its engine to slow its descent
to a touchdown on the near side of the Moon.
Collins in Columbia continued in orbit, awaiting their return.
Okay, I'm going to leave that one foot up there
and both hands down to about the fourth rung up.
There you go.
That's one small step for man
One giant leap for mankind
Ladies and Gentlemen,
Neil Armstrong just said...
That's one small step for man
One giant leap for mankind
That's one small step for a man
One giant leap...
for mankind.
For those not planning a trip to the moon anytime soon...
We Moonshine
got this song for you.
Excuse me, Ms. Moira,
That gentleman who's talking to M.L. Tanakom
Who is he?
A friend from the time when he was in England?
That's Dr. Trin Suwannapas.
Colonel Krailert's nephew.
Voilà! The heartthrob from Paris.
Is he that famous?
Tanwa? Moonshine's lead singer?
Yeah, you bet.
Do you know who his father is?
Padoem Chatbodi.
You sure?
Of course.
Father and son damn hate each other's guts.
I'm leaving now.
got an appointment with the higher-ups.
Hey Trin, I still haven’t shown you all the cuties yet.
I'm so sorry, sir.
Hey there!
Boy!
Could you shine my shoes quickly? I’m in a bit of a rush.
I’ll tip you big—promise.
Skip the ribbon—and scrub harder up front.
Yes, right there.
I'm so fucking ready.
Wait. We need a signal from Victor.
Don't rush it—we’ll just screw up the plan.
Okay, bro.
Here.
Thanks a lot.
Thank you, bro.
Trin.
Good evening, sir.
Oh, now we have to call you Dr. Trin.
It's been so many years.
Since the Deputy Secretary-General of
the National Economic and Social Development Council
is not here yet.
let me tell you frankly.
My boss, the Governor of Bank of Thailand,
would kill to have you on board.
Just think about it—being the governor’s assistant
is a big deal
That role puts you on the right track
to becoming the Bank of Thailand Governor yourself.
Thank you, sir.
Good evening, Mr. Deputy Secretary-General.
Good evening.
How are you doing, Tanat?
You’ve really been thriving at the BOT, huh?
I’m deeply grateful—I genuinely owe this to you.
I learned a lot from my time at NESDC.
No matter where you are,
you can still make a difference for the country.
Dr. Trin,
in your application,
you said you want to join
the National Economic and Social Development Council.
Yes, sir.
The reason why I invited you and Tanat today
to our informal meeting is to make sure
it’s clear that the BOT Governor’s assistant role
is not one that’s offered to just anyone.
I understand if you want to change your mind
or go back home and think it through.
I won't change my mind.
Trin, having a second thought is not a bad idea.
I did make a decision, really.
I want to join the NESDC.
I want to apply the knowledge and experience I gained abroad
to contribute to the betterment of this country,
just as I always hope for.
Hey, Victor's here.
They have landed on the moon.
That's fucking more exciting than the election.
Look at those guys waving guns and grabbing cash—
so hyped about the moon landing,
they fucking forgot millions
are still out here barefoot in the dirt.
Rallying the crew now. We’re marching to the hotel.
Victor, grab these posters and flyers—
start spreading them now. I’ll stall the cops.
You take care.
Don't get yourself arrested.
We just need enough noise to hit the headlines.
Don’t let them pin anything on you.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Steer clear of Huay Kam Saeng!
Just stay obsessed with flying to the moon!
Return the land! To the hands of the people!
No to capitalists! No to investors!
Have the driver pick him up at the rear of the hotel.
Make sure they’re gone before the guests step outside.
Be careful—reporters' lurking.
Yes, sir.
There are protesters outside, sir.
You'd better leave now. I'll handle it from here.
Sounds good.
Colonel, speak with Mr. Padoem—
stick to what we agreed on.
The boss said no negotiations.
Yes, sir.
They are just a bunch of cattle;
let them meet the butcher, and they'll be tamed
and for the stubborn ones,
you just send them to the slaughterhouse.
I hope you can come in as soon as you can.
Just start preparing for the job.
Oh, Colonel. Good evening!
I'm beyond impressed with your nephew.
In the end he chose us over the BOT.
Trin always makes a good call.
A forward-thinking man like him
can get worn down by bureaucracy.
Most don’t last long.
We’d be glad to have you with us for the long term.
So, about the army’s land,
the students are protesting—what exactly is going on there?
It's just a misunderstanding.
I'll get going.
See you later.
Trin
The driver will pick you up at the back. Go home first.
I have another appointment with someone important.
I can head back on my own.
Just feel like taking a walk around the city.
Since coming back from France, I haven’t really seen
what Bangkok’s been up to lately, uncle.
Okay. Be careful.
Uncle
Shouldn't we find another way
to communicate to the students?
This project will benefit all parties.
The Public Relations Department's General Director
is Tanakom's boss.
Don't worry. I'll handle it.
No power plants in Huay Kam Saeng!
No dams!
I'm just taking a picture.
No capitalists!
No power plants!
No investors! Return the land to the people!
No capitalists!
Hey!
Cowards!
You bunch of cronies!
what have you ever actually done for the people?
Don't go. It's dangerous.
Come with me if you're worried.
You know my situation.
You're a real coward.
Claire, please.
You know what?
I really hope you pay back the government
for every single baht they invested in you.
If one day, the same thing happens to your country,
I hope you’ll stand up for your people.
You don’t have to fight for me.
Boss
How it's going?
Nothing to worry about.
The students are just holding up some banners.
Still, the press got plenty of shots.
Tomorrow, every headline
will cover only the moon landing.
Sir
Today is your wedding anniversary.
Handle it for me, will you?
Get roses this time. Deliver them straight to my wife.
I'll drive myself home.
Yes, sir.
The contract, sir.
Thanks.
No power plants! Return the land to the people!
Please share what’s happening in Hauy Kam Saeng.
Hey, Sarge—
there's a protest at Grand Paradiso.
You need to move, now.
Hurry!
You've got a nice piano at home,
but you chose to keep playing here.
It just feels nicer here.
All credits to the hotel owner.
Perhaps you could make your home
a bit more welcoming, Colonel.
Mr. Padoem is going to the cigar room.
Thank you, Moira.
How many do you want?
Just a bag, auntie.
One bag? How about two? I give you one for free.
Okay, two bags. But let me pay.
Save them for the students.
Are you from around here?
I used to go to school nearby.
Back then, I'd sneak out
to grab snacks from you all the time.
You'd always slipped me a little extra,
afraid I wouldn’t have enough to feel full.
I’m way too old to remember something like that.
But look, I've got myself a really handsome customer!
Another handsome face. How many do you want?
I'll have what he's having.
How much is it per bag now, auntie?
One baht, dear.
Two baht for extra size.
One baht?
That's three times than what I used to pay.
It was only a quarter back then.
Everything’s getting more expensive these days—
I’ve got to raise my prices too.
It’s the only way I can stay afloat.
That reminds me—where’ve you been all this time?
I've been away for nine years and just came back.
I see.
Here you are.
Alright, auntie, I’ll get going now. I’ll drop by often.
Okay. See you again soon.
Two bags for you, right?
Here.
I'm full now. You can keep them to sell later, okay?
(Huay Kam Saeng says no to the Army. No capitalists.)
Can I have one?
It's you.
Did you shine my shoes earlier?
What do you want it for?
How well do you know about this?
I know enough to see it’s their home—
the land that gave them life.
long before the idea of ‘land titles’ even existed.
You do realize it’s a risky area—
full of thieves
and Mafia.
The land is too poor to farm.
All the state wants is to develop it
into something sustainable for the future.
Are you the army's spokeperson?
They arrested Keng! Hurry! Let's go!
Give this to your boss.
Stop!
Stop right there!
Don't you think that's too much, Colonel?
Which part do you think is too much, Mr. Padoem?
The part that says my company has to invest
in developing the surrounding area
which has nothing to do with the power plants.
Noted.
Colonel.
Yes?
Please sit down.
We haven’t even begun negotiations.
I’m only here to deliver the documents.
All I need is a yes or no from you,
so I can pass it along to General Pracha.
I didn't say no.
I’m simply voicing my concerns—as an equal partner.
A partner?
The Huay Kam Saeng power plant project was my idea.
I’m the one who invested—
my money, my people, my resources.
The project wouldn't exist without me.
Certainly.
This project was born from your vision
and dedication, Mr. Padoem.
And because the army believed you deserved the chance.
But the land belongs to the army.
The concession wasn't granted through open competition
but through selection.
Your company was selected because it was the fittest.
Sometimes...
you have to lose the battle to win the war.
Aunt Dhevi.
Have you eaten?
I had my fill at the reception.
looks like I need to skip dinner tonight.
I took a walk around my old school.
I bought you some fried dough balls.
This auntie sells the best dough balls in the world.
They look yummy.
How was your meeting with the Deputy Secretary-General?
All set. I start next week.
I'm happy for you.
Uncle Krailert didn't come back with you?
He said he had a meeting with someone important.
I see.
A bouquet from the Colonel, ma'am. For the anniversary.
Purple tulips.
Very pretty.
They are my favorite flowers, Veera.
Thank you.
(Happy Anniversary, Love, from Krailert)
At least
even if he's always buried in work
your uncle still remember I love purple tulips.
They are beautiful. They suit you.
I like them too.
Aunt Dhevi,
The food they served at the reception was so bland.
Maybe tonight,
I'll have to rely on your cooking.
Of course!
Let's have dinner.
Bring the dough balls too.
I made your favorite dish today, see?
All day and night we work without rest
We hold our heads high, doing our best
When evening comes, we let ourselves play
And when it’s night, we dance the night away
We smile with joy, hearts open wide
We are proud women, with nothing to hide
Mom, you’re so loud they can hear you
all the way down the alley!
Who’s got a problem with my singing, huh?
Hey—watch the knife!
I’ll tear your guts out.
What, you’re not enjoying my free concert?
Thank you, Nuch.
I'll take it from here.
You'd better go home.
No need.
If you want to help, go wash your hands first.
How am I supposed to know
where your hands have been all day?
If my customers got diarrhea,
Hey!
I’ll scold you so hard you’ll feel it in your next life.
I know.
What’s got you all grinning and singing like that?
A new customer complimented her today.
Aha!
- What did that guy say? / - Cutie Auntie?
"Your periwinkle curry is tasty"
Come on, Nuch—how can you be so dense?
Periwinkle refers to me,
and tasty means pretty.
That fella can’t say anything without slipping in a little jab.
You’re not married to a writer like me.
You wouldn't understand.
Hey, how long are you gonna keep laughing?
Go away if you're not helping.
Help's coming right up.
I'll give you a hand.
Mom
I've got a lot of tips today.
Just give me half. You can keep the rest and go.
If you have to stay up late tonight to study,
don't wake up early tomorrow. Nuch can give me a hand.
Hey, I wanna sleep in too!
Says someone who has work to do!
Otherwise just drag your lazy ass to school.
See you at four then, auntie.
Uh-huh
Victor
Yes, dad.
Take this to the Reverend at the church.
seems like there are more eulogies to write these days.
A step mistaken
Not everyone will take a great leap
On the day the world is celebrating
there are still many
who live with poverty,
fatigue,
and loneliness—
like the far side of the moon:
the side without reflection,
the side unseen.
Yet the near side, glowing bright,
may not tell the whole truth.
The hidden face, the one we overlook,
may hold a secret someone knows
but never dares to speak—
just like us,
just like them,
trapped in the shadow,
unable to break free.
But how long can we pretend to be outsiders,
when sooner or later,
we must choose a side to stand on?
Claire, your apartment is amazing!
But I'd prefer having a dad
who bought me something this cool.
They look wonderful together. Those two.
It's a pity you're leaving soon.
There’s a whole list of things
we were supposed to do together.
Oh baby.
He cannot stay. Duty calls—
he must return to serve his country
He's a scholarship student.
Wanna go out dancing?
Okay? Let's go dancing. Now!
Wanna race?
(giggle)
Marry me.
Why did you bring me here?
Didn't you say you wanted to meet the Director-General?
Yeah...
Exactly! That's why
But here? Are you serious, punk?
Mr. Trin, you're underestimating me and my boss.
Oh,
Tanakom!
Come on in!
They're here, Sucha?
Since the afternoon.
Come on in, Dr. Trin.
Welcome Dr. Trin!
That's the Director-General, AKA my boss.
He was our senior back in school.
Hey Tanakom!
This way!
Sir...
This is a friend of mine—we were classmates.
He was also in the same house as me back in school.
Really?
That makes him our housemate.
Come take a dip!
Sucha, pour me some booze.
Dude.
Consider my job's done.
I'm leaving, okay?
Take it off.
Your jacket—go on, take it off
Leave it there. Don’t worry, no one’s after what’s yours.
Now the socks. The shoes.
Roll up your sleeves...the trousers too.
Or—
just strip down to you undies.
Messy business, this undressing, huh.
Much better.
Make youself comfy.
Welcome to the far side of the moon.
Cheers.
I'd like the press to publicize the other aspect
of the Huay Kam Saeng power plant project
so the people can see all sides of the issue.
The latter part you're reading
is my economic analysis
of the Huay Kam Saeng case.
Did Krailert ask to you come?
No, sir.
I ask Tanakom to set up this meeting with you.
My uncle doesn't know about it.
The documents look solid.
Thank you, sir.
But let me warn you—as your senior from school:
Spreading this kind of information
is way too risky.
This is Thailand,
not Europe or America.
If what you've written
crosses the wrong people,
even being Krailert's nephew won't protect you.
They can make you disappear—any time, anywhere.
That's why I came to see you.
I owe you my sincere thanks
Tanakom always says he’s lucky to have you as his boss—
because you’re direct,
and principled to the core.
Today, I’ve seen that for myself.
Uh-huh
You two are real busy kissing each other’s asses.
Alright.
I'll take care of it.
United in spirit, our brotherhood stands
Side by side, with ready hands
Unity our armor, faith our might
Bound as one, in shared light
United in spirit, our brotherhood stands
With common dreams and willing hands
Unity our armor, faith our might
Bound as one, our hearts held tight
Com'on guys. Let’s keep ‘em coming!
Sucha, top off our drinks!
I think he said
"a man"
not just "man."
I beg your pardon?
What Neil Armstrong said
when he landed on the moon.
He should've meant his own small step—
a man's step
that's "a man."
But I don’t think “man” was wrong either.
He could've meant
all of humanity—the entire human race.
Right.
Can we evaluate a man
without forcing him
to be a part of something?
You think we can really escape it—
the fact that we have to belong to something?
Sure.
Have you tried?
No, thanks.
You’ve never run from anything?
How about you?
I lost count.
Did you succeed?
I don't know.
I don't care.
If you want to escape it all.
You'd have to fly to the moon.
You still won't make it.
There's a rabbit.
There's a rabbit on the moon?
That's a good one.
What are you writing?
A man wants to escape from the Earth.
He sneaks onto Apollo 11,
and flies to the moon
hoping that
when Neil and the other guys
return to the Earth,
he’ll be all alone up there forever.
But the problem is...
The problem is...
There's a rabbit.
What does he do then?
He lets the bunny out.
Wh..
You know, he has to take a hare-raising leak.
Not funny?
Tinkle in the burrow.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Tanwa.
I'm Trin.
Tinkle in the burrow.
My response to Sarasawadee:
First, your critique
on the song 'The Far Side of the Moon'
by Moonshine
is unexpectedly fresh.
I praise you with all my heart.
Next,
that very freshness leaves us, the readers, wondering
if you might still be of tender age—
too young to have tasted the world.
'The Far Side of the Moon'
speaks of things we haven't fully grasp,
things we may never know,
unless we find the courage
to step away from the bright side.
Ignorance will always be a gateway to the abyss—
but more frightening still,
is the stubbornness to see only what one wishes to see.
I'm bleeding.
Why?
That comment cuts deep!
(My response to Klai Rung)
In the end you still don't see, even though it's painfully obvious.
Lastly,
If you're so sure Klai Rung was in the wrong,
and you are so sure you're right,
go back and read the song's title.
If you still can't grasp the bright side of this issue,
Please contact Moonshine.
and ask them to change the song title to:
'The Dark Side of the Moon'
May that bring you peace.
(Klai Rung)
Nothing remains the same.
Shit...